<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[With Obama’s Approval, Russia Selling 130 Tons of Uranium to Iran #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Under the New Trump Standard, Why Wasn't Obama Impeached?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GIULIANI: IMPEACHMENT IS ABOUT HIDING OBAMA CORRUPTION – “BILLIONS LAUNDERED, EXTORTION AND BRIBERY” #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Three Senate Committees Open Investigations Into Obama-Biden Ukrainian Election Interference #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Clapper admits on CNN that Obama ordered him &amp; others to begin spy &amp; coup against Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,400-Year-Old Gingko Tree Sheds A Spectacular Ocean Of Golden Leaves #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ISIS strap suicide vests to PUPPIES in horror footage of sick front line bomb tactic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats Call For Flags To Be Flown At Half-Mast To Grieve Death Of Soleimani #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People Who Are Not Happy With Themselves #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update: Teens Arrested Who Assaulted Florida Boy On School Bus For Wearing Trump Hat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook suspends conservative comedian's account #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['They’ve Awoken a Giant': 20+ Virginia Counties Become 2A Sanctuaries Overnight - GunsAmerica Digest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some of The Deadliest Samurai Were Women, But History Forgot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NFL Honors Michael Vick, Man Who Tortured And Killed Dogs For Fun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Good Guy With a Gun’ Who Stopped Church Gunman Receives State’s Highest Honor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama Calls UN Security Meeting – US Officials Not Invited – Today Breaking News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tlaib’s Son Arrested For Setting Fire To City Hall Christmas Tree – AJUA news #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schumer Accidentally Admits Trump Is Being Impeached "Without the Facts Coming Out" #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi Approves $4.8 Million In ‘Impeachment Consulting Fees’ To Clinton Foundation – The Cube News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI admits illegal wiretapping of President Trump, issues apology #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roseanne Barr To Give Speech At Trumpettes' Gala At Mar-A-Lago Over Super Bowl Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't bother going to my Funeral #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Malls across U.S. opening early so kids with autism can visit Santa in a calmer environment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scream Queen Jamie Lee Curtis Attacks Donald Trump in Bizarre Tweet - Bounding Into Comics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Minnesota Dem Congressman Says He Will Vote Against Impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Greta Going on Hunger Strike Until Trump is Removed – News leno #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kirstie Alley Unloads On Trump-Hating, 'PC Crazy' Hollywood #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China to Buy Additional $32 Billion in U.S. Farm Goods Over Two Years, Sign Deal in January #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate approves Trump's first black female judge nominee #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN Poll: US economy receives its best ranking in nearly 20 years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miami’s commute is officially the worst in the country. We can’t believe it either #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida: Muslim mechanic admits sabotaging American Airlines plane at Miami International #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giuliani: George Soros "Is Involved" With Hunter Biden/Ukraine Corruption Scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iraq: Protesters celebrate as head of Iran's Quds force General Soleimani killed in US airstrike #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The McCain-Soros connection: It started after senator got caught in ‘Keating Five’ scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Terrence K. Williams on Twitter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[California Considering Tax On Breathing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best actor award goes to,dog GIFs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman in hospital after 'confusing builder’s foam with mousse' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Missing POW’s Remains Returned to His Widow 63 Years After His Death #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are still 12 House Democrats who don't support impeachment proceedings. Why? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The LimoBike Is a Harley Motorcycle Up Front and a Limousine In The Back #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adam Schiff traveled to Ukraine 8/24-8/31 and Jerry Nadler signed off on all expenses on 9/11 day before complaint… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Image: George Soros Said: 'I'm Going to Bring Down the U.S. by Funding ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patton Oswalt: If You Voted For Donald Trump "You're A Stupid Asshole" - Bounding Into Comics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Female Army sergeant repels ambush, kills 3, becomes first woman to earn Silver Star since WWII #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump supporters stage 'Trump flag drop' at Mall of America #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump is Stopping the United Nations from Becoming the Single World Government #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democratic Rep. Debbie Dingell confesses she was blackmailed by party to support Impeachment,lawyers swing into inv… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump warns Iran, terrorists: 'We will find you &amp; eliminate you;' 'We stopped a war, didn't start one' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Georgia sheriff's concealed-carry sign goes viral #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The shadowy Iranian spy chief who helped plan Benghazi #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi Wants To Empty Social Security To Pay The National Debt – Today Breaking News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People in California now Pooping in Grocery Stores #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giuliani Cleared of All Wrongdoing in Ukraine – AJUA news #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Epstein listed 301 Brits in pervert's 'little black book' found by FBI #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dow, S&amp;P 500 close at record highs after Trump signs first phase of U.S.-China trade pact #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Texas law allowing people to carry guns in church went into effect Sept. 1 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man carries away fridge he bought for girlfriend after catching her cheating #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton’s Faith Healer Arrested for Running Biggest Ever Child Sex Ring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump signs law to punish websites for sex trafficking #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran Declines To Sign Colin Kaepernick After Reviewing Workout Video #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What 'universal healthcare' really looks like in socialist Cuba]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rose McGowan, John Cusack bash killing of Iran's Soleimani, slam Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new "beauty trend" for 2020 – to decorate your nails with tiny hands and feet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHY IS NEW BOOK ABOUT TRANSGENDERS NAMED AFTER MICHELLE OBAMA? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giuliani: George Soros "Is Involved" With Hunter Biden/Ukraine Corruption Scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RALLY DAY: Sights and sounds from the YUGE crowds at the Trump rally in Toledo, Ohio #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Swedish Child Beaten By Muslim Immigrant For Having Blue Eyes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Until you have buried someone you love. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Men's Fashion 2020 Collection Is Finally Here! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dumb and Dumber Actor Jeff Daniels Tells Stephen Colbert: America Needs Someone Who Can Punch Donald Trump in the F… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama Waited 13 Hours To Help In Benghazi, Trump Waited 13 Minutes To Help In Iraq (Opinion) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They said they just wanted gay marriage, now we're being told to accept child drag queens, incest and bestiality ·… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eric + Lara Trump Declare Victory In War On Christmas - 'You Can Say Merry Christmas Again' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[183 Australians have been charged with starting bushfires this season #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden on Hunter: "I Didn't Know He Was On The Board Of That Company" #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impeachment Backfiring: SECOND Democrat Leaves The Party In 24 Hours - Daily News Updates #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make Them Cry Again 2020 Hat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats chant 'No one is above the law!' after giving drivers licenses to illegal aliens #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton Pictured With Multiple Pedophiles ; Tony Podesta and George Nader — Steemit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ukraine Just Turned Against Obama and Biden -- Formal Investigation Underway #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giuliani Says He Has Evidence Impeachment is a 'Cover-Up' of Democrat Corruption #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH VIDEO Lebron To NBA: ’Dump The Anthem Or I’ll Quit’ – Magna newspapers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Photo of the Day: Things you see in Miami when you get close to Christmas]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman with a beautiful mind is good for a lifetime #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looking like garbage increases your chance of seeing people you know at the store by 90%, study shows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida deputies searching for man who broke into home to suck victim’s toes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael Douglas shares touching photo of dad on 103rd birthday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[24 people dead 500 million animals dead 8,000 koalas dead Over 5.5 million hectares burned (the size of Belgium) -… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OFFICIAL PLEDGE TO VOTE FOR TRUMP IN 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Muslim Ilhan Omar Recites Islamic Prayer To Allah At Catholic Church In One World Religion Chrislam Service Attende… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Schumer: Having Hunter Biden testify would make impeachment trial a 'circus' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OBAMA WILL CLAIM KENYAN CITIZENSHIP TO KEEP FROM BEING TRIED FOR TREASON #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FISA Judge Collyer Steps Down Unexpectedly #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: AG Bill Barr Directly Targets George Soros… It’s Finally Happening]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[REVEALED: House Democrats Violated The First, Fourth, Fifth, And Sixth Amendments In Impeachment Inquiry… Here’s Ho… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ilham Omar Sides With Iran, Vows To Stop Trump From Protecting USA From Terrorists #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi wants details from Trump after U.S. kills Iranian commander #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Retiree to Spend Rest of Life at Holiday Inn, Since It's Cheaper Than a Senior Home #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
