<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists just discovered that an asteroid may have ended 'Snowball Earth' 2.2 billion years ago… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yang Says He Would ‘Pardon Trump’… There’s Just One Problem With That #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 can't-miss sales to shop this weekend at The North Face, Wayfair, and more #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rep. Jerry Nadler And Trump’s Attorney, Pat Cipollone, Blast Each Other, Chief Justice Roberts Steps In…… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Billionaire Dem 2020 Hopeful Thinks American Farmers Are Brainless Dopes #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best-dressed at the Grammys 2020: Ariana Grande, Lizzo and Lil Nas X turn heads on the red carpet… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Pompous Pelosi’s Impeachment Ceremonies Backfire Badly #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHO declares coronavirus global emergency; State Department raises travel warning to highest level… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HISTORIC: Trump Gives Rush Limbaugh Medal Of Freedom In Middle Of SOTU Speech #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Americans sour on milk, could these famous dairy brands disappear from your fridge? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry, Feminists: Bond Producer Says, ‘He Can Be Of Any Color, But He Is Male’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump, William Barr and Roger Stone made for a turbulent week at DOJ: Here's what you need to know… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MSNBC’s Joy Reid Says In Trump’s America ‘Nazis Are Walking Around’ And People Are Afraid #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isn’t It A ‘Climate Crisis’? Liz Warren Hides Behind Staffers After She Steps Out Of A Private Jet (Video)… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FACT CHECK: Looking at Trump's claims in his State of Union address #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Piers Morgan Lambasts ‘Smug, Sanctimonious Schiff’ Over ‘Impeachment Debacle’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Pocahontas’ Warren Is TANKING In The Polls, But She Has A Plan For That — Play The Woman Card!… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscars 2020: The winners list #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Glorious Weekend Filming With Fellow Deplorables In California #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASCAR vs NBA: What The Differences About Their Two Anthems Tell Us About America #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York Politicians Lied and Their Gun-Control Laws Failed Again #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ousted Recording Academy CEO alleges sexual harassment, corrupt Grammys voting #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lev Parnas accuses AG William Barr of conflict of interest, seeks special prosecutor #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyoncé's Ivy Park line for adidas selling out online but available in select stores Saturday… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[State of the Union: From a snub to a ripped speech to heavy campaign messaging, this was not your typical address… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Americanism: A Genuine Movement #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Is Adam Schiff Covering Up Michael Atkinson’s Testimony? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DOJ Rules That At Least TWO Of The FISA Warrants Were ILLEGALLY Predicated #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Terry Crews apologizes to Gabrielle Union after backlash for 'AGT' comments #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kansas City Chiefs are early favorites over San Francisco 49ers in Super Bowl LIV #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ex-priest convicted in Texas beauty queen's murder dies while serving life #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feds: Alleged leader of al-Qaida terrorist group arrested in Phoenix #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pro-Abortion Pete Asked By Pro-Life Democrat If Her Views Are Still Acceptable By The Party. Here’s What He Said…… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscars: Janelle Monáe, Chris Rock, Steve Martin skewer Academy Awards for lack of diversity #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What current Lakers stars LeBron James and Anthony Davis learned from Kobe Bryant #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ICYMI: Fox Super Bowl Ad Featuring Johnny Cash’s ‘Ragged Old Flag’ Was SPECTACULAR #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keto diet isn't the answer for weight loss, experts say. Here's what is #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: The tear-jerking 'Good Place' series finale stays far away from the Bad Place #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# trends on Twitter after he walks out over impeachment question #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Proposed rules for Trump's Senate impeachment trial could set up a heated debate on Tuesday #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, Senator, It Is NOT Congress’s Job To ‘Redistribute Wealth’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lying Billionaires and Gun Control #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brothers show off basketball skills with trick shots, crazy 3-pointers #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia: Another Examination #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Time Spent With Horses Can Be Good For Your Mental Health #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Hillary Says That She Has ‘The Urge’ To Take On Trump In 2020 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Life after basketball: Kobe Bryant's transition to Oscar, Emmy winner and AAU coach #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not So Broke After All: Hunter Biden Agrees To Temporary Child Settlement With Baby Mama #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democratic candidates talk pocketbook issues of health care, child care and higher education at Iowa debate… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats Are Pressuring GOP Senators To Call Witnesses Using… Cakes?! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Media Outraged Over Trump Blasting Generals As ‘Dopes And Babies’ But Silent During Obama’s ‘Purge’… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter Suspends Huge Pro-Trump Account For… Doing What Joe Biden Did At A Rally #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PUSSIFICATION: Skinny Dork Taunts Big Guy… That Was A BAD Idea (Video) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SAG Awards 2020: Worst-dressed stars, from Renée Zellweger to Elisabeth Moss #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VIDEO: A Black Conservative Pays Tribute to Rush Limbaugh #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Ted Cruz Lights Up Reporter For Suggesting His Young Kids Should Be In Prison #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still Winning: Latest Border Stats Show 8th Straight Month Of Improvement #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dark Money Group With Ties To AOC To Spend $500K On Ads Attacking Biden And Buttigieg #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 things to look for in this year's Super Bowl commercials #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pigskin Pundit’s Superbowl Pick #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sparks Fly At Prayer Breakfast As Trump Takes Dead Aim At Pelosi And Romney #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impeachment Defense: Team Counters Schiff’s Emotions With A Barrage of Facts (Video) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Highly talented': Fake rowing résumé allegedly touts Lori Loughlin's daughter Olivia Jade #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great-grandmother celebrates 100th birthday with rendition of 'When You're Smiling' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats Don’t Care About American Lives #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roger Stone should serve 7 to 9 years in prison for lying to Congress, prosecutors say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Trump Art: You Tell ’em I’m Coming And America’s Coming With Me! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brutally honest reviews and rankings of every Grammys 2020 performance #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Debunking The 5 Favorite Lies Of The Dems And Their Impeachment Schiff Show #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Jersey authorities investigating four JV players for allegedly beating up coach after game… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IMPEACHMENT: Mitch McConnel’s Opening Remarks Set The Tone Of What Is To Come #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DISGUSTING: House Democrats Block Vote Supporting Iranian Protesters #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodbye Sammy, Our Patriot Greyhound #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 2010s Were A Decade Of Big Tech Abuses #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dems Will Dis Trump For His Runaway Spending… Here’s Why They’re Wrong #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASTY: CDC Names US Cities With Highest STD Rates … Is Yours On The List? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: Will Ferrell, Julia Louis-Dreyfus' 'Downhill' heads in the wrong direction from start… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LGBT: Trump Vs. Preachy Pete … And Potential Foreign Policy Implications #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[49ers run wild on Packers for NFC title, set up Super Bowl matchup with Chiefs #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey NEVERTRUMPKINS: DJT Declares Religious Freedom Day 2020 And There’s More #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Formula for the NFL, Politics, Everyday Living: Do the Right Thing Every Time #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosmith drummer Joey Kramer won't be performing with group at the Grammys, judge says #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Warren Says Trump’s Judicial Appointments Are Homophobic, Racist, Sexist, And Anti-Voter… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jesus Empowers People Most Religious Folks Would Pass On #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Husband Claims He Threw $1M Cash In A Bonfire Rather Than Pay His Ex And Kids #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ilhan Omar Offended By Ted Cruz’s Statement On Faith And Patriotism… Cruz Takes Her To School… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China's coronavirus outbreak has made adopting a child a 'crushing' experience for US families… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey Socialists: We Dare You To Watch This “Tear Down This Wall” Speech Writer’s Interview (Video)… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It is All Fake News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NAVARRO: Trump Gained UNPRECEDENTED Concessions From China In This Trade Deal #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obnoxious Jerk Harasses Retail Worker … MAGA Twitter Comes To Her Rescue #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Undying love: Years after losing cancer battle, he still gets wife Valentine's Day flowers #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weddings chain Noah's Event Venue closes abruptly, stranding up to 7,500 brides and grooms #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Oscars' 10 worst best-picture winners ever, ranked (we're talking about you, 'Crash') #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Controversial Thriller Where Liberal ‘Elites’ Kidnap And Hunt ‘Deplorables’ To Be Released In March… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch: This Powerful Trump Superbowl Ad Even Impressed Some Democrats! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Kapoor, founder of Insys Therapeutics, sentenced to 66 months in landmark fentanyl bribery case… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chick Who Invoked Red Flag Law In Colorado Gets Arrested For Perjury #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHOA! Did CNN’s Alisyn Camerota Just Criticize Adam Schiff On The Air? (VIDEO) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google Wants More Government Regulation. Here’s Why. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
