<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Mumbai knocked out; Gill’s dream run continues #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ole Gunnar Solskjaer confirms Sir Alex Ferguson visit to Carrington, reveals influence he is having on Manchester U… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hogmanay lights up Scotland with fireworks, and Franz Ferdinand #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cardiff City vs Tottenham Hotspur: Premier League match preview and confirmed line-ups #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Factbox: South Africa vs Pakistan – second test #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louis C.K. Slammed After Mocking Parkland Shooting Survivors In Recent Comedy Set #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Things People Don’t Realize You’re Doing Because You Haven’t Mastered Loving Yourself Quite Yet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cummins and Australia puzzle over lack of old-ball help #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gordon Ramsay and Wife Tana Are Expecting Their Fifth Child After Miscarriage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Transfer window LIVE: Latest news, rumours and done deals as Arsenal ace linked with Juve and Liverpool set to lose… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pompeo says cooperation with Israel over Syria and Iran to continue #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everton vs Leicester City: Premier League match preview and confirmed line-ups #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Stranger Things’ Season 3 Gets Release Date — and Haunting New Poster! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[32 Microshifts You Can Start Doing Today To Transform Your 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chelsea in Isco u-turn as they pull the plug on £75m deal for Real Madrid star #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Premier League table based on every club’s home results in 2018 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Penny Marshall’s Cause of Death Revealed #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cricket: Sri Lanka series chance for NZ players to push World Cup claims #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessie James Decker Shares NSFW Nude Photo of Husband Eric Decker Enjoying His Retirement #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2018 in Review: In an Otherwise Garbage Year, Pop Culture Is What Made Us Feel #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Transfer advice including Manchester City, Man United and Southampton stars #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PSG star Adrien Rabiot to snub Spurs interest as ‘they are beneath him’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Juventus favourites to sign Arsenal midfielder with £7m-a-year contract offer #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lionel Messi, Mohamed Salah and Harry Kane among leading goal machines in European football #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrat Warren takes step to challenge Trump in 2020 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tottenham move ‘beneath’ PSG star, Mesut Ozil rules out Arsenal exit, Chelsea reject £20m bid for starlet… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jamie Vardy nets first Premier League goal of 2019 as Foxes win at Goodison Park #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carrie Underwood Shares Sign Her Second Baby’s Due Date Is Approaching #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top 14 goalkeepers of 2018 with the most league clean sheets in Europe’s top five divisions #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal vs Fulham: Premier League match preview and confirmed line-ups #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rebel Wilson Rescued Off Top of a Mountain During Ski Vacation #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best players in the top flight so far based on stats #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Manchester United ‘ready to go crazy’ to bring Napoli defender Kalidou Koulibaly #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China 2018 movie box office revenue growth slows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Reflects on Overcoming ‘Lowest Lows’ in 2018 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NZ fast bowler Jamieson takes third-best figures in T20 cricket #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Krasinski Is Officially Writing a ‘Quiet Place’ Sequel #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chelsea striker Tammy Abraham may cut short Aston Villa stay to pursue Premier League loan move… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most shocking football transfers, including Ashley Cole to Chelsea, Sol Campbell at Arsenal and Mo Johnston to Rang… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Chelsea striker Diego Costa wakes up his brother with hilarious, indoor fireworks prank #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ashwin trains at SCG nets in race for final-Test fitness #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tennis Sloane Stephens bundled out of Brisbane, Andy Murray advances #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tennis Nick Kyrgios launches Brisbane title defence #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roger Federer’s Swiss team bests Serena Williams’ American pair in mixed doubles match at Hopman Cup #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Manchester United star blasted for showing a lack of class by former Liverpool striker Dean Saunders… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alexis Sanchez backed to show true class by Ole Gunnar Solskjaer ahead of Newcastle comeback #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Afghanistan earn direct qualification in 2020 T20 World Cup #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Premier League table based on every club’s away results in 2018 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liverpool forward ‘close’ to agreeing deal with Lazio ahead of summer move #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Factbox: Departments hit by partial U.S. government shutdown #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Marco Rose? Salzburg boss and friend of Jurgen Klopp linked with Old Trafford job #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lindsay Lohan Surprises Her Hard-Partying Staff in ‘Beach Club’ Sneak Peek #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Wishes Fans ‘Laughter, Clarity and Healing’ Following Her Tough Year #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cricket: Pakistan look to fix batting woes against hostile South Africa #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marco Silva says ‘no reason to be nervous’ despite recent poor form #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Blues could line-up at end of January window with Mats Hummels, Nabil Fekir and a new striker… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPDATE 8-Big Bash League Standings #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Red Bull Salzburg boss Marco Rose ‘on Manchester United shortlist if Mauricio Pochettino turns down the job’… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Ole Gunnar Solskjaer has already bettered Jose Mourinho at Old Trafford #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal man Bukayo Saka becomes first born in 2001 to play in Premier League #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner Heads Into the New Year With a Brand New Hair Color #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez Take a Spin in a Red Convertible with Their Kids #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Leeds United beat Nottingham Forest manager Brian Clough to the signing of Gary McAllister in 1990… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stoinis makes his mark as Melbourne Stars take bragging rights #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lynn fifty in vain as Sydney Sixers complete final-over win #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tottenham top, Arsenal 11th – The Premier League table based on every club’s away results in 2018… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eleven players who could be on the move this winter, including Tottenham, Liverpool and Chelsea stars… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Channels ‘Childhood Hero’ at New Year’s Eve Costume Party With Blake Lively, Gigi Hadid: Pics! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Josh Peck Welcomes First Child With Wife Paige O’Brien — See the Precious Pic! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Premier League 2018/19 final table: Super Computer predicts where every team will finish #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ricky Martin Welcomes Baby Girl With Husband Jwan Yosef #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Mattis exits, he tells U.S. military to keep ‘faith in our country’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. agents fire tear gas at ‘violent mob’ near Mexico border #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Five reasons why Liverpool will end their 29-year hoodoo and be crowned Premier League champions this season… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Andy Cohen Reveals He’s Having a Baby Boy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liverpool 2nd, Manchester United 4th #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato Vows to Never Take Another Day ‘For Granted’ 5 Months After Apparent Overdose #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is Where You Need To Focus And Invest Yourself In 2019, Based On Your Zodiac Sign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mesut Ozil left out of Arsenal squad for Premier League clash with Fulham, Lucas Torreira drops to bench… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canterbury quick Jamieson takes third-best return in T20s #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Fickle’ Arsenal fans slammed for booing Alexandre Lacazette/Aaron Ramsey substitution before Welshman scores cruci… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huddersfield Town sign England youth international from Tottenham Hotspur #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MCG Boxing Day Test pitch rated ‘average’ by ICC #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fulham reportedly closing in on Chelsea defender Gary Cahill in attempt to solve defensive woes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[30 Fun Facts About Noah Centineo #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Posts, Then Deletes Sweet Tribute to Mac Miller #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Andy Murray admits doubt over future career as he wins on competitive return #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blues set price tag for Callum Hudson-Odoi after snubbing £20million bid from Bayern Munich #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gunners ease to New Year’s Day win against relegation strugglers #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats maneuver to end shutdown, without Trump wall money #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump invites congressional leaders to border security briefing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every deal done by top flight clubs in the January transfer window #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sadio Mane comes second to Manchester United transfer target Kalidou Koulibaly in Senegal player of the year… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonathan Van Ness Reveals He’s Single With Ariana Grande-Inspired Post #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celine Dion Rocks Out at Lady Gaga’s Las Vegas Residency — Watch! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spurs ease to New Year triumph with first-half rout #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Italy’s Uffizi demands return of Nazi-looted painting #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top U.S. commander in Afghanistan sees peace opportunity in 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Singer Jimmy Osmond suffers stroke during UK pantomime performance #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Navy pursuing block buy of two aircraft carriers: senator #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
