<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Catherine Zeta-Jones Introduces Family's New Puppy Following the Loss of Father-in-Law Kirk Douglas #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Channels Britney Spears and Justin Timberlake in All-Denim Look #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt &amp; Jennifer Aniston Have Loving Reunion at SAG Awards #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celebs Cuddling Furry Friends ... Pawesome! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Poses So Young Fan Can Get the Perfect Shot: See the Pic! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Family Rescued After Falling Through Ice on Frozen Big Bear Lake #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Wild Wild West' Star Robert Conrad Dead at 84 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Drops New Album 'Changes' -- All the Songs About Wife Hailey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Bold Type': Katie Stevens Says She Can Relate to Jane's Insecurity Over Ryan's Infidelity (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Snoop Dogg Apologizes to Gayle King Over Kobe Bryant Comments #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber's Kobe Bryant Tribute Art Raises $12,000 for MambaOnThree #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[San Francisco Giants Hire First Full-Time Female Coach in MLB History #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NikkieTutorials Talks Growing Up Transgender in First Interview Since Coming Out #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Walmart Makes Insensitive Paul Walker Joke on Twitter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt Wins First Acting Oscar, Proving Life Can Get Better #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez Takes a Rehearsal Break for Snuggle Time With Her Twins #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Schwimmer Suggests an All-Black or All-Asian 'Friends' Reboot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Norma Michaels, Star of 'King of Queens' and 'Modern Family,' Dead at 95 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sean Kingston Detained and Released As Cops Search for Guns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Vanderpump Rules' Star Lala Kent Drops Real Meryl Streep Run-in Story #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jay-Z Re-Defends NFL Partnership, Says He's Not Betraying Kaepernick #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Property Brothers' Jonathan Scott Talks 'Incredible' Love With Zooey Deschanel and If They’ll Wed (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Bryant Posts About Kobe, I Miss My Best Friend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Game Says Cops Were Targeting YG for Arrest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hoda Kotb and Jenna Bush Hager's 4th Hour of 'Today' Is Undergoing Some Major Changes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown Agrees to Fight Logan Paul, 'Hopeful' He'll Get Back In NFL #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meek Mill Confirms His Girlfriend Is Pregnant Amid Explosive Nicki Minaj Feud #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adele Continues to Show Off Her Slim Figure in Fitted Workout Wear #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billie Eilish to Perform 'No Time to Die' Title Track #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zsa Zsa Gabor's Husband Says Bernie Madoff Should Rot in Prison #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Cheer' Cast Hot Bods -- Guess Who! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Bryant Makes Instagram Public: Her Sweetest Moments With Kobe and Gigi #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Safaree and Erica Mena Share First Photo of Baby Girl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LeBron James Gives Powerful Speech About Kobe Bryant Before First Game Since Death #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keith Urban -- Good Genes or Good Docs?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tamra Judge Reveals She's Leaving 'Real Housewives of Orange County' After 12 Years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Oz Scoffs at Testicles 'Taste Challenge' on TikTok #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Bachelor in Paradise' Alums Joe Amabile and Kendall Long Call It Quits #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Wahlberg Shares His Favorite Memory With Kobe Bryant (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez &amp; Shakira Rock Miami for Super Bowl Halftime Show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Megan Thee Stallion Sets Record Straight on 2015 Arrest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Van Jones Says Dwyane Wade Was Courageous for Supporting Zaya #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Ruffalo Says He'd Be Honored to be Part of 'Parasite' TV Show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hollywood's Ready for the 92nd Academy Awards, Outfits Run the Gamut #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amanda Bynes Shares Photo With Her 'Lover' Following Engagement #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyoncé and Rihanna Step Out in Style at Roc Nation Brunch -- See Their Fabulous Looks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosmith's Joey Kramer Playing with the Band in Vegas, No Audition Required #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle Will Not Appear on BFF Jessica Mulroney's Netflix Series #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pamela Anderson Looks So in Love in First Photo With Husband Jon Peters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Celebrity Shoe Collections -- From Jennifer Lopez to Rihanna to Selena Gomez #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Hudgens Spotted Having Dinner With NBA Star Kyle Kuzma Following Austin Butler Split #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant and Daughter GiGi Die in Helicopter Crash, Academy Players React #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nipsey Hussle Honored at Grammys by YG, John Legend and DJ Khaled #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louis C.K. Postpones Houston Shows Due to 'Family Emergency' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lakers Giving Away 20,000 Kobe Bryant Shirts at Staples, Players To Wear Patch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get to Know Lady Gaga's New Boyfriend, Michael Polansky #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown Surrendering To Police, Arrives At Jail #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump Gets Standing Ovation At National Championship Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eva Mendes Has the Perfect Response to Troll Who Said She's 'Getting Old' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Bryant Announces MambaOnThree Fund to Help Families Affected By Tragic Helicopter Crash #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Bachelor' Producers Speak Out on Tyler Gwozdz's Death #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria and David Beckham’s Daughter Harper Gets a Hug From Justin Bieber During London Concert #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosmith Drummer Joey Kramer Could Return to Band Soon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cameron Diaz and Benji Madden's Baby Girl's Full Name and Date of Birth Revealed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Swae Lee Wants to Sing National Anthem at Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Robert Pattinson as 'The Batman' Revealed in Quick First Look #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Valentine's Day Dresses for Wherever Your Plans Take You #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato Brings House Down with Super Bowl LIV National Anthem #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside the 2020 Oscars After-Parties: From Celebrity Run-Ins to Lots of PDA! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift's Netflix Documentary Will Show Her Side of the Kanye West, Kim Kardashian Feud #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['You': Ambyr Childers and James Scully Break Down the Best Deaths of Season 2 (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sophie Turner and Joe Jonas Expecting First Child Together #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Space Force Reveals First Uniform and They Might Need a Redesign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SpaceX Launches Crew Dragon Spacecraft to Test for Astronaut Safety #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rihanna Reportedly Splits From Billionaire Boyfriend Hassan Jameel After Nearly 3 Years of Dating #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ryan Guzman Reveals His 1-Year-Old Son Couldn’t Breathe During ‘Nightmare’ Incident #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Love Is Blind': Watch Couples Get Engaged Before They Ever See Each Other on Netflix's New Dating Show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Country Singer Daniel Lee Martin Commits Suicide Amid Child Sex Abuse Arrest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Offset Throws Flying Punch at Strip Club After Cardi B Gets Sprayed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Star Trek: Voyager' Celebrates 25 Years: Kate Mulgrew and Jeri Ryan on the Groundbreaking Series #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[J.J. Watt Marries Kealia Ohai in Beautiful Tropical Ceremony: See the Pics! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[R. Kelly's Ex-GF Azriel Clary Shares Photos Back with Her Family #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YG Arrested After Raid at Home #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Monaghan Jokingly Tells Brad Pitt Not to 'Break Our Hearts Again' After Jennifer Aniston Reunion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blueface Says Tekashi's Bodyguards Are Smart for Passing on the Job #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yo Gotti, Team Roc File Lawsuit on Behalf of Mississippi Prisoners #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nick Cannon Says He Doesn't Believe In Marriage After Mariah Carey Divorce (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gwen Stefani Cancels 'Just a Girl' Vegas Residency Show Due to Illness #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Saturday Night Live' Takes On Democratic Debates With Some Familiar Faces In Political Cold-Open #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hot Guys In Towels -- Guess Who! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dwayne Johnson's Dad, WWE Superstar Rocky 'Soulman' Johnson Dead at 75 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiffany Haddish, Chadwick Boseman and More Celebs Attend NBA All-Star Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rihanna Talks New Fenty Line and 'Antagonizing' Her Fans About Upcoming Album (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shaquille O’Neal Hasn't Eaten or Slept Since Kobe Bryant’s Death: ‘I’m Sick' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway Invokes MLK Jr.'s Name to Blast Trump Impeachment Trial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle and Prince Harry Seen for the First Time Since Royal Exit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blake Lively Says She Works Out With Her Kids Every Morning: 'I Use Them as Weights' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lakers Owner Jeanie Buss Speaks Out On Kobe Bryant, 'Gigi Motivates Me' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NBA Postpones Lakers Game After Kobe Bryant Crash #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj's Brother Sentenced to 25 Years to Life for Child Rape #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
