<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# can i get your contact info?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Follow #HASHTAG# for the largest network of journalists in Ottawa. Algonquin journalism students supplementing Ottawa Citize…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best bus driver on the 95 right now. I feel like I'm on a guided tour. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: "I'm feeling honoured," says #HASHTAG# winner #HASHTAG# Yousafzai #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liberal candidate for Carleton-Mississippi Mills #USER# campaign received a B- overall according to #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YouTube is a new way of creating/consuming media &amp; Ottawa has stars of their own. Check out my piece in #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# open for #USER# to kick off Orientation Week at #USER# #HASHTAG# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT #USER#: #USER# camp saying it's too close to call in #HASHTAG#. Taylor only a slight lead on #USER#  #HASHTAG#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# a couple'a hustlin' fellas came by to talk about their upcoming film and online auditions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: At least one person wounded in shooting at National War Memorial. Centre and East Blocks on Parl. Hill are locked down.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Taylor leading in Bay ward # ATvotes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nervous crowd awaits official declaration of Taylor as winner of Bay ward. He's only 450 votes ahead of Cullen. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Pedaling with Bombay Bicycle Club #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dom looking so dashing in his bowtie for national dog day… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Power outage: what we know so far #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# in November? A great way to end the term. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey! I'm a journalist at Gulf News covering the UK election. Are you voting and have a minute for a quick chat?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# its here! Stop by Algonquin College to see your face in #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# ELECTED: 7. Bay - Mark Taylor #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi, I'm a journalist at Gulf News in Dubai covering the UK election. Have a minute for a chat?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Valentine's Day date with #USER# at CBC today ;)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# all the dog pics please]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# not too late! Inbox me your number.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# found an unopened bag of mini eggs in an old jacket. Its a good day.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Published piece of Trudeau at #USER#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# stopped by #USER#  last week. Here's my coverage of it #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Interview with samanthajlong89 at Algonquin Times #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Senators. The talk of the town. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I did graduate last year, back on the east coast now. Hope all is well with you!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: A belated thanks to #USER# for profiling your new President in your paper! #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# if you're planning on voting or not in the election.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First concert of the semester. #USER# #USER#  #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My two favorite things: interviews and makeup chat with #USER# for the winter issue of #USER#.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks for remembering! Check it! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thin margin between Taylor and Cullen in Bay ward. The room isn't even applauding. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Statement from Premier Paul Davis. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Incumbent Rick Chiarelli has lead in College Ward and Mark Taylor has the lead over Alex Cullen in Bay #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey, I'm a journalist at Gulf News covering the UK elections. Do you have a minute for a chat?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lots of support in the room for #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If only I could spend all the money I've invested into my car on makeup instead.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Gander International Airport #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: You pronounce Newfoundland like "understand", according to my friend who just shot a movie there.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# do I have to wait an hour in the phone queue to swap my SIM card or can I do it online?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks for all your help! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# greeted by cheers at Papa Sam's in Kanata. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prospective journalist me a year ago would never believe I use Sedar on a daily basis.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Algonquin loses application of two campuses in Qatif, Saudi Arabia. President indicates deficit in Jazan may have played a role. #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey,I'm a journalist at Gulf News writing about the upcoming UK election. Are you voting by chance?Have a minute for a quick chat?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bombay Bicycle Club stopped by the #USER# on Oct. 17. Check out my story in the #USER# this Thurs. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# picks up again in Ottawa tomorrow at #USER#. So stoked to be back on the road! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's Algonquin's new president #USER#'s view on the Saudi campuses?Learn more about Cheryl in the upcoming #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some cool Ottawa YouTubers in the new issue of #USER# out now! #USER# #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a reporter working for metroland tonight. Will you be around Time Out Bar &amp; Grill tonight for a few words after?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Are you fashionable enough for Dubai? Here are the most carried handbags in town]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Shoutout &amp; thanks #USER# 4 featuring me in Glue Mag &amp; follow #USER# for being awesome &amp; making it happen☺️ h…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Waiting for #USER# to arrive in Bay ward. #HASHTAG#. He won last year against longtime councilor Alex Cullen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# your piece in the #USER#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just sat down with #USER# new president #USER#. She's looking forward to mingling with the students. #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liberal candidate #USER#  3000 votes behind PC MacLaren.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# okay cool! Inbox me your number.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks for all your help! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carleton-Mississippi Mills Liberal candidate #USER# behind by 700 votes. Riding has been PC for 148 years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: ELECTED: 7. Bay - Mark Taylor #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Johnny Cash’s son arrested in his underwear at Deer Lake airport #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear #USER#. Can you please make a #USER# filter. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm a real journalist meow! Right by the bridge in hfx #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: .#USER# confirms that a transportation referendum is upcoming. #HASHTAG# See my previous U-Pass stories...http…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ive been to Canadian Tire twice this week. Ew.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Such a coincidence, yes! The online content went up today. Hope all is well with you :)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# DM me! I need to ask you a question.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The guy blaring Celine Dion on Duckworth St is my soulmate &lt;3.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[400 votes separate Taylor from Cullen in Bay ward #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Sexual harassment dominates headlines #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This is your first lesson in business class...remember its nothing but fake money. " #USER# #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[108/311 polls predict PC Jack MacLaren the clear winner of #HASHTAG#.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# just complimented me on my shawl. Guess I'm exuding 'homeless chic' today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Listening to Omar Khadr's Canadian lawyer talk #USER# about his treatment in Guantanamo for #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey! I'm a journalism student writing a piece on YouTubers in Ottawa. Would you be free for a chat?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: It's okay to be scared.  We are here for you 613-238-3311 #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor addresses the crowd after a tight race #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patiently waiting on Strangelove to call me for a interview. First question: can you summarize you're book on YouTube in 15 minutes?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liberal candidate leading 33-20 in #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I am a journalist in Ottawa &amp; have a story w sources about Muslim discrimination by RCMP in St.John's interested in details?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hey! I'm a journalist at Gulf News in Dubai covering the UK election. Have a minute for a quick chat?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# thanks for all your help! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Slut shaming needs to stop. My column in the #USER# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I almost never use twitter for work, but since we're launching the latest news media outlet in town ....  #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching the votes come in at Rosalyn Steven's headquarters in Kanata. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just sent my first interview request via Instagram. #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Breakfast meeting; meeting councillors; phone calls; speaking to J class at algonquin; trustees dinner; Candlelight vi…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The cat seems sufficiently out of the bag. Warm welcome to #USER#, the newest addition to #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Positive vibes of a job well done at Liberal candidate #USER# despite PC taking the vote. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dubai's fur industry is feeling the heat in the wake of Russia's recession. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best part of working in the office alone: I can talk to myself and no one tells me to shut up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# are you voting in the UK election?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# cancels 2 more campuses in Saudi Arabia due to rocky first year in Jazan. Read #USER# on Thurs for more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I'm a journalist #USER# writing a piece about popular bags in Dubai. Is there a sales rep/communications dept to talk with?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Excited to welcome #USER# to the growing newsroom at the newly renamed #URL#!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# rough start in #USER# lead to the cancellation of two new campuses in Saudi. Read my story here #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer fun begins in two days. Vacation + moving! #USER# #USER#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
