<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Top Obama WH Lawyer Charged With Lying About Foreign Collusion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giuliani warns Hillary: Days of 'you cannot indict a Clinton' are over #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rudy Exposes Hillary Clinton On Live TV, Puts Her On Notice: ‘Better Get A Lawyer!’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI reveals Comey memos contained highly classified info than previously known - including names #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama Justice Department Was Involved In IRS Targeting, Lerner Emails Reveal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Story Confirms What I’ve Told You About Twitter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Communities Forced to Accept Refugees With Little Say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: FISA Court Says FBI Lied to Them, Illegally Spied]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump and Congress just legalized hemp #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coca-Cola, Ford and Xerox: We No Longer Donate to Planned Parenthood Abortion Business #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big Pharma Exec Perp Walked In Handcuffs After Surrendering On Opioid Trafficking Charges #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Admin to Block Illegal Aliens from Taking Public Housing from Americans #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI Spy Program Used On Trump Has Long History Of Vicious Abuses #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mueller’s conclusions expose disgrace of Obama’s spy chiefs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Comey tweets he has 'so many answers' after release of Mueller report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Immigrants from 50 countries illegally entering US: Border Patrol official #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario Passes Law Allowing Gov't to Seize Children From Parents Who Oppose Gender Transition #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden's senior adviser in 2016: 'We don't need white people leading the Democratic Party right now' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jerome Corsi sues Mueller, Justice, CIA, FBI, NSA for $350 million #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here you go the Muller Report. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Obama White House Counsel Expected to Be Indicted Soon in Case Stemming From Mueller’s Probe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump to Omar: We will never forget what you said about 9/11! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden announces he is running for president in 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Kerry clashes with Rep. Thomas Massie on his college degree, climate change: ‘Are you serious?’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rep. Matt Gaetz taunts Rep. Adam Schiff with PENCIL Act #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Friendly Reminder:  Early Voting Ends Tuesday If you live in the County; please go vote in the School Board Electio… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS: FISA Court says FBI lied to them, illegally spied #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike Huckabee Fires Back at Mitt Romney's Claim That Trump 'Makes Me Sick' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's here! See humanity’s first image of a black hole's event horizon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Appeals court rules Donald Trump can build border wall #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is a FISA warrant? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Flake: It Would Be Better If A Socialist Won In 2020, Instead Of Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sri Lanka: Two Muslims identified as attackers in Easter jihad massacres, death toll now 165 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cher Doubles Down: 'Excuse the Fk Out of Me If I Don’t Want, Murders, Rapists, &amp; CHILD MOLESTERS to Vote' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York Post stirs Ilhan Omar controversy with 9/11 cover #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden endorsed by Michael Avenatti after launching 2020 bid: 'He has my enthusiastic support' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump orders crackdown on 'visa overstays' in latest push against illegal immigration #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[America's Second Civil War Has Already Begun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did Russian Dossier Have to Be ‘Verified’ for FBI to Use It to get a Secret Warrant? - Liberty Headlines #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama Campaign Paid $972,000 To Law Firm That Paid Fusion GPS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Georgetown University students approve new fee to fund reparations for slavery]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Irish Slave Trade – The Forgotten “White” Slaves - Global Research #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Aren't Monuments to Byrd, Wilson Upsetting Democrats? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police: 875 French Catholic Churches Desecrated in 2018 Alone #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dem leadership holding secret Stop Bernie meetings in NY, DC, battle rages for control of party #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[F.B.I. Was Told That Militia in New Mexico Planned to Kill Obama and Clinton #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White House releases snaps of Trump golfing with Rush Limbaugh #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US is the most dangerous place in the developed world to give birth #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TABLES HAVE TURNED: Former Obama Lawyer Indicted In Case Related To Mueller Probe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HEY, FACEBOOK WE KNOW YOUR ARE SHADOW BANNING OUR DEEP EAST TEXAS TEA PARTY PAGE. STOP IT]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Open Easter Day 10: am #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bruce Ohr Revealed Political Operatives Got FBI To Investigate The NRA #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rand Paul Proposes Immunity for Assange in Exchange for Testimony #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UCLA Students Sign Petition to Put Trump Supporters in Concentration Camps #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz Says Trump Team Should Sue Congress For Abuse of Power #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: Those “Russian bots” were really Democrat operatives – The Millennium Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fraud probe into Bernie’s wife could ruin his hopes for 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats Buying Votes With Our Money. Free Medical Free Education Free Citizenship Free Everything Is that despera… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden says his proudest moment of Obama's presidency was 'not one whisper of scandal' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A running list of President Donald Trump’s Executive Orders #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opioid prescription drug deaths dwarf shooting deaths, yet there’s no call to ban Big Pharma #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Argentinian President Claims Former Obama Official Asked The Country To Provide Iran With Nuclear Fuel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Because she was a liar. She was an unethical, dishonest lawyer, she conspired to violate the Constitution, the rul… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATER DAMAGED RV ROOF. THE NUMBER ONE CAUSE OF RV DEATH. Re-Coat needed if you can see any cracking or grey showing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hemp VS Trees: One Billion Reasons To Use Hemp Instead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FISA Court Finds "Serious Fourth Amendment Issue" In Obama's "Widespread" Illegal Searches Of American Citizens #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who really cares what you think . #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Search for 14-year-old Carroll County boy now a 'criminal investigation'; officials have spoken to 'person of inter… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US weekly jobless claims drop to the lowest level since 1969 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RINOs No More? McCains FINALLY Go Full Democrat - Will Support Biden In 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN: 'God Allowed The Mueller Report To Test Our Unshakable Faith In Collusion' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Brennan blasts Trump's 'sociopathic ramblings,' denies participating in a 'coup' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Photos Corroborate Perjury Claims Against Rep. Ilhan Omar, as She Deletes Social Media Evidence #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge CRIES as she leaves court #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wikileaks exposes secret list of 65 mainstream media reporters who are part of the Clinton mafia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Videos appear to show armed militia detaining migrants at US-Mexico border #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter is run by Democratic donors and activists #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Americans Favor Fifteen Dollars an Hour for Congress #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["SOME PEOPLE DID SOMETHING" TO THAT CATHEDRAL IN PARIS]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Comey: 'We Did Not Spy---We Just Observed And Reported Secretly Without The Subject's Knowledge Or Consent' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is America Turning Into a Nation of Dunces? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alabama bill requires schools to conduct Pledge of Allegiance #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this is a link to the released Muller report. The President has been cleared. So now let us get down to the real in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lawyer files to have ex-FBI chief James Comey disbarred after Clinton scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ann Coulter says she’d consider vote for Bernie Sanders #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker: Left struggles to say the word 'Christians' following Easter Sunday attacks in Sri Lanka #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Unplanned' Director Reveals Large Number of Abortion Workers Wanting To Leave Field After Seeing Film #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama 'Put a Target on Their Backs', SEAL Team 6 Family Members Say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brzezinski: 'It’s Infinitely Easier to Kill than Control a Million People' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump says will award Tiger Woods the Presidential Medal of Freedom #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[24-hour Black News Channel set for November debut: ‘By black people for black people’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Obama Holdover Sally Yates Helped Sink Michael Flynn #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House Republicans leave border tour shocked to learn immigrant children being recycled by smugglers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Confirmed: DOJ Used False Info To Secure Wiretaps On Trump Associate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All 11 FISA Court Judges Who Approved Unlawful Spying on Trump Appointed by John Roberts – The Millennium Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AOC suffers social media gaffe by criticizing photo of 'GOP' politician who is actually a Democrat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Commentary: Democrats Must Apologize to America for the Russia Collusion Hoax - Tennessee Star #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EMERGENCY! If Obama Goes Down, The Left Will Riot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Unleash Hell': New Al Qaeda magazine describes in detail how to start huge forest fires across the U.S..with instr… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barr says he thinks the government spied on the Trump campaign #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
