<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Photographs Document Changing Archaeological Sites in Jordan: Photographs Document Changing Archaeol... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  US Braces for Hurricane Matthew: Southern and Eastern states braces themselves for Hurricane Matthew... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Photographic Evidence that the British Royal Family Loves Balloons: At her first public playdate, Princess Ch... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Welcome, Adam Levine, to PEOPLE's Sexiest Man Alive Dads' Club: Join us in initiating the Maroon 5 frontman –... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Well Do You Remember Will &amp; Grace?: Two best friends + kooky neighbors = loads of laughs. See what you re... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American Horror Story: Roanoke's Biggest Horror References: Did you catch off of these nods to horror classic... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos From Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Times the Doctors of Grey's Anatomy Should Have Been (or Stayed) Fired: Their job security is remarkable [... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hugh Grant, Plus David Beckham, Mandy Moore, Justin Bieber and More!: From Hollywood to New York and everywhe... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's Why You Recognize the Stars of This Is Us: Did you know two of them are tied to the Marvel universe? [... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Celebs Who've Opened Up About Their Relationship Regrets: These stars looked back and lamented these ill-fa... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Colorful Days of Autumn: The fall season brings beautiful foliage and crisp weather. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos from Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[January Jones, Plus Britney Spears, Kate Hudson, Anna Kendrick and More!: From Hollywood to New York and ever... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Way They Were: Brad &amp; Angelina's PDA-Filled Moments: Amid shocking news of their impending divorce, we lo... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Shimon Peres: A Life in Pictures: Photos from the life and career of Shimon Peres. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shailene Woodley &amp; Joseph Gordon-Levitt, Plus Kate Winslet, Jamie Dornan, Cara Delevingne &amp; More!: From Holly... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Keira Knightley Stuns on the Red Carpet: This month's hottest celebrity pictures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos from Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rihanna, Plus Jennifer Lawrence, Kate Moss, Jimmy Fallon and More!: From Hollywood to New York and everywhere... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sports, Planes and Wine, Oh My! The 7 Best Photos From Prince William and Princess Kate's Fourth Day in Canad... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  World Mourns Former Israeli President Shimon Peres: The ninth president of Israel died at age 93. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kerry Washington's Most Stunning Red Carpet Maternity Moments: The actress is an absolute queen when it comes... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt's Divorce: The 7 Biggest Revelations: Jolie's decision to file for divorce from ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[25 of the Best Netflix Originals, Ranked: Let the binge-watching begin! [26 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Walking Dead Stars Like You've Never Seen Them: Guess who's real-life sexy. [29 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Most Popular TV Show Set in Each State (and D.C.): According to #URL# users! [52 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Priyanka Chopra, Plus Idina Menzel, Chris Martin, Amber Rose &amp; More!: From Hollywood to New York and everywhe... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Look Back at Brad Pitt &amp; Angelina Jolie's Best Collaborations: From Mr. &amp; Mrs. Smith to their advocacy for ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS: America's Got Talent Winner Grace VanderWaal on Her Childhood – and Plans for the Future: The tiny uk... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Definitive Proof the Cast of Stranger Things Won the Emmys: TV's most adorable new superstars took the show by storm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos from Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Most Badass Women of The Walking Dead, Ranked: Warning: Badass spoilers ahead. [16 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8 Times Hilaria Baldwin Proudly Posted Her Post-Baby Body on Instagram: The yoga instructor and fitness guru ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Go Inside the Pope's Summer Residence: The papal apartment in Castel Gandolfo, the summer residence ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So Long, Canada! How the Royals Spent Their Final 24 Hours Abroad: George and Charlotte wave goodbye to well-... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Duchess Kate, Prince William and Children Visit Canada: Will, Kate and their children travel to Canada. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  PHOTOS: Migrant Family's Journey From Tumult to Tranquility: Migrant family finds peace in Germany. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Beckham, Plus Kristen Stewart, Amal Clooney &amp; Much More!: From Hollywood to New York and everywhere ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Criminal Minds Quiz: Are you an expert when it comes to Criminal Minds? Time to find out. [23 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[George and Charlotte's Cutest Moments in Canada – So Far: They're adorable at home – but in Canada, they may ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Portraits of Nobel Prize Winners: The Nobel Prize in Literature has been awarded annually since 1901. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Hurricane Matthew Makes Landfall: 'Life-threatening' hurricane Matthew could cause landslides, flash... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Best Celeb Quotes This Week: Gigi Hadid on defending herself during a physical altercation in Italy. Plus,... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If You Liked That, Watch This! 7 New Fall TV Shows to Fill the Void Left by Departed Fan Favorites: Replaceme... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  The 2016 World Series in Pictures: The best photos of the Cleveland Indians and Chicago Cubs from th... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gigi Hadid, Plus Anthony Anderson, Amal Clooney, Emily Blunt and Much More!: From Hollywood to New York and e... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Worst Hurricanes in US History: From Audrey to Sandy, hurricanes have cut a wide swath of destruction. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The iHeartRadio Music Festival Was Star-Studded and Sexy: See the Pics!: Everyone from BSB to John Stamos mad... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going Nowhere: All the Stars Who've Been Stuck in Elevators: While Demi Lovato and Joe Jonas's latest stunt t... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[19 Heartbreaking Celebrity Breakups, Ranked: Love. Is. Dead. [20 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos From Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lawrence, Scarlett Johansson and More Stars Who've Opened Up About Their Personal Experiences with P... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actors Who Look Just Like That Other Actor: We can't tell them apart, can you? [31 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17 Times Michael Weatherly Was Our Favorite GoofBull: He may be a Bull in the courtroom, but in real life, Mi... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Photos from Princess Kate and Prince William's Day in the Great Canadian Outdoors: The fifth day of ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos from Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Katie Holmes Embraces Autumn on the Red Carpet: This month's hottest celebrity pictures. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 17 Creepiest Harry Potter Monsters &amp; Villains, Ranked: Giant spiders? No, thank you. [18 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mean Girls Stars: Where Are They Now?: So, is Aaron Samuels still hot? [23 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The West Wing Stars: Where Are They Now?: They've been busy. [27 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Celebrating the End of Fighting in Colombia, FARC Looks to the Future: FARC fighters begin to transf... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Deadliest TV Murderers: See some of the most frightening killers Hollywood has come up with. [26 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Photographer Captures Ancient Trees Under the Night Sky: Photographer Beth Moon captures the link be... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Man Fatally Shot in Charlotte Protests: A civilian shot the man during violent protests over Keith S... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cartoon Twins! 9 Celebs with Animated Look-alikes: See which stars have spot-on animated twins from classic c... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie Through the Years: Angelina Jolie, Brad Pitt #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Best Cosplay From New York Comic Con 2016: Costumed characters and fans attend the annual comic con ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Monday in Canada! Everything Will and Kate Did on Their Third Day Up North: Prince William and Princess Kate ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Legendary Guitarist Chuck Berry Turns 90: Rock and roll musician and writer of the song "Johnny B. G... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jersey Shore Stars: Where Are They Now?: A lot has happened since the GTL days. [19 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Times Hayley Atwell Was Your Style Icon: Both onscreen and off, Hayley Atwell is the epitome of fashion go... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  2016 National Geographic Nature Photographer of the Year Contest Entries: Capturing penguins to flam... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every Photo You Need to See of the Royal Family in Canada This Weekend: Yes, there's plenty of George and Charlotte! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Definitive Ranking of the Hottest Women on Star Trek: Check out these intergalactic hotties. [24 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exclusive Photos: Carrie, Luke, Blake and More Behind the Scenes at "Forever Country": PEOPLE captured portra... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Famine Threatens Yemen Amid Civil War: Famine Threatens Yemen Amid Civil War #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Dancing with the Stars Feuds That Kicked Up Drama on the Dance Floor: Though most friendships created on Da... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Presidential Trick-Or-Treats: Presidential Trick-Or-Treats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Geekiest Big Bang Theory Quiz Ever: Think you know the CBS sitcom? Time to find out. [23 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reboot, Reuse, Recycle: 5 Big-Screen Greats with Major Fall TV Buzz: We get the small-screen appeal of the Ho... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Hurricane Matthew Pounds the Caribbean: Photos of the devastation caused by Hurricane Matthew. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emily Blunt, Plus Jessica Simpson, Emma Watson, Minka Kelly &amp; More!: From Hollywood to New York and everywher... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake &amp; Anna Kendrick, Plus Helen Mirren, Michelle Obama and More!: From Hollywood to New York an... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will &amp; Grace Guest Stars Who Are More Famous Than Will or Grace: You'll never believe who showed up [29 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Definitive Ranking of the Hottest Guys on Star Trek: They're classic, out-of-this-world hot [19 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is What Game of Thrones Stars Really Look Like: Dang, Jon Snow looks _good_. [21 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the Big Brother: Over the Top Cast: Expect the unexpected -- including sisters! [12 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  French Authorities Shut Down Calais Camp: Thousands of migrants who made treacherous journeys to Eur... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  This Week in Pictures: Top Photos from Around the Globe: Find this week's top photos from around the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fall TV Popularity Contest 2016: Which New Shows Won You Over?: Vote for your favorites! [2 photos] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liam Hemsworth, Plus Gina Rodriguez, Mark Wahlberg, Miranda Kerr and More!: From Hollywood to New York and ev... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Violent Protests in Charlotte After Fatal Police Shooting: Police-involved shooting leads to protest... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  NJ Transit Train Crashes Into Hoboken Terminal: Officials are investigating a commuter train crash i... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PHOTOS:  Nikon's 2016 Small World Photography Contest Winners: Nikon's 2016 World Microscopic Photography Con... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead Season 7 Character Portraits: Get a good look, because one of these people won't survive the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All the Cutest Photos from the Royal Fab 4's Farewell to Canada: From Charlotte's tiny wave to George's adora... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Kids on the Block! 5 TV Favorites Joining Returning Fall TV Series: John Stamos, Rob Lowe, Tom Felton and... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Look Back at Naomi Watts and Liev Schreiber's 11-Year-Relationship: The two actors, who announced their spl... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Celeb Couples Whose Relationships Totally Failed (or Prevailed!) on Reality TV: There might be a reality T... #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
