<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Skeleton Makeup Tutorial Halloween 2016: The Prettiest Skeleton Costume How-To: How to get skeleton makeup fo... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taraji P. Henson's *Benjamin Button* Salary Was Less Than 2 Percent of Brad Pitt's: Taraji P. Henson opens up... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my everyday style: all laced up for fall!: Lace up tops, sweaters, shoes... you name it! This fall season is ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What It's Really Like to Raise a Child with Down Syndrome: Model Amanda Booth clears up stereotypes about her... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen Shows You How to Look Sexy During Sweater Season: She stepped out in an off-the-shoulder sweat... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my everyday style: a major announcement!: Did I click bait you with that awesome post title!!?? I had to. Jus... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Melania Trump Has Had Enough of Donald in SNL's Lemonade Parody: She's not sorry. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the Inspiring Girls of the New CNN Documentary 'We Will Rise': Nearly 50 girls from Morocco and Liberia ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Truly Affordable Gifts for Boss's Day: Great gifts for kissing up to the boss in style—they only look expensive. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The Contour Song:" Finally, an Anthem for Everyone Who Sucks at Makeup: The Contour Song is the super catchy... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dianna Agron's $20,000 Valentino Wedding Dress Is Anything But Bridal: The bride didn’t wear white: When Dian... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Defuse Conflicts With Coworkers: You're ticked at a coworker and the last thing on your mind is to for... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Presidential Debate Sparked Some Golden Craigslist Casual Encounter Ads: For the final presidential debat... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amanda Seyfried Opens Up About Her Struggles With Mental Illness: Amanda Seyfried opens up about her struggle... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mermaid Makeup Tutorial Halloween 2016: The Prettiest Mermaid Costume to Try: Mermaid makeup is making a spla... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Beauty Products You Can Get at Forever21: The beauty aisle at Forever21 has cute hair, makeup, skin ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How *Crazy Ex-Girlfriend*'s Rachel Bloom Survived the Worst Depression of Her Life: Rachel Bloom, TV’s Crazy ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[loving + wanting at the Shopbop sale!: The Shopbop sale is going on now and friends, it's pretty epic!  The e... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Melania Trump Says Donald Was "Egged On" By Billy Bush: The hopeful first lady dismissed her husband's "grab ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Wants to Double the Tax Credit for Parents of Young Children. Here's What That Means: The Cli... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Hold Your Handbag Like a Celebrity: Looking for newfangled ways to carry your favorite handbags this s... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why I Left My Multi-Million Dollar Events Business: Paige Chenault had a multimillion-dollar events business,... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dancing With the Stars 2016 Results: Was Pitbull Out of Line for His Comment About Jana Kramer's Outfit?: Amb... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[crazy for camel!: Creamy, gorgeous camel is a go-to fall color for my wardrobe.  Every time I am shopping it ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Olivia Wilde and Jason Sudeikis Had a Baby Girl! See Her First Photo: Olivia Wilde and Jason Sudeikis are pro... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fall 2016 Denim Trends: The Best Jeans for Women: Game-changing styles that knock straightforward skinny jean... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[30 Outfit-Making Fall Bags Under $300: From satin backpacks to minimalist mini bags, there's something for everyone. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Mindy Finn, the 35-Year Old Candidate for Vice President: Finn talks about following Geraldine Ferraro a... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17 Tiny Things You Can Buy on Amazon, Because Tiny Is Always Better: Behold these miniature items that every ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two Women Are Claiming Donald Trump Sexually Assaulted Them: Two women speak out against Donald Trump for sex... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Halloween Website Is Selling a Totally Inappropriate 'Kim Kardashian Robbery' Costume: Halloween retailer c... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Big Bang Theory "The Cohabitation Experimentation" Recap: Sheldon and Amy Move in Together: Sheldon and A... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PSA: You Can See All Eight Harry Potter Movies in IMAX Theaters This Week: All eight Harry Potter movies are ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Signs You’re a Good—Or Bad—Boss: Give your performance a review. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amber Tamblyn: Yes, Misogyny Exists—And It’s The Gift That Keeps On Grabbing: The actress, who recently revea... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Target’s Home Decor Is Getting a Gorgeous Modern Refresh: If you’re partial to modern decor, you’ve probably ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Reappears on Social Media With a Subtle Statement: Kim Kardashian quietly returned to Twitter ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyoncé Performed With a Bleeding Ear at Tidal X: 1015 Because She's Beyoncé: Beyoncé's earring ripped out du... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Supporters Tweet to #HASHTAG# After Realizing Only Men Can Win Him the Election: Donald Trump supp... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my everyday fall style: a blazer for fall!: Nothing says fall style to me more than a blazer.  It's the first... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Fall Hairstyle for You, According to Your Horoscope: If you're in need of some fall hairstyle inspir... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Women Share Why Planned Parenthood Is Vital on Its 100th Birthday: In celebration of Planned Parenthood's 100... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Clever Things You Need to Decorate If You Have a Teeny-Tiny Apartme: Whether it’s furniture with hidden st... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Broke Her Family's Silence on Kim's Robbery: The Kardashians have been keeping to themselves... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Unicorn Halloween Costume Ideas That Are Blowing Up on Pinterest: The best unicorn halloween costume... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Piece of Kim Kardashian's Stolen Jewelry Was Recovered: A passerby found her cross pendant on the sidewalk ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Texting Using Only Proper Grammar for a Week Was the Hardest Thing I've Ever Done: Texting using only proper ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus Talking About Her Pansexuality Is Both Amazing and Important: Miley Cyrus doesn't want you to put... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Smithsonian Needs $300,000 to Save Dorothy's Ruby Slippers: The Smithsonian Institute, which has housed t... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The "Vote for Hillary" Plea Every Sanders Supporter Needs to Hear: Bernie Sanders' deputy campaign manager, R... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Calvin Klein-Inspired T-Shirt Is The Only Political Fashion Statement You Need: The political fashion st... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kendall Jenner Is Accepting Applications From Aspiring Models—In Selfie Form: The reality TV star turned mode... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato Has Long, Blond Hair Now, and She Looks Amazing: New season, new look: Demi Lovato showed off her... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Sweet Reason Why Barack Obama Doesn't Wear His Wedding Ring: Now you won't freak out the next time you se... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Samsung Galaxy Note 7 Has Been Banned From All U.S. Flights: The FAA officially banned the Samsung Galaxy... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter Reclaims Donald Trump's 'Nasty Woman' Debate Comment With Badass Messages of Feminism: The Internet t... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm Embarrassed to Tell Dates That I'm Married But Separated: I am actively dating but it's hard to admit som... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[on my radar: October 2016!: Today I am pulling together a few things from around the web that are on my radar... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pat McGrath’s Metalmorphosis 005 Metallic Makeup Kit Is Everything: Makeup artist Pat McGrath is launching a ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American Horror Story Season 6 Episode 5 Recap: Introducing Evan Peters as Edward Phillip Mott: American Horr... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why I Quit Using the Word Just in My Emails: Shortly after starting my first full-time job, I realized I'd de... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chronically Late People Excuses: Why I'll Never Actually "See Ya In 10": Why are chronically late people alwa... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Have to See the Season One KUWTK Throwback Pic Kylie Posted: 2007 feels like a lifetime ago. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my everyday style: cozy layers!: There is NOTHING better than a cool and gloomy fall weekend where you can bu... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All the Nobel Prizes Went to Men This Year, and People Aren't Happy: Reminder: It's 2016. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Potter Makeup You Can Actually Buy Really Exists!: Harry Potter makeup isn't just a thing out of a fair... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my everyday style: pink + grey!: I'm definitely having a moment with pink this fall.  I love pink any time of... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Cult-Favorite Korean Beauty Products You Can Buy on Amazon: You don't need a plane ticket to get the best ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[George and Amal Clooney's New Condo Has an Insane Number of Windows: The building won't be completed until 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton’s Debate Response About Abortion Is Exactly the One Wo: In an eloquent response, Hillary Clin... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sugar Skull Makeup: An Easy Tutorial for Day of the Dead: How to do Sugar Skull makeup for Dia de los Muertos... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YouTube Star Ingrid Nilsen Explains Why This Election Is So Important and What We Can Learn from We the Voter... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nightclub Mogul Noah Tepperberg and Melissa Wood Had the Wedding of the Year: Hospitality mogul Noah Tepperbe... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wouldn't It Be Nice If Employers Gave Us "Unsick" Days?: One company wants to make sure its employees have ti... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yep, Pumpkin Spice Outfits Are a Thing This Fall: Yep, Pumpkin Spice Outfits Are a Thing This Fall. Pumpkin s... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shailene Woodley Livestreamed Getting Arrested in North Dakota: Actress Shailene Woodley was peacefully prote... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Take a Tour of the U.S. Capitol Through the Eyes of a High School Girl: Girls from Communities in Schools and... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How One Italian Psychologist Is Helping to Protect Refugees: Roberta Laganà never thought she'd work with tra... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blonde Hair Colors: "Soft Roots" Will Help Make Your Roots Less Obvious: Roots are a big problem for women wi... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Cape-Wearing Toddler Is School Picture Day Goals: Three-year-old Kaylieann Steinbach's school picture is... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[25 Political TV Shows and Movies to Watch When You Need a Break From the 2016 Election: From the funny to the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Celebrity Couples Halloween Costumes Ever: These 30 celebrity couples, including Kim Kardashian and ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy Six-Month Birthday, Luna! Here's How Chrissy Teigen and John Legend Marked the Occasion: Chrissy Teigen... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Am I Bleeding?: An OB/GYN explains your erratic periods, blood after sex, and any other unusual bleeding ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's the Real Reason Why You Reuse Passwords (Plus An Easy Way to Kick the Habit): None of our passwords ar... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Navigate Inviting Coworkers to Your Wedding: There's something pretty exciting about heading to work a... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This *Clueless* Plot Mistake Will Drive You Nuts: Did you ever notice this glaring plot hole in the movie Clu... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here’s Your Exclusive First Look at Vera Wang’s New Wedding Dresses for David's Bridal: The new White by Vera... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's What I Think We Should Do About #HASHTAG#: Why #HASHTAG# is such a tough thing to fi... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rihanna and Drake Might Have Broken Up, but Here's Why You Shouldn't Freak Out: Say it ain't so! Rihanna and ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best French Beauty Brands You Can Score on Amazon: The best French beauty brands don't require a plane ti... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Skin Care Secrets Every Model Knows: How do models get such incredible skin? Well, genetics for one. But th... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to Wear to Work This Fall: 5 Power Pairings to Try: Revive your office wardrobe with these easy outfit f... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two Women Tried Weed Tampons to Get Rid of Menstrual Cramps: Can Foria's cannabis suppositories actually ease... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Instagram's New Update Lets You to Help Friends With Eating Disorders or Suicidal Thoughts: The social media ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dating App Culture Is Being Reconsidered, and We're All About It: The culture of swiping on dating apps has l... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Vision of an "Optimal" Board of Directors Is Seriously Sexist: Gender diversity in board membership is n... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Most Feminist Horror Movies of All Time: Not all horror movies are misogynistic garbage. Here are 18 scar... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do People Actually Enjoy Watching Horror Movies?: With Halloween 2016 approaching, I investigate why people l... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shop Paint, Furniture, Rugs and More From Fixer Upper's Joanna Gaines and Magnolia Home Furniture: The HGTV s... #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
