<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Advocates In Conn. Sue ICE, Claiming Agency's Acting-Director Is Serving Illegally #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rush Limbaugh: ‘Mr. Man’ Trump Will ‘Have Fun’ With ‘Gay Guy’ Buttigieg Kissing His Husband #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: Missing Migrant Children Being Funneled Through Christian Adoption Agency - #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Sure you could share quotes from Trump five years ago praising stop-and-frisk to show his hypocrisy OR you could tell Blo…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sacred Site in Arizona Destroyed for Construction of Trump Border Wall #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calls for Michael Bloomberg to drop out of race over leaked audio #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Klobuchar's 3rd Place Finish In New Hampshire 'Shocked The Establishment' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man arrested for trying to pay for prostitute with hamburger #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago Public Schools To Compensate Special Ed Students Illegally Denied Services #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Praises Attorney General Barr For 'Taking Charge' Of Roger Stone Case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,100 Former DOJ Employees Call On Barr To Resign After Intervening In Stone Case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ohio State Football Players Suspended, Charged With Rape and Kidnapping  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[High school basketball game in California ends in ugly, xenophobic taunts #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the Journalist Who Exposed Bloomberg’s Racist Defense of Targeting Black &amp; Brown Youth #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bloomberg digs in -- doesn’t want female former employees freed from NDAs - ABC News - #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PolitiFact - Fake newspaper clip says a teenage Pete Buttigieg killed dogs. He didn’t #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders tops poll for his character, personal values #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Hi. My name is Kathy Griffin. I’ve been on the no fly list, the Interpol list and maybe five eyes. You think I’m scared o…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Ghost' DNA In West Africans Complicates Story Of Human Origins #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had 2 exes try to lure me into post VD hanky panky with pizza &amp; I want to feel insulted by that... But then I look… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: THANK YOU!!!! First member of Congress to speak out. Where are the others? Where is the media? This is Ukraine all over agai…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeffries: Trump budget is a 'declaration of war on the American dream' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beer Waste Saves Montana Town $1 Million On Water Treatment  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roger Stone's Crimes #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Study: White nationalist propaganda distribution on college campuses nearly doubled in 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Molly Crabapple: Bloomberg Is a Billionaire Republican Who Terrorized Black &amp; Brown Youth #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alaska will no longer allow workers with disabilities to be paid less than minimum wage #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Roger Stone lied to Congress and threatened a witness to cover up Trump campaign contacts with Wikileaks.  He was found…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.N. Releases List of 100 Companies Linked to Israeli-Occupied West Bank Settlements #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders lays out his vision for America: finish what Franklin Roosevelt started #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What The Hell Has Final Fantasy VII Remake Done To Carbuncle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I remember when Republicans used to say they were for states' rights. Now the president thinks he can dictate tax policies to…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Conservative Judge Draws a Line in the Sand With the Trump Administration #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump travels to Dover AFB to honor 2 soldiers killed in Afghanistan insider attack #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Conditionally Approves Peace Deal with the Taliban #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Has Now Shifted $1.7 Million From Campaign Donors To His Private Business via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“F**gots Are Maggots” tour cancelled because Pope Francis &amp; Tony Perkins won’t help #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leading Christian website says Pete Buttigieg is “deserving of death” because he’s gay #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Video: Trump's Misleading Post on Pelosi Ripping Up SOTU Address #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House Votes To Revive Equal Rights Amendment, Removing Ratification Deadline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["A true desecration": Sacred Native American site blasted to build Trump border wall #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: “Bloomberg is way richer than Trump” isn’t actually a good reason to support Bloomberg.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Individuals Shouldering 50% Of Tax Burden, Corporations Only 6% #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Halloween is a gateway to drug addiction, claimed ministry backed by Amy Klobuchar #URL# by #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Just Plain Ugly': Proposed Executive Order Takes Aim At Modern Architecture #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did Amy Klobuchar Send an Innocent Teenager to Life in Prison? Questions Mount over Her Record as DA… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Primary voters know Bernie Sanders can beat Trump with his vision for America #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[D.C. Makes It A Crime To Wear Masks. So Why Was A Group Of White Nationalists Able To? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s Tough Benefits Changes Will Make Life Harder for Rural People with Disabilities #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2.5M Pounds Of Radioactive Waste Illegally Dumped In Oregon Landfill #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump just put a 29-year-old fired over allegations of financial crimes in charge of all personnel decisions… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats Accuse Justice Department Of Politicizing Immigration Courts  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Republicans think tampons need to be taxed to limit women from buying too many #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The President says if New York will stop investigating potential crimes he committed he will restore the global entry stat…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: A Massachusetts program has become a model for helping kids return to school after mental health-related absences.    It's run in…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump says 'I won't be changing my mind' on his view that brain injuries suffered by US troops in Iran's attack are… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Traveling teen mistakenly taken down by local police. ACLU has filed a lawsuit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pritzker under federal investigation for property tax scheme #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Mr. President, a couple minor corrections: (1) I have never committed a crime, which is an important pre-req for jail in most co…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gay workers not covered by civil rights law, Trump admin tells Supreme Court #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Corporate Media Is Directly Profiting from Mike Bloomberg’s Rise as He Spends Fortune on TV Ads… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DOJ Asks Court For 'Far Less' Prison Time For Roger Stone After Trump Tweet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Undercover video finds trophy-hunting convention vendors selling captive-bred lion hunts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Detroit Overtaxed Residents by $600M, Causing Foreclosure Crisis. Residents Are Now Fighting Back. #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iowa bill would ban teachers from saying that Pete Buttigieg is gay without notifying parents #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Utah Senate committee unanimously approves bill to decriminalize polygamy  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meme Misquotes Virginia Governor on Abortion Bill #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fact-Checking Trump's Defense for Removing Vindman #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney+ users are confused why movies like ’Home Alone’ are already being removed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conservative proposes adding sexual orientation to marriage licenses &amp; punishing liars #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Right-Wing Doesn’t Want to Talk About Christian Atrocities, So Let’s Talk About Christian Atrocities… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump is sending armed tactical forces to arrest immigrants in sanctuary cities #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man who broke a trans woman’s jaw for using a restroom is getting what he deserves #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poll: Bernie Sanders is beating every other candidate in Nevada #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: “Bloomberg uses foul language and has problems with women and African Americans” said Sarah Sanders while defending a mi…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The #HASHTAG# calls for $800 billion in cuts to Medicare, and $25 Billion in cuts to Social Security.  I worked HARD for…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge Voids UNC's Controversial Settlement Over Confederate Statue 'Silent Sam' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate Approves Legislation To Limit President's War Powers Against Iran #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Six teenage boys broke a gay author’s nose &amp; cheekbone during his walk in the park #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump fired America’s pandemic response team and 6 other ways he ‘sabotaged’ our coronavirus response on Front Page… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indigenous Anti-Pipeline Blockades Cripple Canada’s Rail Transportation #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Grim Reaper" Mitch McConnell admits there are 395 House bills sitting in the Senate: "We're not going to pass thos… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Calls For End To Student Loan Forgiveness Program via #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chuck Schumer Calls for Investigation into Trump’s Retaliation-Motivated Firings #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Despite Corporate Media’s “War on Bernie,” Sanders Rides Wave of Support into New Hampshire Primary… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virginia Legislature Votes To Allow Cities To Remove Confederate Statues #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lest We Forget, This Gay Man Made Donald Trump the Man He Is Today #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi Didn't Raid Social Security for Impeachment Inquiry #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Upper East Side man strangled, mutilated by younger man he met on dating app: cops #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Be mine… FOREVER! The Valentine’s Day Tower is now live, featuring NEW Brutalities for Kano, Jax and Kitana! #HASHTAG# https:…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl Scouts set up cookie booth outside Illinois cannabis dispensary #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: Where Parents Have More Choice, Schools Appear To Become More Segregated #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virginia Democrats walk out as GOP-invited pastor denigrates gay people on House floor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Study: 1 In 5 Patients Gets A Surprise Medical Bill After Surgery #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump supporters' kids are donating to Bernie Sanders' campaign and their parents are not happy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump says he may stop allowing aides to listen to foreign leader calls following infamous Ukraine call #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thousands Of Fetal Remains, Found After Abortion Provider's Death, Buried In Indiana #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump claims 40-50,000 people attended New Hampshire rally, held at venue with maximum capacity of just under 12,000 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The president of the United States today accused Bob Mueller, a former FBI director and prosecutor, of a felony by asser…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos Wants Larger Class Sizes and Fewer Teachers #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
