<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Game of Thrones’: The Night King Speaks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Book Review: ‘Martin Buber: A Life of Faith and Dissent’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Clara’ Review: Love Means Never Having to Say You’re Starry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quentin Fiore, Who Made the Medium His Message, Dies at 99 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Is All Too Real. But to Better Understand It, Turn to Fiction. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marilyn Stasio Gets Cozy With Some Unlikely Heroines — and a Hit Man #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[20 Art Exhibitions to View in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Decade of Fire’ Review: A Documentary Remembers the Blazes That Scorched the Bronx #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: ‘Paul Swan Is Dead and Gone,’ but First, He’s Dévastaté #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Prayer at the Heart of a ‘Quintessentially French’ Opera #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With Woodstock 50 in Peril, Michael Lang Is Defiant: ‘We’re Not Stopping Now’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘The Intruder’ Review: Dennis Quaid as a Homeowner’s Nightmare #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘El Chicano’ Review: Freeing East Los Angeles With Bloodshed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teenage Filmmaker Wins Top Prize at the Tribeca Film Festival #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miller Theater Unveils Its 20th Composer Portraits Series #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Broadway’s  Bawdy Bloodbath: ‘Gary: A Sequel to Titus Andronicus’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New in Paperback: ‘There There,’ ‘Motherhood’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Choreographer Pam Tanowitz’s Dance Card Is Overflowing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Plays and Musicals to Go to in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘A Fortunate Man’ Review: A Danish Engineer Strives for Success #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Court Rules Spanish Museum Can Keep a Painting Seen as Nazi Loot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: Two Lives and Two Playwrights ‘Entangled’ by Gunfire #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nick Hornby on Marriage: For Better, for Worse, for 10 Minutes at a Time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two Novels About Young Soviet Transplants in America #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Years Later, PEN World Voices Festival Is Still Trying to Unify the World #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Being Young, Gay and Addicted in the 1970s #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Les Murray, the ‘Bush Bard’ of Australia, Is Dead at 80 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Is Ruth Asawa, the Artist in Today’s Google Doodle? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In ‘The Second Mountain,’ David Brooks Chronicles His Journey Toward Faith #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 Pop, Rock and Jazz Concerts to Check Out in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Books to Watch for in May #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Hesburgh’ Review: A Portrait of a Heroic and Scandal-Free Catholic Priest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Long Shot’ Review: Charlize Theron and Seth Rogen Give Good Heart #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Dawoud Bey Met David Hammons #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney and Universal Shore Up Their Benches #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tefaf Brings Masterpieces (and Tulips) to the Armory #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stephen Colbert Is Not a Fan of the Attorney General #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Movies and TV Shows New on Netflix Canada in May #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With Sculpture, Frieze Expands to Manhattan #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: In ‘Dead to Me’ on Netflix, Widows Make the Best BFFs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Phil Solomon, Leading Experimental Filmmaker, Is Dead at 65 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Scrabble Words Get the ‘OK’ (Now Worth 6 Points) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘The Convent’ Review: Twisted Sisters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Call Me a Science Fiction Writer. I’ll Come to Your House and Nail Your Pet’s Head to a Coffee Table.’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rapper Wins Fans With a Snarling Critique of Brexit Britain #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Short Books for Kids That Make a Big Impact #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Game of Thrones’: Carice van Houten on Melisandre’s Final Act #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer in the City is back #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BRIC Celebrate Brooklyn! Festival Announces Summer Lineup #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Move Over, Richard Prince. Here Comes Bootleg Art From ‘Christy’s’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Forget ‘Game of Thrones.’ No One Does Violence Like Euripides. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Step Up’ Is One of Pop Culture’s Most Enduring Franchises. How Did That Happen? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Ask Dr. Ruth’ Review: Out of the Bedroom and into the Light #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Classical Music Concerts to See in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last Chance: ‘Atlantis’ at Virginia Rep Through May 5 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Meeting Gorbachev’ Review: Sitting Down With the Last Soviet Leader #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Clay Tablets to Smartphones: 5,000 Years of Writing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At Frieze New York, Islands of Daring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Move a Masterpiece? If It’s This Big, Very Carefully #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She Entered the U.S. Illegally as a Child. She Was Stabbed Nearly to Death After Being Deported. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Collect Like an Artist Does. Hint: Use Instagram #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Protest Dance of Everyday Moves and Volunteer Nudes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Same Pictures. Same Places. 68 Years Apart. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[Theme of the Month] Dramas and food #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 Film Series to Catch in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stewart O’Nan Returns to the Fictional Maxwell Family #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tarantino’s ‘Once Upon a Time in Hollywood’ Is Confirmed for Cannes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Revisiting a British Artist Whose Vision Was Shaped by War #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can an Art Collective Become the Disney of the Experience Economy? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 New Books We Recommend This Week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Non-Fiction’ Review: Sex Comedy Disguised as Tech Treatise, or Vice Versa? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alex Trebek Discusses Cancer and Depression in ABC Interview #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Much Watching Time Do You Have This Weekend? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘UglyDolls’ Review: Stay Ugly, Friends #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everybody Focus, Please: ‘Mrs. Murray’s Menagerie’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kill It: Series Review, Episodes 7-12 (Final) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 Comedy Shows to Catch in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Repercussions From a Political Murder Play Out in a Spanish Village #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What’s on TV Thursday: ‘Someone Great’ and ‘Aliens’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want to Check Out Frieze? All You Need Is an App and a Headset #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woody Allen Pitched a Memoir. Publishers Weren’t Interested. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyeri, Kim Sang-kyung in new tvN comedy Miss Lee #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: ‘Tuca &amp; Bertie’ Is an Eggsellent Adventure #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Fellow Citizens: Episodes 17-18 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turner Prize Shortlist Promotes Political Artists #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[By the Book: Ruth Reichl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[50 Years On, the Art Ensemble of Chicago Is Still Transforming #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Dance Performances to See in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cynthia Ozick Reviews Julie Orringer’s ‘The Flight Portfolio’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Extremely Wicked, Shockingly Evil and Vile’ Review: Killing Me Softly #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How a Canadian Chain Is Reinventing Book Selling #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Novel That’s Equals Parts Murder Mystery, Courtroom Drama and Immigration Tale #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch ‘Boyz N the Hood’ for Free at the Tribeca Film Festival #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Shadow’ Review: A Bleak World Splashed With Red #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In ‘The Paris Diversion,’ a Spy Stumbles in a Belated Sequel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love, Sex and Robots Collide in a New Ian McEwan Novel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vampire Weekend Wraps Breakdowns in Musical Smiles on ‘Father of the Bride’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patti Harrison Bucks Transgender Stereotypes, One Joke at a Time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8 Things to Do With Your Kids in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Frieze New York Addresses the Heat and Expands the Kitchen #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
