<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Voting App Flaws Could Have Let Hackers Manipulate Results #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: BART’s weekend, night ridership figures drop by 10 million #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Tower Warmers (2020): Zadro and Haven #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mobile World Congress Is Canceled Over Coronavirus Fears #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Man declared incompetent in SF pier killing case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Wild video shows transformer fire that took out power in San Francisco #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Duuuuude. What Happens If the Earth Gains Consciousness? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Warriors’ Klay Thompson, Draymond Green attend Vanity Fair Oscars after-party #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: ‘We dated for a brief time’: Breed details relationship with Nuru #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Proposes a Cut in Research Spending, but a Boost for AI #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA’s Epic Gamble to Get Martian Dirt Back to Earth #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Why Bay Area temperatures are warmer than forecast this morning #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kesha, Lil Wayne, and Albums That Don’t Need a Viral Hit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shakeups at the Justice Department Top This Week’s Internet News Roundup #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conservative News Sites Track You Lots More Than Left-Leaning Ones #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Adam Sandler delivers Independent Spirit Awards speech as Billy Madison #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Levy Plus Review: A Comfy, Affordable Electric Scooter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[19 Valentine’s Day Deals to Gift Your Sweetheart (or Yourself) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The DOJ Asks Startup Investors: Are Tech Giants Too Powerful? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Report: At least 3 pedestrians struck by vehicle in SF’s Mission #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: SF Public Works director in bribery case resigns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: New case of novel coronavirus identified in California, bringing state total to 7 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Best Sound Machines for 2020 (Best White Noise Machines) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There Were 646,152 Things to Watch on TV Last Year #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Post-Oscars parties: Catch the celebs after the show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pokémon Home Is Reuniting Joyful Fans With Long-Lost Squirtles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sony Envisions an AI-Fueled World, From Kitchen Bots to Games #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S20, S20+, S20 Ultra Hands On: New Cameras, 8K, and 5G #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flipboard TV: Price, Details, Release Date #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Ways for Big Tech to Protect Teens From Harm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Activision Blizzard Pulled Its Games From Nvidia’s Streaming Service #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can a Database of Animal Viruses Help Predict the Next Pandemic? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Trump to transfer $3.8B from military to fund his wall #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vexed by Missed Deliveries? Data-Savvy Tech Can Help #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Ridge blocking rain from California can be seen from space #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S20, S20+, S20 Ultra: Price, Specs, Release Date #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The ‘Robo Revenge’ App Makes It Easy to Sue Robocallers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 500 Chrome Extensions Secretly Uploaded Private Data #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Darpa Cranks Up Antibody Research to Stall Coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Augmented Reality From the Driver’s Seat, and More Car News This Week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Airbnb Has Devoured London. Here’s the Data to Prove It #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Social Network Becomes a Social Science Subject #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Utopia Falls’ Is a Bold Attempt to Make a Better YA Dystopia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You May Not Even Know You’re Spreading Lies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Airbus’ Blended Wing Maveric Hits the Skies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Marsupial Dies After Marathon Mating. Now It’s Got Bigger Worries #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Doctors on Earth Treated a Blood Clot on the ISS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coway Bidetmega 400 Review: A Glorious Way to Clean Your Derrière #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Are We Polarized? Don’t Blame Social Media, Says Ezra Klein #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft’s Financials Reveal Two Ride-Hailing Strategies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Can’t Take This Photo: The Colossal Underbelly of an Iceberg #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Big (Yet Hidden) Consequences of Antarctica’s Record Heat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Barr: Trump tweets make it ‘impossible for me to do my job’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Psychedelic Fiber Offers a New Twist on the Science of Knots  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Luke Perry left out of Oscar’s ‘In Memoriam’ tribute #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China Launches a Crush of Clinical Trials Aimed at Covid-19 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With In-Car AR, Drivers Get a New View of the Road Ahead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Spectacle of Samsung’s Launch Event #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bloomberg’s Influencer Campaign, a Hackable Voting App, and More News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Influencer Election Is Here #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To Bolster Cybersecurity, the US Should Look to Estonia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Signal Is Finally Bringing Its Secure Messaging to the Masses #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How a Space Engineer Justine Haupt Made Her Own Rotary Cell Phone #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chrome Is Fixing the Web’s Most Annoying Video Problem #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Christina Koch and Jessica Weir: The Stellar Women of the ISS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Insta360 One R Review: A Smarter, Modular Action Camera #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want Unlimited Clean Energy? Just Drill the World’s Hottest Well #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cults Are Scarier Without Magic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Social Network Wants to Pay You (in Crypto) to Do Good #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Going the Distance (and Beyond) to Catch Marathon Cheaters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The US Hits Huawei With New Charges of Trade Secret Theft #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Baby Talk’ Can Help Kids Learn Language (Oh *Yes* It *Can*\!) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: PG&amp;E, 7 others subpoenaed in widening San Francisco public corruption probe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[26 Best Nintendo Switch Accessories (2020): Docks, Cases, and More #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Butler returns to lead Heat past Warriors, 113-101 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cricut Joy Review: An Easy Way to Start Crafting #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hurling Satellites Into Space Seems Crazy—but Might Just Work #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China’s Hacking Spree Will Have a Decades-Long Fallout #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: Report: Larry Ellison hosting Donald Trump at California estate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Z Flip Hands On: A Folding Phone With a Glass Screen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscars Woes for Netflix, Money for Yahoo Users, and More News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Geoff Keighley Says Sayonara to E3 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SFGATE: ‘I’m going to flagrant foul him’: Draymond and Iggy reunite #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge Rules That T-Mobile Can Acquire Sprint #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Food We’ll Eat on the Journey to Mars (Algae Caviar, Anyone?) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix Had a Disappointing Night at the Oscars #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Motorola Razr Review: A Cheap Phone in an Expensive Body #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google’s Giving Out Security Keys to Help Protect Campaigns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Best Xbox One Games (2020): ‘Halo’, ‘Control’, and More #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Samsung Phones, Record Heat in Antarctica, and More News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA Puts a Price on a 2024 Moon Landing  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Polaroid Lab Review: Turn Your Smartphone Snaps Into Polaroid Prints #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why the FTC Wants to Revisit Hundreds of Deals by Big Tech #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Enable Dark Mode on All Your Apps and Devices #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus Has a Name: The Deadly Disease Is Covid-19 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 747 Set a New Record for Crossing the Atlantic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How 4 Chinese Hackers Allegedly Took Down Equifax #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The US Fears Huawei Because It Knows How Tempting Backdoors Are #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can the Government Buy Its Way Around the Fourth Amendment? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zuck’s Lost Notebook, Marsupial Trouble, and More News #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
