<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump says Pakistan ‘harbors terrorists.’ The real story isn’t so simple. – Washington Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Attacks Obama, Quotes Mother Theresa In Whiplash-Inducing Tweet Storm – Deadline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top 10 Kids &amp; Family Playstation 4 Collection // Video Games 2017 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton to appear at Riverside Theater Nov. 9 to talk about new book – Milwaukee Journal Sentinel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Donald Trump Scandal Ended Kathy Griffin and Anderson Cooper’s Friendship – Vanity Fair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[iphone 8 trailer official apple 2017! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why ‘Pokemon Go’ Is Taking Over the World NBC Nightly News – NBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump to lift military gear ban for local police – CNN International #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brian Montgomery    Fox Business News 8 28 2017 Cavuto #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Caught on Hot Mic Trash-Talking Obama? – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Minecraft: PlayStation®4 Edition ep 2 con mio cugino #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nandyal By Elections Results 2017 Live]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz On Catastrophic Flooding In Texas: ‘I’ve Never Seen Anything Like It’ – TPM #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[German Nurse Suspected Of Murdering At Least 86 Patients In His Care – NPR #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Strike against Donald Trump in different cities of Pakistan #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking News 28 August 2017 General Qamar Javed DABANG ACTION on Donald Trump WARNING, Must Watch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In all-hands-on-deck response to Harvey, lessons learned from earlier storms – Christian Science Monitor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lateste News Hillary Clinton On Fox News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If Hillary Clinton starts preaching, would her congregation be bipartisan? – News &amp; Observer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One minute World News BBC 28-8-2017 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s time for conservatives who were wishy-washy about Donald Trump to officially pull the plug – The Daily… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump’s Approval Rating Just Hit Another All-Time Low (Again) – TIME #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China power producer Guodian to merge with Shenhua Coal: government – Reuters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton will go to Wisconsin, this time – Los Angeles Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grandfather Of Teen Killed By Homeowner In Armed Burglary Says Ar-15 Made For Unfair F #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey cancellations now above 5000, extend into Tuesday – USA TODAY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New iPhone 8 Coming Out September 12, Reports Say – Gadget Hacks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mbappe joins up with france, alongside £74m liverpool target lemar [US NEWS] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why the next iPhone’s facial-recognition feature could be a privacy disaster – Mashable #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[ World News ] Breaking News LIVE : Hurricane Harvey: Storm makes landfall in TexasMORE DANGER USA #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flower and vegitable Business rush in Onam Market]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump on Harvey destruction: ‘We are one American family’ – CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon Apple Fest Offers iPhone 7, MacBook Pro &amp; More With Cashbacks and Discounts – NDTV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While Houston Is Under Water, People Start Looting #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Breaking News Storm Harvey: Coast Guard urges people not to tweet for help 28/08/17 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tech News #HASHTAG# Nokia 8 Specifications,JioPhone Suspension,WhatsApp Business]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New iPhones might be able to recognize your face – USA TODAY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Madden NFL 18 PlayStation 4 Review: Storming The Field – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YS Jaganmohan Reddy about Winning and Losing in Elections || Power Punch || NTV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bhuma Brahmanda Reddy Face to Face || Wins in Nandyal By-Elections || NTV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump signed ‘letter of intent’ for Russian tower during campaign, lawyer says – ABC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6th Iowa Democrat joins race for US House seat held by Young – San Francisco Chronicle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump Holds News Conference With President Sauli Niinistö]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Houston Stations Run Out of Gas During Hurricane Harvey – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Breaking News MTV VMAs: Kendrick Lamar dominates as awards show gets … 28/08/17 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Kenya, Selling or Importing Plastic Bags Will Cost You $19000 — or Jail – New York Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cavaliers nix $140M plan to renovate Quicken Loans Arena – Sporting News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Houston’s police chief patrols Harvey-flooded streets for those in need – New York Daily News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Minecraft: PlayStation®4 Edition Monster Jam track 2 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Breaking News MTV VMAs: Highlights 28/08/17 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iraq: Car bombing at busy Baghdad market kills 10 people – ABC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YS Jagan on Nandyal Election Result #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton to sign books at Larkin Square – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal manager arsene wenger slams 4-0 defeat by liverpool [US NEWS] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber’s New CEO Inherits an Identity Crisis – Bloomberg #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keyboard Sports – Videoanteprima gamescom 2017 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Raheem sterling’s dismissal was a killjoy act [US NEWS] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Hillary Clinton exposed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Planet of the Eyes coming to Xbox One and PlayStation 4 next month – TheXboxHub (blog) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Engaged in Harvey Response – U.S. News &amp; World Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey may force 30000 people into shelters while flooding will linger, officials warn – Washington Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hurricane Harvey Update on WORLD NEWS NOW live hit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton to hit the Schnitz this winter – Philadelphia Business Journal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The iPhone 8 Is (Probably) Coming September 12 – New York Magazine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Breaking News MTV VMAs: Highlights 28/08/17 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Browns’ DeShone Kizer: Involvement in preseason finale to be determined – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 thoughts on the Bears’ 19-7 preseason win over Titans – Chicago Tribune #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suit blaming iPhone for student’s death by texting driver is defeated by Apple – Ars Technica #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Business Aamir Liaquat Has Started In Dubai After Leaving Bol News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s Attack on the Rule of Law – U.S. News &amp; World Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Business News Wales Meets Simon Powell #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trolling as Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton in roblox! (funny reactions!) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top 10 Playstation 3 Games Collection // Video Games 2017 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple iPhone may still come at a discount on e-commerce sites – Economic Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Astros-Rangers series could move out of Texas due to flooding, reports say – Sporting News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Hillary Clinton Launches 15 City Live Tour – $1200 Per Ticket! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scorecard: Mayweather tactfully bests McGregor in weekend’s biggest fight – ESPN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix Comedy Special Trailer [HD] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Was Just CAUGHT in HUGE $117 Million FRAUD Scandal 960×540 2 14Mbps 2017 08 28 21 46 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All set for Kakinada Municipal Corporation elections Polling #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leaked iPhone 8 pictures, information suggest it will be priced at $999 – The Express Tribune #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Donald Trump Right About NAFTA? – Forbes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: Sheriff Joe Arpaio Announces Shock Reason Trump Pardoned Him #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[KR Hot News-Trump’s business sought deal on a trump tower in moscow while he ran… #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Stevens explains the Isaiah Thomas trade to Celtics fan (VIDEO) – Yahoo Sports #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift at the MTV VMAs: Through the Years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS TRUMP 8/28/17: America’s Newsroom – Fox News Today August 28, 2017 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal midfielder aaron ramsey apologises to fans for anfield rout [US NEWS] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arjun Reddy mania in Theaters – Show Time – TV9 Entertainment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Xerox Corporation (NYSE:XRX) Sees Unusual Trading Volume in Its Shares – Highlight Press #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sony’s dropping the price of PlayStation VR – Polygon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the Galaxy Note 8 means for the iPhone 8 – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PlayStation VR gets a price cut — and then there were three – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom Brady says trust he had with Julian Edelman hardest to replace – ESPN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Lorde Danced Away With the 2017 Video Music Awards – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ajax resign siem de jong in £4m deal from newcastle [US NEWS] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Hellboy’ Reboot Will Try to Cast An Asian Actor as Ben Daimio – #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple reportedly holding iPhone event on September 12th – The Verge #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NEWS24 বিজনেস at 11pm Business News on 28th August, 2017 on News24 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mayor de Blasio signs bill to hike cigarette pack price to $13 minimum, reduce smoking – New York Daily News #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
