<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Things You Didn’t Know About Vladimir Putin  Listed here are 10 unknown details about one of the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McLaren and OnePlus kick off exclusive partnership with McLaren OnePlus 6T The McLaren OnePlus 6T has simply been m… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hacking microcontroller firmware through a USB  In this article, I want to demonstrate extracting the firmware from… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Plurox: Modular backdoor  In February this year, a curious backdoor passed across our virtual desk. The analysis sh… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Malicious Cyber Activity Surges Coincide With Geopolitical Events Protect yourself! Visit #URL# t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj is Already Discussing Marriage &amp; Kids with New Boyfriend  Nicki Minaj Talkin’ Marriage ceremony Bells &amp;… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google still has no answers for YouTube’s biggest problem  From Pizzagate to QAnon, YouTube has a critical problem… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The top 10 bars in Bloorcourt and Bloordale   Bars in Bloorcourt and Bloordale make for a merry crawl alongside an… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I know what you did last summer, MuddyWater blending in the crowd  Introduction MuddyWater is an APT with a focus o… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Not-so-dear subscribers  Many people have had a run-in with subscriptions to mobile content providers. They appear… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NBA scores, highlights: Raptors blow out Clippers without Kawhi Leonard; Rockets end three-game losing streak   Wel… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FIN7.5: the infamous cybercrime rig “FIN7” continues its activities  On August 1, 2018, the US Department of Justic… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Game of Threats  Introduction While the way we consume TV content is rapidly changing, the content itself remains i… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Threat Landscape for Industrial Automation Systems in H2 2018  H2 2018 in figures All statistical data used in this… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dolphins OL Ted Larsen Says Kenyan Drake Made Great Play, But He Wanted To Score!!   Dolphins Lineman Ted Larsen Ke… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spam and phishing in 2018  Numbers of the year  The share of spam in mail traffic was 52.48%, which is 4.15 p.p. le… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New zero-day vulnerability CVE-2019-0859 in win32k.sys  In March 2019, our automatic Exploit Prevention (EP) system… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ATM robber WinPot: a slot machine instead of cutlets  Automation of all kinds is there to help people with their ro… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New FinSpy iOS and Android implants revealed ITW  FinSpy is spyware made by the German company Gamma Group. Through… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[APT trends report Q1 2019   For just under two years, the Global Research and Analysis Team (GReAT) at Kaspersky La… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sucks to be a polar bear Sucks to be a polar bear   #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Criminals, ATMs and a cup of coffee  In spring 2019, we discovered a new ATM malware sample written in Java that wa… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Attack and Defend a Prosthetic Arm  The IoT world has long since grown beyond the now-ubiquitous smartwatche… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Study highlights ‘uncomfortable truth’ about racism in the job market  Racialized employees in Ontario are consider… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lakers outlast Heat in final LeBron vs. Wade duel; Wade misses game-tying 3-pointer   LeBron James’ squad outlasted… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remotely controlled EV home chargers – the threats and vulnerabilities  We are now seeing signs of a possible shift… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zero-day in Windows Kernel Transaction Manager (CVE-2018-8611)  Executive summary In October 2018, our AEP (Automat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bots and botnets in 2018  Due to the wide media coverage of incidents involving Mirai and other specialized botnets… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AVIToolbox 2.8  Make frequent video recordsdata operations, resembling video splitting, audio extraction, image cap… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fourth horseman: CVE-2019-0797 vulnerability   The new zero-day in the Windows OS exploited in targeted attacks… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fill me up – Block Fitting Puz  Fill the grid with the oddly formed puzzle items supplied. Appears straightforward… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Operation ShadowHammer: a high-profile supply chain attack  In late March 2019, we briefly highlighted our research… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Magnet Driver Space Rocket magnetic screwdriver hits Kickstarter  Makers, hobbyists and engineers out there for a m… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zero-day in Windows Kernel Transaction Manager (CVE-2018-8611)  Executive summary In October 2018, our AEP (Automat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Razy in search of cryptocurrency  Last year, we discovered malware that installs a malicious browser extension on i… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pirate matryoshka  The use of torrent trackers to spread malware is a well-known practice; cybercriminals disguise… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Thrift Store Finds That Made People Rich  These are the 10 luckiest thrift retailer and storage pr… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Twas the night before  Recently, the United States Cyber Command (USCYBERCOM Malware Alert #USER#) highl… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Project TajMahal – a sophisticated new APT framework   By AMR on April 10, 2019. 3:10 am  Executive summary ‘TajMah… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sodin ransomware exploits Windows vulnerability and processor architecture  When Sodin (also known as Sodinokibi an… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GreyEnergy’s overlap with Zebrocy  In October 2018, ESET published a report describing a set of activity they calle… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook building evacuated after reported bomb threat  A building on Facebook’s Menlo Park campus, which homes eac… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gaza Cybergang Group1, operation SneakyPastes  Gaza Cybergang(s) is a politically motivated Arabic-language cyberth… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 holiday gift ideas for the stylish guy in Toronto  Holiday items for the stylish guy in Toronto will hold a pers… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[APT review of the year  What were the most interesting developments in terms of APT activity throughout the year an… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chafer used Remexi malware to spy on Iran-based foreign diplomatic entities  Executive Summary Throughout the autum… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Riltok mobile Trojan: A banker with global reach  Riltok is one of numerous families of mobile banking Trojans with… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MLB winter meetings rumors, updates: Red Sox unlikely to bring back Kimbrel; Astros interested in Brantley  Welcome… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Digital Doppelgangers  Carding exists for over 20 years. And it is not dead yet. It is alive, and even more – it is… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Subtraction Flashcard Match Games for Kids in Kindergarten, 1st and 2nd Grade  Constructing math expertise and stud… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency businesses still being targeted by Lazarus  It’s hardly news to anyone who follows cyberthreat intel… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Large-scale SIM swap fraud  Introduction SIM swap fraud is a type of account takeover fraud that generally targets… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Platinum is back  In June 2018, we came across an unusual set of samples spreading throughout South and Southeast A… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The return of the BOM   Because sometimes you can’t teach an old malware developer new tricks  By GReAT on March 28… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DDoS Attacks in Q4 2018   News overview In Q4 2018, security researchers detected a number of new botnets, which in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Most Expensive Homes of NFL Players  Listed here are 10 of probably the most luxurious and costly prope… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beware of stalkerware  Spyware might sound like a concept from a Hollywood movie, yet commercial versions of such p… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AZORult++: Rewriting history  The AZORult Trojan is one of the most commonly bought and sold stealers in Russian fo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apology to AO Kaspersky Lab  In the past we here at Cyber Pros Consulting where posting articles that we found on t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New human rights report finds extreme racial bias in Toronto policing  A surprising new report from the Ontario Hum… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lawsuit Accuses Trudeau of Selling Out Millennials on Climate Change  Catherine Gauthier acquired sick of listening… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zebrocy’s Multilanguage Malware Salad  Zebrocy is Russian speaking APT that presents a strange set of stripes. To k… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remotely controlled EV home chargers – the threats and vulnerabilities  We are now seeing signs of a possible shift… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yorkdale Mall now has a gender inclusive washroom Rejoice, lovers of inclusiveness and progress. Yorkdale Mall is n… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Things You Didn’t Know About Elon Musk  Listed below are 10 little recognized details about one of ma… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ViceLeaker Operation: mobile espionage targeting Middle East  In May 2018, we discovered a campaign targeting dozen… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Things JUUL Doesn’t Want You To Know  Listed here are 10 unsettling info about the preferred vape, JUUL… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Things You Didn’t Know About Elon Musk  Listed below are 10 little recognized details about one of ma… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Packers player has a theory on why Green Bay has been so bad this year   After spending the primary three se… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LocateMe  The one app that DOES NOT want web to report correct location of, simply ship SMS out of your cellular “T… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WebSite X5 Professional 17  On daily basis we provide FREE licensed software program you’d have to purchase in any… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DDoS attacks in Q1 2019   News overview The start of the year saw the appearance of various new tools in the arsena… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The world’s southernmost security conference  When asked about his best race, Ayrton Senna replied that it was when… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roaming Mantis, part IV  One year has passed since we published the first blogpost about the Roaming Mantis campaig… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BasBanke: Trend-setting Brazilian banking Trojan   By GReAT on April 4, 2019. 11:00 am  BasBanke is a new Android m… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what Toronto’s future transit map could look like Toronto has extra residents, guests and day by day commut… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Cyber Attack in Saudi Arabia Had a Deadly Goal – Experts Fear Another Try Protect yourself! Visit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Financial Cyberthreats in 2018  Introduction and Key Findings The world of finance has been a great source of incom… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What kids get up to online  Today’s children navigate the Internet better than adults. They are not afraid to try o… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 2019 DBIR Is Out  Once again, we are happy to support a large, voluntary, collaborative effort like the 2019 Da… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Moving Meditations  Moving Meditationsfor Households with Autism – Take a break from stress and anxiousness. Comply… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cyber threat landscape growing, potential for emergence of destruction of service attacks: Cisco Found this article… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IT threat evolution Q1 2019. Statistics  These statistics are based on detection verdicts of Kaspersky Lab products… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hearst councillor Gaetan Baillargeon says province changing rules on pledging allegiance to the Crown  A newly elec… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*EXPIRED* Spelling Star  Spelling Star is the proper app for practising your spelling lists. Create lists by gettin… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Operation ShadowHammer  Earlier today, Motherboard published a story by Kim Zetter on Operation ShadowHammer, a new… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Zebrocy Go Downloader  Last year at SAS2018 in Cancun, Mexico, “Masha and these Bears” included discussion of a s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mobile malware evolution 2018   The statistical data for this report came from all Kaspersky Lab mobile security so… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj’s New Boyfriend is a Rekindled Ex-Flame  Nicki Minaj Troubled New BF is Blast From Her Romantic Previou… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama is coming to Toronto on her book tour  Many in Toronto love the Obama household, from their iconic c… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Offset Wants Cardi B Back, But Thinks Haters Will Ruin His Chances  Offset  I Need Cardi Again … Haters Are Messing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Threats to users of adult websites in 2018  Introduction 2018 was a year that saw campaigns to decrease online porn… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Should Not Get Immunity in Return for Resignation, Congressman Says   U.S. Rep. Adriano Espaillat  No… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A predatory tale: Who’s afraid of the thief?  In mid-February, Kaspersky Lab received a request for incident respon… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything we know about gender violence in one new website  A newly launched authorities website is bringing colle… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How we hacked our colleague’s smart home  In this article, we publish the results of our study of the Fibaro Home C… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[*EXPIRED* Push-ups   The “Push-ups” utility lets you depend the proper push-ups you could have finished. Additional… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ScarCruft continues to evolve, introduces Bluetooth harvester  Executive summary After publishing our initial serie… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spam and phishing in Q1 2019  Quarterly highlights Valentine’s Day As per tradition, phishing timed to coincide wit… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
