<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[102-Year-Old Abandoned Ship is a Floating Forest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The DX-12 Punisher Is A Double-Barreled Shotgun Pistol From The Future #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman Leaves Back Door Open During Storm, Finds 3 Deer Huddled In Living Room #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peter Falk dies at 83; actor found acclaim as 'Columbo' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Solar Powered Floating Islands Could Extract CO2 From Seawater To Produce Fuel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dogs are born with ears and tails. They should get to keep them. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Create a Garden with No Soil, and Little Work #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orangutan from Borneo photographed using a spear tool to fish #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eliminate All Poisons From Your Body In 48 Hours: A Weekend Detoxification Diet Plan #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My life is in danger, says Jacob Zuma]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Image: Zimbabwe's founding leader Robert Mugabe dead at 95: sources #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yet Another Dead Whale Is Grave Reminder Of Our Massive Plastic Problem #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SA’s Load shedding was self-created, special investigation found #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Urgent call for help in the white squatter camps, South Africa]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eskom dishes out huge salaries to execs despite R20 billion loss #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man Builds "Dog Train" To Take Rescued Pups Out On Little Adventures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man who robbed bank to get away from wife sentenced to home confinement #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Another R139bn stolen at Eskom? – probe underway #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, Plastic Straws Are Not The Worst Ocean Contaminant, Cigarette Butts Are #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turmeric and Honey: The Most Powerful Antibiotic That not even Doctors Can Explain #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THE SCARY TRUTH ABOUT THE NOTRE DAME FIRE THAT NO ONE IS TALKING ABOUT... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Losing a dog can be harder than losing a relative or friend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[90-Year-Old Tortoise Gains A New Set Of Wheels After Losing Her Legs To Rat Bites #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ecuador Claims It's Been Hit With 40 Million Cyberattacks Since Giving Up Julian Assange #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Mandisa Mfeka, South Africa's 1st black female combat pilot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Terrifying 'flying grenade' drone can wipe out enemies 6 MILES away – and can even loiter in sky for an ambush #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shocking photo shows Caribbean Sea being 'choked to death by human waste' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Science Confirms That Dogs Can Recognize A Bad Person #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trophy Hunter Who Kills Endangered Elephants and Lions 'Eaten By Crocodiles' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Landmark Study Shows Half of Cancer Patients are Killed by Chemo -- NOT Cancer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Puppy Drags Her New Blanket Outside To Share With A Cold Homeless Dog #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[50 Astonishing Benjamin Franklin Quotes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Energy drinks 'completely ruined my life' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American biker gang destroys dog fight rings and rescues animals from violent owners — Bikernet Blog - Online Biker… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Children who help with the housework are more likely to be successful in life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Africa’s army has run out of money – here’s how bad things have got #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britain faces invasion of Asian Hornets that kill humans with one sting – 80 nests found #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Afrikaaners were oppressed and confined to concentration camps by the English yet they rose above it and built SA” #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Firefighters, EMS can now free pets from hot cars without penalty #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three ‘Rhino Poachers’ Eaten By Lions After Breaking In To South African Game Reserve #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Artist Transforms Found Stones Into Animals You Can Hold in the Palm of Your Hand #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More people are adopting old, sick dogs to keep them from dying alone and afraid #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Traffic Camera Accidentally Snaps Beautiful Photo of a Snowy Owl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Limpopo Hawks clamp down on yet another vehicle testing station, arrest five officials - Review #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wild Elephant Brings Her New Baby To Meet The People Who Saved Her Life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Missing Dog Returns Home With New Dog And Goat Friend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Dog the Bounty Hunter' wife Beth Chapman dies of cancer at 51 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Barbaric': Two KZN paramedics shot, robbed after fake emergency call #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Guy Invented A Homemade Beehive To Save The Bees, And It's Going Viral! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miracle Teenager Survives On His Own For Almost 6 Hours With No Wi-Fi #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Malema warns ANC of bloodshed and ‘unled revolution’ if land isn’t expropriated #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Ramaphosa won't help": FF+ urge farmers to defend themselves instead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to bring back rural safety commandos to tackle farm attacks? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Before Facebook: This Is How We Used to Unfriend People Back Then #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hero Dog Found 7 Kittens in The Forest And Decided To Become Their Mother #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FW De Klerk And The Covert Dealings Prior To The 1994 Elections (Where Did All The Gold And Diamonds Go?) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Owl Missed The Man Who Saved Her So Much She Couldn’t Stop Hugging Him #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Child draws on dad's passport, dad gets stuck in South Korea #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Study: The More you Hug your Kids, the More Their Brains Develop #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicole Kidman Says: Trump Is The Best President In U.S History, We Must Respect Him. Do you Support Her? - Kh Stars #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Moringa Concentrate Extract for Diabetes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teacher's Tongue 'Eaten Away' After Drinking Six Energy Drinks A Day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nice Whale Returns Phone Woman Accidentally Dropped Into Sea #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A farm under siege – and why it should worry us all #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Researchers Discover That Magnesium, NOT Calcium, Is The Key To Healthy, Strong Bones #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Ingredients in McDonald’s Fries Linked to Brain Damage, Autoimmune Disease, and Cancer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boeing unveils rendering of hypersonic jet that would fly from US to Japan in 3 hours #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Traffic officer given 6 years behind bars for accepting R200 bribe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“Jesus Not Coming Back By The Looks Of It” Admits Vatican #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OPINIONISTA: The National Health Insurance Bill is a blueprint for disaster #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He Pours Dish Soap Into The Toilet. The Reason? This Changes Everything! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Female Dragonflies Fake Their Death To Avoid Males #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vladimir Putin Reveals: The West Is Controlled By Satanic Pedophiles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mum gives dying son CANNABIS to ease cancer pain and he makes miracle recovery #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Massive Studies Link Soda To Heart Attacks, Brain Damage, Depression, Kidney Damage and More #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Devon man catches world's BIGGEST carp at staggering 232lbs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cash in transit robbers accidentally bombed the getaway car killing themselves along with the money #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Honey thieves strike again in KZN, kill farmer's bees #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MacGyver Star Dead at Age 67 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon Tribe Wins Lawsuit Against Big Oil, Saving Millions Of Acres Of Rainforest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2-Year-Old Toddler Went Missing For 2 Days, Found Protected By A Hero Pit Bull! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SAPS harbours thousands of convicted criminals, says Bheki Cele #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am a ‘credible leader’, I am ‘not corrupt’ – Ace Magashule #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goodbye Surgery - Scientists Just Made Eye Drops that Dissolve Cataracts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Goose Saves Stray Puppy From Freezing Weather By Warming Him Under Its Wings #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mangoes Destroy Cancer, Blast Fat, Reduce Cholesterol, and More #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eat More Pumpkin Seeds: They Kill Cancer Cells, Improve Sleep and Eyesight, Fight Diabetes and More #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Petrol price increase: Motorists could potentially pay R17-per-litre in June #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grieving Horse Smells His Beloved Owner’s Casket And Breaks Down At His Funeral #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
