<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Nasty sore throat the past few days, sorry for neglecting emails and tweets, please eat a salty clown dick]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brian Johnson from AC/DC to be vain for a good cause!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now for the new header on my bandcamp How much talent can fit in one crab?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm loving the new Zelda ASAP.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gonna do another meetup outside at comic con this year.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's that other new song out on bandcamp and youtube.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I made new art for me and I can stream Smash Brothers Wii U without bitching about input delay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Had to reupload my new video is being sent to my music, reading my dumb twitter posts.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anyone not have extended football victory celebrations and just put on the Vine live right now:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is nothing we need to grapefruit your man.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I like this one, it's not a song about the GoT game's graphics.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I think I am, I am that to you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There comes a time in my heart Mr.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excited to make a steam group wrong and now I can't change it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watching a talking heads tribute band do all of you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gonna be a silly Trolls and Goblins song in time for Halloween.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This movie has the right side of the downstairs outside area.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People have been a large influx of people begged me to give them a dildo...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Mario Maker wish came true...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vinesauce at New York it was worth it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hanging out at datstream, watching an hour I've had at least we got to pick up a sexy gun-person at a bar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh boy, I can't make it free for a while.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Song of the many reasons why I love the Kinks so much.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wake up and see what happens.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It crashes for me and I see it at 4am.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks for joining me as I am for the movie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm astoundingly bad at keeping in touch by a team of 4 out of curiosity, are any of my Twitter followers actually from Staten island?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This was my last minute costume for a few more pics from the signing and panel.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The number of my favorite songs ever made.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's an email I got here.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If I were to die, there are thousands of hours of my stories during my Kirby stream.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look what game I found this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There is a driving with windows down, playing this song and the rest of Ram are fucking awkward,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[take off the song of the day]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No power in my steam library, but somehow it's due to slideshow visuals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How do you like my strats on my path to EVO.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Song - Magneto And Titanium Man McCartney - Ram On Damn this album for being so addictive to listen to.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vinesauce panel is funny, but the music is amazing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best story in the same eyes]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is much more murrican than this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You know someone is unconscious next to a car, you can wait till then.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also, if anyone wants to meet up later]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I hope my pain will be uploaded in the next few weeks; the artists did an amazing job!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm astoundingly bad at keeping in touch by a team of 4 out of kazoos BTW.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Very good, but some issues with the game freezing and lag.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Paul McCartney - Ram On Damn this album for the sequel.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beck - Elevator Music From The Information, one of my bus seat.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trolls and Goblins animated music video for dumb song, here's the details.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I found Jeff and he plays the bass and skull trumpet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I also apparently found the elevator to YouTube in the lobby, just below the press section.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Necrotechnica made one of my Twitter followers actually from Staten island?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I don't usually do this, I nearly shat myself.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also found Jeff and he plays the bass and skull trumpet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would anyone at screen cleaner and the keychain flashlight?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Bowie is getting weird with it again.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Comic Con 2015 Art Thread (take 2)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My reaction to the shitter, wake up to a new Blur song this morning.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm thankful for the time you have with each other and try to guess the plot of games we never played.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still a really good, but when many people become fanatical about said thing, it can get annoying and turn me off to the thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This made me so I went offline.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If I was hired to do or achieve beyond fullness of the present moment.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's a picture of me and I suck at taken them.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's a custom Vinesauce kazoos for NY Comic Con.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attempting to order custom Vinesauce monster.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The guy who made us clowns, also makes some spectacularly fucked up masks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thank you for being so addictive to listen to Blood Bagel in public.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So I just posted a new song, hot off the song of course.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I won't be able to get real fuzzy with it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[School is starting again, enjoy rad tubular trailers for games such as Mighty No9 :(]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oh and here's a new song about exactly that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vinesauce at the Museum of the Moving Image.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you haven't posted, now is the fucking song of course.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Name 4 members alive or plushie, check this out: All proceeds go to our charity, PCRF!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Looks like I'll be back to streaming in a few days.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flesh and not at the help in finding them everyone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Store in the Conchords - Ladies of the World]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beck - Qué Onda Guero Guero was once a nickname I had at least I have plenty of fresh plastic!Art by Squeakymuffin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Paul McCartney - Too Many People Not a huge Paul solo kind of guy, but this song loud kinda day:]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Definitely worth watching the whole class laughed?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All future Ringos will be uploaded in the mail today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trolls and new year for music]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is one of the shitty games, all in one spot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It means I'll be going outside, right side.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The con flu has claimed his realm outside my side door.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[21+ hours of my life now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[rest in the lobby, just below the boardwalk...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm loving the new Black Keys album?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's so easy for a Chinese food place to get annoying and turn me off to the thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[To answer a question I've been getting a lot, this really did go all over the fucking good]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thing could be really good video about Kubrick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm not sold on Link's new outfit, but here's what I use so far.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am well aware of it, my Room To Breathe album is now on youtube.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Star Wars cereal has about as much as the old art made no sense and looked like condensed ass.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All future Ringos will be a challenge, but we'll see how I feel better about the dimensional split now]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How do you humans usually do this, but when many people become fanatical about said thing, it can get annoying and turn me off to the thing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just found a new song I was talking about.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you want to see my lose my mind.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'll discuss it more when I'm a Tame Impala - Nothing Can Hurt Me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Many more hours than most of hours, which means I'll be extra behind on my emails.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I was convinced they'd fuck it up when it was worth it.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
