<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Bolton backs officials who testified in House #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate impeachment trial: How to watch and what we don't know #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least 6 celebrities are showing off new face tattoos, including a sneaker and a bloody buzz saw… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Senate is bracing for a fight from the start as today's trial marks a historic moment in US history… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He is fashioning the presidency around his own personality. It's unrestrained, unaccountable, often profane and imp… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 16-year-old boy broke up a bullying incident. Days later, police say he was fatally shot by one of the boys invol… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8 unanswered questions about Trump and Ukraine that will live on #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We're about to find out if Netflix can keep Disney+ at bay #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pamela Anderson and Jon Peters split 12 days after their wedding #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Easy Ways to Start Building Financial Security, via OTDP #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MLB considering new playoff format and live selection TV show, report says #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US threatens to hike tariffs on UK car exports #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hear what Kobe Bryant said in one of his final interviews #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hong Kong to take drastic measures over coronavirus #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Parasite's' win is an awesome test of the one-inch barrier #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 teens accused of killing their mothers and siblings within a week #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon steamrolls Bill Maher #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Easy Ways to Start Building Financial Security #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hunters put the squeeze on 80 snakes in Florida's Python Bowl #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giveaway Profits PRO Review, via OTDP #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists discover cool phenomenon with sand dunes #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conor McGregor wins in first UFC match in 15 months #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The humanities aren't dead #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Veteran-turned-impeachment manager makes fight over military aid personal #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Irish election count begins as tied exit poll means it's too close to call #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's the right way to cut an avocado for your Super Bowl party without injuring yourself #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opening statements in Harvey Weinstein's sex assault trial are set to begin #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Easy Ways to Start Building Financial Security, via OTDP #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An 18-year-old stole the Grammys #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hope Hicks' return is a sure sign of White House arrogance #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giveaway Profits PRO Review, via OTDP #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fact check: 65 ways Trump's been dishonest about impeachment #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A shooter is on the run after wounding NYPD officer in 'assassination attempt' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Declassified FBI bulletin says Saudi officials help their citizens flee US legal issues #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A boy paid off the lunch debt for his entire school #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What in the world does pettifogging mean? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Key impeachment witness expects to leave White House post, source says #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The stock market is eerily calm again. Uh-oh... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why the San Francisco 49ers are called the 49ers #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After ending her losing streak in finals, is Serena Williams on course to win the Australian Open?… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The club of $1 trillion companies just keeps growing #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An unlikely friendship between a coyote and badger was caught in this adorable video #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Immigrant acquitted in Kate Steinle shooting is not competent to stand trial, evaluator says #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Ways To Make Money On Bitcoin In 2020, via OTDP #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A black high school athlete walked into a locker room to see a racist drawing with his name on it… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More Iranian students are being deported at US airports, advocates say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK will allow Huawei to help build its 5G network despite US pressure #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More fallout: Bolton's book could pull Barr into political fight he has avoided for months #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Angela Merkel lambasts her party's cooperation with far-right AfD #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's time for the Puppy Bowl! Here's everything you need to know #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 shot, 2 dead, at a South Carolina bar #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Hudson to perform Kobe Bryant tribute at All-Star Game #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the 'Doomsday Clock' means and why it's bad when we're close to midnight #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Ways To Make Money On Bitcoin In 2020, via OTDP #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYT: US attorney leading Russia probe investigating whether US intelligence agencies hid information… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The price of wine is dropping fast #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a painful lesson in Trump's impeachment trial #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 1 week, 3 states considered bills to ban discrimination based on hair texture or style #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Queen's grandson Peter Phillips and wife Autumn to divorce #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney parks expand vegan food options and they're delicious (just don't call them 'vegan') #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['No smoking gun': Bezos hacking report leaves cybersecurity experts with doubts #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu indicted in corruption cases #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No smoke, no water, no waste. VR could train the next generation of firefighters #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 killed, 1 wounded in Utah shooting #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: Sinn Fein surged in Ireland's election. Here's why that's so controversial #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York Times editorial board breaks with the norm and endorses two candidates #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Ways To Make Money On Bitcoin In 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lawmakers across the US try to get sky-rocketing cost of insulin under control #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dust and rain causes delays at Australian Open #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Baltimore police sergeant was spat on and kicked during a check, authorities say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surfing champion dies at age 24 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Dakota lawmakers push to let residents keep their plastic bags and straws #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China: US overreacting to outbreak #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barnes and Noble suspends book covers over backlash #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The supergiant Betelgeuse star will explode. It's just a matter of when, astronomers say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['SNL' presents the impeachment trial of President Trump 'you wish had happened' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why truckers are turning to cooking oil #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant's final hours started with prayer. It would end in a crush of metal #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael Avenatti heads to trial for allegedly trying to extort millions of dollars from Nike #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Avlon: Trump is at war with the truth #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1 student was killed and 5 others injured after they were hit by a pick-up truck during track practice… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These oil companies are leading the industry's green transformation #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Playing golf may help older adults live longer, study says #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IPhone maker Foxconn wants to work with Fiat Chrysler on electric cars #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctor tried to save lives, but was silenced. Now he has coronavirus #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What you need to know about today's Women's March #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How To Earn Money Online- 20 Ways To Start Making Money Online As A Student #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi: I'm not counting Biden out #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Oscar, anyway? And other Academy Awards secrets #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How To Earn Money Online- 20 Ways To Start Making Money Online As A Student, via OTDP #URL#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Authorities believe man faked his own death to avoid prosecution in child rape case #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Kansas City Chiefs got their name, and why it's so controversial #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are these Spanish islands the next adventure hotspot? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Photo of mice squabbling on subway platform wins prestigious photography award #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This river is now filled with 97,000 gallons of wine after a spill #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opinion: Adam Schiff is the one helping Vladimir Putin destabilize US democracy #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The coronavirus could cost China's economy $60 billion #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inaugural class at LeBron James' school to receive free tuition to Kent State #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN fact checks Trump claim about Ivanka during speech #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opinion: Democrats, stop pretending we're in dictatorship #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
