<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Kanye West Spends Time with Daughter North Amid Twitter Rant #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All About the Royal Baby's Debut Bonnet — and It's Connection to Big Sister Princess… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Allison Mack Released from Jail Into Her Parents' Custody — But Will Remain Under House… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tina Knowles Lawson Poses with 'Talented' Tiffany Haddish Following 'Who Bit #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney World’s Free Dining Plan Is Back—Here’s How to Save on Your Next Trip #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House of Horrors Siblings' Move to New Home Marks 'Wonderful' Turn in Their Recovery: Expert #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Has Golden State Killer — Believed Responsible for 12 Murders and 45 Rapes in 1970s and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Double Trouble: Firefighters Rescue Man Who Got Stuck in Tree Trying to Rescue Cat Stuck in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lauren Conrad Shows Off Her Adorable 'Dinner Date' — 9-Month-Old Son Liam #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald and Melania Trump Hold Hands at Their First State Dinner After Earlier Awkward Moment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian West Promotes Her Upcoming KKW Body Launch with Racy Topless Photo #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's All in a Name: When Will Royal Baby #HASHTAG#'s Name Be Announced? #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Married at First Sight Season Six Star Shawniece Jackson #HASHTAG# First Child Ahead of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Groom Paralyzed Playing Football Walks Down The Aisle: 'The Accident Brought Me To Her' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NBA Vet Derek Fisher Is Engaged to the Ex-Wife of Former Teammate and Rival Matt Barnes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Tyler Baltierra Says He Is Trying 'Natural Remedies' to Treat Bipolar Disorder #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Newlywed Richard Gere Is a 'Much Happier' Man at 68 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Stars of New Royal Baby and Princess Diana Are Aligned, Says Di's Former Astrologer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tyra Banks Says Lindsay Lohan Will Star in Life-Size 2! #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Somber Morning for Prince Harry and Meghan Markle as They Attend Veterans' Memorial Service #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pregnant Rachel Weisz Walks First Red Carpet Since Announcing She Is #HASHTAG# with Daniel… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Every Perfect Detail About Princess Charlotte’s Adorable Hospital Look #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Does the Birth of a New Prince Change the Royal Line of Succession? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blake Shelton Seemingly Calls Out Ex-Wife Miranda Lambert Amid Reports She's Dating Married… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Husband of Southwest Explosion Victim Speaks Out About Her Loss: 'I Have Not Been Angry Yet' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keith Urban Coaxes Nicole Kidman on Stage for Romantic Duet: 'Come On, Baby!' #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lindsay Lohan’s Childhood #HASHTAG# Lost to Foreclosure After Mom Dina Defaults on Mortgage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She’s Back at It! First Look at Carrie Underwood in New Athleisure Campaign: ‘She Looks… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Shares ANOTHER Nude Photo As Concerns for Husband Kanye West Grow #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mia Farrow Admits She Didn't Want Dylan to 'Resurrect' Woody Allen Molestation Accusations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scarlett Johansson Accidentally Flashed a Man on a Plane! 'My Entire Vagina Was Out' #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Family Goals! Enrique Iglesias Poses with Both of His 4-Month-Old Twins on 'Game Day' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Family Shocks Mother-to-Be with Gender Reveal — That She Can Wear! Watch the Special Moment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girls Trip! Brie Bella Says She May Take Nikki to Napa on What Would Have Been Her Wedding… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiffany Haddish Says Getting a Perm to Impress Guys Was Dumb: ‘They’re Gonna Like You… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See Chip Gaines Adorably Fanboying Over His Pregnant Wife, Joanna, Outside Today #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim &amp; Rob Kardashian Honor Victims of the Armenian Genocide 103 Years After First Attack #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump's State Dinner Will Feature Fancy Offerings — Not Hamburgers As Promised on Campaign… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michigan Police Line 13 Semi-Trucks Under Bridge to Help Suicidal Man #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen Wants Out of Kim Zolciak and NeNe Leakes' Feud: 'Keep This Mess to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Total Bellas' Brie Bella Talks Raising Daughter Birdie, 11 Months, as a Vegetarian #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Channing Tatum Walks His First Red Carpet Since Split from Jenna Dewan #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katie Holmes and Jamie Foxx Caught Leaving Restaurant Separately After Date Night in N.Y.C. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britney Spears Is 'Switching Up' Her Workout Routine to Prep for the Piece of Me Tour #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Woman Graduates College and Invites a Special Guest — the Police Officer Who Arrested Her #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teenager Allegedly Enlisted Friends to Fatally Stab His Mom After First Trying to Poison… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Cleveland Kidnapping Survivor Michelle Knight Found Love After Her Captivity #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[50 Expert Tips to Help You Look and Feel More Beautiful — Now! #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Without Flea, Tick and Heartworm Protection, Your Pet Could Develop Serious Health Problems #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince William Says New Prince Is 'Behaving Himself' and Sleeping 'Well' as Name Wait… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big Reveal! Robert and Kym Johnson Herjavec Name Newborn #HASHTAG# Haven Mae and Hudson Robert #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lisa Rinna Recreates Her Playboy Hair from Almost a Decade Ago for RHOBH Reunion #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Garner Fangirls Over Ellen Page's Dancer Wife: 'I Cannot Stop Watching' Her #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rachel McAdams Says Her Sex Scene with Rachel Weisz Had an 'Energy' She Never Had with Male… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner's Wig Guru Tokyo Stylez Says She Owns 'At Least 100' of His Creations #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meek Mill Released From Jail After Serving 5 Months: 'I Plan to Overturn This Unwarranted… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rachel McAdams Makes First Red Carpet Appearance Since Welcoming First Child #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lethal Weapon's Clayne Crawford Apologizes as He Admits He Was 'Reprimanded' for On-Set… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessica Chastain Responds After Thandie Newton Says Time's Up Left Her Out: 'No One Is… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celebrating International Guide Dog Day with One of the Smartest Puppies We Know #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teen Mom OG's Tyler Baltierra Reveals He Was Diagnosed with Bipolar Disorder #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SJP by Sarah Jessica Parker Bridal Collaboration with GILT Is Finally Here! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Holding Hands and Brushing Off 'Dandruff': Trump Tries to a Forge Bromance with French… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beach Hotties! Shirtless Charlie Hunnam Shows Off Buff Body in Hawaii with Mystery Woman #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Renée Zellweger, Is That You? Actress Transforms Into Judy Garland on Set of Upcoming Biopic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the Ohio Teen Fighting Infant Heroin Addiction One Baby Blanket at a Time #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner Shows Off Her 11-Week Post-Baby Body in Curve-Hugging Dress #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are They or Aren't They? We Investigate the Status of 7 Celeb Couples Who Are Confusing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton's Subtle Tribute to the Queen After She Gave Birth Almost Went Unnoticed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kanye West Has Had 'Explosive' Fights with Kris Jenner &amp; Kim Kardashian Can't 'Control' Him… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See Melania Trump's Latest Awkward Hand-Holding Moment -- In the White Hat Setting Twitter… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virginia Daycare Worker Accused of Sexually Assaulting Multiple 5-Year-Old Girls #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Dwayne Johnson’s Loving Relationship with Longtime Girlfriend Lauren Hashian #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists Have Discovered That Uranus Stinks — Literally #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anne Hathaway Hits Red Carpet After Shutting Down Body Shamers While 'Gaining Weight' for… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Handmaid’s Tale Season 2 Continues Its Nightmarish Saga with Undiminished Terror and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marcia Gay Harden Recalls the Heartbreaking Moment Her Mom with Alzheimer's Didn't… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hank Azaria 'Willing to Step Aside' from Voicing Indian Simpsons Character Apu Amid… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Guy Fieri Surprise Car Enthusiast Jay Leno with a Giant Motorized Shopping Cart #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Flirty Hillary?' Clinton Loves to Get Giggly with 'Handsome, Preferably Straight' Men: New… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See the Odd Gift from George H.W. Bush That Became Barbara's 'Most Prized Possession' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See Prince George, Princess Charlotte and the New Royal Baby's Debut Photos Side-by-Side #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Destiny's Child's Michelle Williams Didn't Think 'Young' #HASHTAG# Crowd Would Know Who… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Can't Stop Auction House From Selling Lock of Her Hair, Underwear, Tupac Breakup… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Will We See the Royal Family of Five Together for the First Time? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bachelor Producers Announce New Dating Series Hosted by Jesse Palmer: All About The Proposal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Photo of Barack Obama Consoling George W. Bush Has New Poignance with Bush's Dad… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baby Photos Prove These Stars Transformed From Cuties to Beauties, Inside and Out! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Anderson's Cause of #HASHTAG# Revealed: Night Court Star Died of a Stroke #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Garner Shows Off Ripped Arms After Getting In Shape for New Action-Packed Role #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG#'s Daughter Willow on Her Beautiful Issue Cover: 'Does It Mean I Get an Extra Dessert?' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Legend Says He’s Been Cooking for Pregnant Chrissy Teigen Because She ‘Needs to Sit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Pit Bull Attacks Woman on New York City Subway — and Police Are Investigating #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exotic Ticks Identified After Farmer Is Found Covered in Thousands Have Now Made N.J. Home #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Texas Mom Allegedly Tried Burning Her Car With 3 Daughters Inside: 'You’re Going To See… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 Things You Need Now from Wayfair’s Massive One-Day #HASHTAG# Sale #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kanye West ‘Seems to Be on the Edge’ and ‘Is Very Hard to Deal with Right Now’: Sources #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Listeria and Risk of Botulism Prompt Recalls on Two Types of Raw Dog Food #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Jenna Dewan, Justin Theroux &amp; More Celebs Returned to Social Media After Announcing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Hudson Wishes Tobey Maguire's Ex Jennifer Meyer Happy Birthday with Sweet Post: 'Love… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
