<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama to make his first appearance on HBO's 'Real Time With Bill Maher' - Chicago Tribune #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders supporter Susan Sarandon endorses Jill Stein - New York Daily News #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bryan Cranston Would Leave the US If Donald Trump Becomes President: 10 Other Stars Who'... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian and Tristan Thompson Put Their Romance on Display With Plenty of Hallow... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake: New Album 'Punches You Between the Eyes' - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clinton says she won't be 'knocked off course' in final week - The Boston Globe #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hilary Duff Apologizes For Offensive Halloween Costume: 'It Was Not Properly Thought Thr... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Writes Open Letter to Fans After Storming Off Stage in Manchester - Us Weekly #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adele speaks out on baby blues, booze, Beyonce, Bette and Trump - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An 'AHS: Coven' &amp; 'Murder House' Crossover Is Coming &amp; These Are The Characters Who Need... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More TV Networks Just Signed on to Hulu's New Live-Streaming Service - Fortune #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fox, Disney Add Channels to Hulu's Live TV Service - Hollywood Reporter #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opera Fan's Last Wish Led to Terror Scare at the Met - New York Times #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Today,' 'GMA,' more morning show hosts reveal their Halloween costumes - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Can't Keep Her Cool in Ellen DeGeneres' Haunted House - E! Online #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Briefly Returned to Facebook Last Night - E! Online #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicole Phelps's Wedding Dress Designer: 'She Did Not Want the Traditional Bridal Gown' -... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey &amp; James Packer in Settlement Negotiations - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Norman Brokaw, a Stalwart at William Morris, Dies at 89 - Billboard #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyoncé, Jay Z and Blue Ivy Carter Dress Up as Barbie and Ken for Halloween - E! Online #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Jane the Virgin Gets Right About Sex That Game of Thrones Doesn't - Vanity Fair #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Relive the creepiest 'Stranger Things' moments with cute Funko figures - CNET #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead: Khary Payton Describes Ezekiel Meeting Negan - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyoncé, Jay Z, &amp; Blue Ivy SLAY Halloween Once Again In Barbie &amp; Ken Themed Costumes -- ... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ricky Skaggs, Chris Stapleton honored by ASCAP - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead's Real Game Changer Isn't Negan—It's King Ezekiel - Vanity Fair #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Posts 1st Photo On Social Media After Robbery — Gorgeous Pic - Hollywood Life #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Late Show': Mel Gibson Advises Younger Self to "Shut the F--- Up" - Hollywood Reporter #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian 'Not Expected' To Attend Upcoming Event Honoring Her Late Father - PerezH... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead Episode 702 Recap: Meet King Ezekiel - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['#HASHTAG#': Mariah Carey Breaks Social Media Silence Amid Breakup Rumors  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Joanne' Just Became Lady Gaga's Fourth No. 1 Album - Celebuzz #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner Just Won Halloween With Her "Dirrty" Tribute to Christina Aguilera - E! Online #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CMA Awards: Who should win, who will win - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talk Shows Celebrate Halloween: Hamilton, Pikachu, Joker and Harley Quinn Among Most Pop... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga earns fourth No. 1 album with Joanne - Entertainment Weekly #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jane the Virgin showrunner dissects THAT sex scene - Entertainment Weekly #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake, Jessica Biel and Son Silas Dressed Up as Trolls and We Can't Stop the... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Crown': TV Review - Hollywood Reporter #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Joins 'Fantastic Beasts' Sequel - Hollywood Reporter #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Powder Sprinkled Into Metropolitan Opera Pit May Have Been Human Ashes - Billboard #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Things We Learned About Zayn Malik in His New Book: Anxiety, Evictions and How His Mom... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosmith's Joey Kramer Wants Nothing to Do with President Obama Photo - Billboard #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bruno Mars, Mark Ronson Face Lawsuit Over 'Uptown Funk' - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake, Jessica Biel, Son Silas Troll Out for Halloween: Cute Photos! - Us Weekly #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hear Song Taylor Swift Wrote for Little Big Town - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Walking Dead': What the Comics Reveal About Ezekiel and Carol's Possible Future - Holly... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Walking Dead' Season 7: How The Kingdom copes with Negan - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fake 'Stranger Things' newscast gives fans an update on Barb - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rob Kardashian Blocks His Sisters and Calls Them 'Dramatic' After Fighting with Blac Chy... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Doctor Strange': It's a trippy kind of magic - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Box Office: 'Inferno' Fizzles With $15 Million as 'Madea' Pulls Off Victor... - Reuters #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Wrote a Country Song for Little Big Town — And It's a Total Breakup Jam - U... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Interactive Demogorgon Costume Is the Strangest Thing You'll See All Halloween - PO... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Madness and Majesty of “Hacksaw Ridge” - The New Yorker #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Timberlake and Jessica Biel Dress Up as Trolls for Halloween With Cute Son Silas:... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gwyneth Paltrow Give the Little Black Dress with a Sparkly Twist for LACMA Art + Film Ga... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today in Entertainment: 'The Flash' loses another director and Kim Kardashian's social m... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Her Own Words: What Kind of Girlfriend Will Meghan Markle Be for Prince Harry?  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bryan Cranston says he 'would definitely move' to Canada if Donald Trump became presiden... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bette Midler dressed as her 'Hocus Pocus' character, and it's to die for - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bryan Cranston Would Leave the US If Donald Trump Becomes President: 10 Other Stars Who'... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Is Meghan Markle? 5 Things to Know About Prince Harry's Rumored New Flame - Yahoo News #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will Mariah Carey Have to Return Her $10 Million Engagement Ring? Probably Not  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Timeless' Gets More Episodes at NBC - Hollywood Reporter #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen Performs, Jon Stewart Roasts Donald Trump at Stand Up for Heroes Benef... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Stranger Things' Halloween Sketch Addresses Barb's Fate - Newsweek #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's what's coming and going on Netflix in November - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adele Talks Postpartum Depression With Vanity Fair: 'I Felt Like I'd Made the Worst Deci... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Did Taylor Swift Write "Better Man" About? We Investigate the Lyrics for Little Big ... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Friendly Exes Jennifer Lopez and Marc Anthony Reunite in Miami for Hillary Clinton Conce... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Halloween Throwback! See How Kim and Kourtney Kardashian Celebrated the Holiday in 1982 ... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CMA Awards By the Numbers: Who Has the Most Wins? Who Is the Youngest Winner? - Billboard #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey and James Packer's split is a mess of money, mansions and gossip grenades -... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katy Perry and Orlando Bloom Celebrate Her 32nd Birthday with a Grease-Inspired '50s Par... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Time to Get Dirrty! Kylie Jenner Recreates Christina Aguilera's 2002 Look for Round 2 of... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Westworld' Broke Every Major TV-Sex Boundary in One Episode: That Orgy, Necrophilia and... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blake Lively Asks for a “Husband Upgrade” After Taylor Swift Dresses as Deadpool - Vanity Fair #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Norman Brokaw, trailblazing talent agent for top Hollywood stars, dies at 89 - LA Daily News #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Christina Aguilera Reacts to Kylie Jenner's 'Dirrty' Halloween Costume, and She Approves... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Westworld' Recap 1×05: 'The Thing About Forgetting' - Observer #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ezekiel Is Exactly What The Walking Dead Needed Exactly When It Needed Him - Comi #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stranger Things newscast proves people actually cared about Barb - Entertainment Weekly #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Walking Dead': 7 Key Moments From "The Well" - Hollywood Reporter #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heidi Klum's Halloween Costume: Model Goes As Herself With A Crew Of Clones - Hollywood Life #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hilary Duff Addresses Native American, Pilgrim Halloween Costume: 'I Am So Sorry to Peop... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything We Know About Kim Kardashian's Life After Her Traumatic Paris Robbery  #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Stranger Things' gives Barb a bit of justice - USA TODAY #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heidi Klum Clones Herself for Epic Halloween Costume That Includes Five Prosthetically E... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey Enjoys Drama-Free Night Out With Close Friends Days After James Packer Brea... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney Is Making a Live-Action Version of Snow White - E! Online #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Walking Dead: Khary Payton has a fascinating theory about Ezekiel and Negan - Entert... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey's Out Again With Backup Dancer - #URL# #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Photos: Heidi Klum comes to party as herself, clones for... - Atlanta Journal Constitution #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suspicious powder at NYC's Met Opera may have been ashes, police say - CBS News #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hilary Duff and Jason Walsh Apologize Following Backlash Over Controversial Halloween Co... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Jane the Virgin' is no longer: Behind the making of Monday's big episode - Los Angeles Times #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Set to Star in Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them Sequel - E! Online #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hollywood's Most Controversial Halloween Costumes: Hilary Duff, Jason Walsh, Heidi Klum ... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warner Bros partners with Google &amp; others to promote “Fantastic Beasts” with mobile spel... #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
