<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Don Jr. Gives NASTY Surprise To Hillary Clinton After Calling For Trump’s Impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IT’S A MIRACLE! The Saudi King Gives SPECIAL Gift To President Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loretta Lynch Has Now Been Tied to Trump Wire Tapping #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BUSTED: Hillary Clinton Got $145,920,412 Richer Thanks To Russia... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Friends Think That Being A Socialist Is About Being Nice #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI Agents Believe Bill Clinton Struck Secret Deal With Loretta Lynch in Plane Meeting #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Illegal immigrants will collect Social Security benefits beginning in 2017. Please stop this, Congress! - True... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big Pharma Stands To Lose $18.5 Billion If All 50 States Legalize Medical Marijuana #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Kathy Griffin Just Lost Her Last Hope – You Won’t Believe What Happened To Her Moments Ago! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New ABC Poll Shows a NEW Record For Trump's Approval Ratings! It Is HIGHER Than You Think! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IT'S OVER! What Pelosi Got Caught Doing Will Put Her in JAIL For A LONG Time - SHOULD SHE BE ARRESTED?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will Obama Be The First President In History Given A Felony Charge #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IT HAS NOW BEEN CONFIRMED: It Was NOT RUSSIA … IT WAS OBAMA! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Top Democrat Just Backed President Trump 100% Over Obama’s Wiretap Scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Germany Announces Plan To PROSECUTE OBAMA After Learning The Sick Thing He Did In Final Days Or... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Sessions Just Handed Barack Obama The WORST News Of His Life – It’s Happening! ~ US Political Insight #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHOA! Look What Melania Just Did To Her Entire Flight Crew After What Happened To Her Staff ⋆ Freedom Daily #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poll : 95% Say Hillary Clinton Should Be Criminally Prosecuted !]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calling “All Hands”: The Immediate Arrest Of President Barack Obama - USAPoliticsNow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[POLL : TRUMP PLANS TO UNDO OBAMA’S WORK AND DEPORT ALL MUSLIM REFUGEES. DO YOU SUPPORT THAT? || - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senator Tom Cotton: We Know Where the Leaks Are Coming From: Obama Administration Officials! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump Announces Sale of California to Mexico – The Art of The Deal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Sessions: Charge the Mayor of New Orleans with breaking federal, perjury and breaking OSHA laws. - Sign the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Orders Removal Of Islamic Symbols, Practices In The White House. Do You Support Him?! - USA NEWS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HERE Is a LIST OF EVERY SINGLE TIME OBAMA COMMITTED An IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE That DEMS &amp; MEDIA COVERED UP -... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[State Passes Law Letting Teachers Use Bibles In The Classroom. Do They Have Your Support? - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FDA Announces That DTap Vaccine Can Cause Autism #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Trey Gowdy Sends DEVASTATING NEWS To Obama... This Could Mean WAR! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING : 1.2 BILLION Barrels of Oil Discovered in Alaska! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Confirmed! Reid’s Letter ADMITS Guilt In Wiretap – Dems Are TERRIFIED! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge Jeanine Pirro Goes All In, Rips Michelle Obama Limb From Limb On Live TV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attorgey General Lynch Signed Off On ALL FISA Applications to WireTap Trump - TREASON! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING : Kremlin Spokesman Confirms Russian Ambassador Met With Clinton Campaign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hospital Makes Tragic Announcement About The Second Victim From Virginia Shooting - PLEASE PRAY! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Massive Rally AGAINST Islam In France But You’d NEVER Know It If You Watch CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: ICE Raids Four Kentucky Towns–Arrest 53 ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS - DO YOU APPROVE? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BRAKING: Nancy Pelosi KICKED OUT of Congress Because...... - USAPoliticsNow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus: “TODAY I LEAVE AMERICA &amp; NEVER COME BACK”... See Ya! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TRUMP SIGNS UNHEARD OF EXECUTIVE ORDER, Literally TURNING POWER BACK OVER TO THE PEOPLE! - USAPoliticsNow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VIDEO : Maxine Waters Totally Unable to Explain What the Democrats Stand For #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IRONY: Pelosi Says People “Have A Right To Know” What’s In Healthcare Bill Before It Passes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Got Politically ASSASSINATED: Wikileaks Just RELEASED Her Full ISIS DONOR List With Names! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Ted Cruz Goes After Soros and Obama With Stunning New Investigation... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FLASHBACK VIDEO : In 1993 Janet Reno Fired ALL 93 US Attorneys in One Day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Nominates Actual Fascist David Clarke for Department of Homeland Security #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liberals Aren't Liking This Newly-Discovered Photo Of The 1924 Democratic Convention... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Wants to Know Why Hillary Isn't Being INVESTIGATED #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING : YES, President Trump CAN Fire James Comey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In China, businesses &amp; women flock to copy Ivanka Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN Reporter DIDN'T KNOW She Was STILL ON THE AIR, ADMITS OBAMA PAID THEM TO LIE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THIS IS HUGE: Trump’s Secretary Of State Just Fired Every Hillary And Obama Person At The State Department - True... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SESSIONS STRIKES BACK! What He Did Moments Ago Is Going Make Obama Hide Under The Table! * LIBERTY WRITERS NEWS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[QUESTION: Should THESE Men Get The DEATH PENALTY If Found Guilty of Raping a 9-Year-Old Girl? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liberals Aren't Liking This Newly-Discovered Photo Of The 1924 Democratic Convention... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BOOM: Look What Obama Gave Hillary Before Election... This Means TREASON! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JUST IN : George Clooney Leaves U.S And Never Come Back. Do You Support This? - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus: “Today I Leave America And Never Come Back, In 10 Days I Will Be British Citizen” #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rex Tillerson Drops A Bombshell On John McCain - He is DONE! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McCain Proves Once More He's a REAL TRAITOR - Attacks Trump On Live TV - RESIGNATION DEMANDED #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CONFIRMED: FBI tapped computers in Trump tower and found NO EVIDENCE OF COLLUSION! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LEAKED—Obama’s Real Birth Certificate Finally Exposed...Trump Right All Along?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vermont Mayor Loses Election After Flooding His Town With Refugees #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Obama Caught In $3 BILLION Criminal Scandal. Should He Be Prosecuted? - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Chuck Schumer Caught Leading "Pay-to-Play" Scheme... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Orders Removal Of Islamic Symbols, Practices In The White House Do You Supports Him ? - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gowdy To Obama: You Are NO LONGER My President, We Will CHARGE Hillary Clinton #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI BUSTED — Admits That Hillary Belongs In Prison After All! [VIDEO] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Julian Assange Confirms Sanders Was Threatened #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[POLL: Has Obama Made a Complete FOOL Of Himself As President? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Healey - While My Guitar Gently Weeps (Live) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Sessions Just Handed Barack Obama The WORST News Of His Life – It’s Happening! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After Paul Ryan Tried to BLOCK His Border Wall, WATCH Trump Respond With 6 Brutal Words - USAPoliticsNow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Sessions to cut loose the hounds of hell? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Melania Surprises Children At Italian Hospital With Incredible Gift... First Time In HISTORY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uh Oh: Comey Said Under Oath That He's NEVER Been Asked To Halt an FBI Investigation by Senior Officials]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHILE NO ONE WAS PAYING ATTENTION THE FBI HAS JUST ADMITTED HILLARY BELONGS IN PRISON AFTER ALL … [VIDEO] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Julian Assange RELEASES Video Every American Needs To See! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WikiLeaks: Clinton Bribed 6 Republicans To ‘Destroy Trump’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Massive Fraud Just Uncovered, and It Amounts to Over 7 MILLION Votes... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Sean Hannity is declaring war and he NEEDS OUR HELP! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Toby Keith - Courtesy Of The Red, White And Blue (The Angry American) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JUST IN: AG Sessions may Investigate HOLDER/LYNCH Justice Depts via Independent Counsel with power to BRING CHARGES! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JUST IN: Trump Just Gave Comey A Nasty Surprise Destroying Him &amp; His 'Memo' For Good! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXPOSED: Loretta Lynch Now In DEEP Trouble - SHE IS FINISHED! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[OH MY! After What Melania Did Last Night, Everyone In America Fell In Love With Her... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liberals Go HAYWIRE After Seeing What Ivanka Trump Just Got Saudi Arabia to Do... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING : Nancy Pelosi DEMANDS to Know What's IN THE HEALTHCARE LAW Before It Passes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rick Simpson: Cure Cancer With Cannabis THC, Not CBD #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GREAT AGAIN: US Treasury reports National Debt has dropped by $68 BILLION since Trump's Inauguration! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do You Agree? || - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[POLL: Should Trey Gowdy Be The Next FBI Director? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lt. General McInerney: OBAMA &amp; HILLARY FACING UP TO 30 YEARS IN PRISON For VIOLATING Espionage Act of 1917 For... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Ted Cruz Goes After Soros and Obama With Stunning New Investigation... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UN to Trump: Accept Refugees and Illegal Aliens or Else! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poll : Protesters who decided to riot, set fire to cars and break windows on Inauguration Day now face 8 years in... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whoopi Goldberg To Be Fired From Show After Mocking Slain Solider, Should She Be Let Go? - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stage 4 To  No More! See How THIS Man Beat Cancer, No Chemo, No Radiation. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trey Gowdy Is Preparing To Go After Obama’s Illegal Actions. Do You Support This? - True Trumpers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Clinton Foundation Ordered To Cease Operations – Chelsea Charged With Fraud! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NY Car Killer Was Not Drunk, This Is A Premeditated Attack! [VIDEO] ⋆ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
