<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Who needs best-by labels when your package is sensing the food inside it? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How this Danish energy company is transitioning from oil and gas to all renewables #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Bernie Sanders plans to revive the New Deal—governing by mobilization #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This portable personal cleaning device mimics a cat’s tongue #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The North Face is sending its designers back to school. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reproductive health is a business issue #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These bacteria-sniffing dogs are protecting your orange juice from a global citrus pandemic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This biodegradable bioplastic sucks carbon from the air #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This city has a plan to stop homelessness by the end of the year #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Creating new parks in cities can be slow, expensive, and time-consuming. This new system can help. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 ways that supermarkets can help eliminate single-use plastic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How this Danish energy company is transitioning from oil and gas to all renewables #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fruit scraps and ugly pieces of produce are finding second lives. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to unleash creativity on the world’s biggest problems, from Alphabet’s moonshot division #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These carbon offsets counter your emissions while helping rain forest workers access healthcare #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If Uber and Lyft got ahead of EV mandates, they could become the sustainable leaders they so often claim to be. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This is not a new technology. I like to say it's 500 to 700 million years old." #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[By 2050, the U.S. will lose $83 billion a year because of all the nature we’ve destroyed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The North Face’s latest quest? Clothes that last forever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This startup wants to replace traditional package delivery with hyperlocal, electric-trike-driving couriers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eating honey is more complicated than you might think #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The North Face’s latest quest? Clothes that last forever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft should electrify their fleets—before cities make them do it anyway #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Congrats to #USER#, a winner of our 2019 Environmental Journalism Award. #URL# #HASHTAG# https:/…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These DARPA-funded bricks can self-repair—and replicate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Body Shop will start hiring the first person who applies for any retail job #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check out the Australian shopping center that’s touted as the most sustainable in the world #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Progressive politicians’ push for climate action is making Republicans rethink their denial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s time to regulate fashion the way we regulate the oil industry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The simple design change that could help doctors prevent opioid addiction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where in the U.S. is the rent too damn high? Everywhere #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This nonprofit turns vacant storefronts into pop-up communal spaces #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warming is going to push farming North, releasing huge swaths of carbon stored in the soil #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This electric motorcycle startup is transforming the Rwandan taxi industry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The box for this toy doesn’t get thrown out—it’s part of the toy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even business-to-business companies benefit from having a purpose #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giant brands love Loop’s zero-waste packaging—and now it’s coming to a store near you #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new organization wants to help cities create a broader idea of what resilience means #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How maps tracking climate disasters fall short—and endanger lives #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this new Dutch neighborhood, there will be 1 shared car for every 3 households #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[By 2025, Ørsted plans to be the first carbon neutral utility. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could this gorgeous electric plane be the Tesla of the skies? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This just-add-water hand wash lets you stop using so many plastic bottles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new sugar substitute is made from food waste #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get used to the look of Amazon’s new electric delivery van, because they’re making 100,000 of them #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This electric motorcycle startup is transforming the Rwandan taxi industry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“People have opinions about the way it looks—I’ll leave it at that." #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This compostable packaging can tell you when your food is going bad #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We’re on track to hit 1.5°C of warming in 2040. Here’s how it will change our work lives #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Food delivery workers in L.A. spend more to make a delivery than anywhere else #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Progressive politicians’ push for climate action is making Republicans rethink their denial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber and Lyft should electrify their fleets—before cities make them do it anyway #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[California considers tax on companies with large pay gaps between CEOs and their workers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will it take for the 75% of companies that don’t have climate commitments to step up? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagining a world of sustainable, regenerative brands #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fabric, called Circulose, is a new innovation that lets old fabrics be turned into new thread. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This robot trash bin automatically sorts your recyclables for you #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists analyzed 1,700 cities and determined how to design safe streets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If bacteria don’t kill you the old-fashioned way, they’ll just kill you with climate change instead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This bacon looks like the real thing as it sizzles—but it’s made from fungus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even looking at flood maps can’t convince coastal residents their homes will be underwater #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get used to the look of Amazon’s new electric delivery van, because they’re making 100,000 of them #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can food banks put an end to hunger if their biggest donors are the cause of the hunger? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gates have given away $53.8 billion (so far): Here’s what they’ve learned #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This graph will show you the carbon footprint of your protein #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Worker buy-in is the real key for successful corporate sustainability #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What happens when all the tiny satellites we’re shooting into space get hacked? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How maps tracking climate disasters fall short—and endanger lives #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Park in a Truck’ is like Ikea but for building neighborhood parks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Even your tofu shipped to you across the world and wrapped in plastic will have a lower footprint than meat.” #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists analyzed 1,700 cities and determined how to design safe streets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[23% of the Fortune 500 have made a real climate commitment. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This startup wants to replace traditional package delivery with hyperlocal, electric-trike-driving couriers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boston University is building the city’s largest carbon-neutral, fossil fuel-free building #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How maps tracking climate disasters fall short—and endanger lives #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The box for this toy doesn’t get thrown out—it’s part of the toy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most Democratic candidates talk about reining in Wall Street, but they’re short on specifics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In this new Dutch neighborhood, there will be 1 shared car for every 3 households #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reproductive health is a business issue #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new magical coating saves water by making toilets so slippery that poop basically flushes itself #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Giant brands love Loop’s zero-waste packaging—and now it’s coming to a store near you #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new H&amp;M dress is made from wood and recycled jeans #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boston University is building the city’s largest carbon-neutral, fossil fuel-free building #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How this Danish energy company is transitioning from oil and gas to all renewables #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We use a lot of natural processes—bees to pollinate, rivers to irrigate crops. When they’re gone, it’s going to get… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even business-to-business companies benefit from having a purpose #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There are way more people struggling with poverty in New York than we think #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While not as strong as concrete, the bricks could reduce the CO2 footprint of a building, self-heal, and even repro… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new sugar substitute is made from food waste #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill and Melinda Gates have given away $53.8 billion (so far): Here’s what they’ve learned #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Body Shop will start hiring the first person who applies for any retail job #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even business-to-business companies benefit from having a purpose #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Progressive politicians’ push for climate action is making Republicans rethink their denial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will it take for the 75% of companies that don’t have climate commitments to step up? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This biodegradable bioplastic sucks carbon from the air #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want to know if your clothes are ethically sourced? Theory’s new labeling system is for you #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How UNICEF redesigned its tents to be ready for a changing world #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This biodegradable bioplastic sucks carbon from the air #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why just have a box when you can have a launch tower for a rocket? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new H&amp;M dress is made from wood and recycled jeans #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
