<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: A stone pleasure being back at TVO studios for an involved chat with the wonderful Carmen Robertson and the redoubtable…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I can’t wait for the 3rd season of Political Blind Date to premiere January 21st on #USER#. Check out this great intervie…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TVO Original "The Fruit Machine" is available to stream for free on the TVO website #URL#  and on… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Rigorously researched, exceptionally edited, and emotionally draining... There Are No Fakes might be one of the mo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thanks to the generosity of donors like you, there are lots of great documentaries to look forward to this year inc… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Interesting episode of #USER# Political Blind Date, #HASHTAG# City Councillors #USER# and #USER# explore different p…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode of TVO Podcast On Docs, actor and filmmaker Maryam Zaree joins host #USER# to discuss her… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: “Why does it have to be underground?” #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: People are already talking about episode four of #USER#, which is about The Food We Eat. February 11th on #USER# at 9pm.…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This 12-part series follows the dedicated crew at the Toronto Wildlife Centre as they help thousands of animals fin… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Caught this on #USER# last night and it wouldn't let me go. This is a fascinating documentary. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The TVO Original film "Coppers" by award-winning filmmaker #USER# is an honest, hard-hitting, and empathetic look… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: best.Episode.Ever. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On this week's #HASHTAG#, #USER# speaks with #USER# about the documentary that Nova Scotia-born actor… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["My goal is to bring you films and series that explore Ontario’s social, economic and political issues through a pe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On the next episode of TVO Original #HASHTAG#, Toronto Councillors #USER# and #USER# debate… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From multi-residential and laneway housing to rapid densification, councillors #USER# &amp; #USER# hold… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great to see TVO Original #USER# named as a contender on Vulture's list of Best Movies of the Decade. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["...it boils down to a fundamentally simple question: How are we going to make room for the tens of thousands of pe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: "When you hand it over to the community, what your staff learn, what the public service learns, is parks really do mean everything…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twenty-two years after fleeing an abusive relationship, filmmaker Attiya Khan meets with her ex-boyfriend to talk a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch a special Christmas Day marathon of "Victorian House of Arts and Crafts" tonight on TVO beginning at 7pm. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Catch a glimpse of the beautiful coasts of New Zealand! #HASHTAG# streaming now on TVO #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# with Ana Bailão and Stephen Holyday airs February 4 on #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We've hit the halfway point for Season 3 of #HASHTAG#! The first three episodes - City Budgets, Subways,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Explore the #USER#  interactive experience, "It Was Me" at #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TVO Original 'There Are No Fakes' is now streaming at #URL# and on the TVO Docs YouTube Channel. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: One of our most popular shows, #USER#, returns tonight at 9 pm. Let us wet your whistle with a preview at 8 pm of #USER#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did you know that, thanks to our donors, we’re able to finance 15 TVO Original documentaries and series every year?… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TVO Docs contribute to defining who we are as Ontarians and help us tell our story. TVO Original "Prey" is an unden… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Excellent documentary on the Belo Monte dam project in Brazil from #USER# : #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["As I watched this week’s episode of #URL#’s Political Blind Date, I couldn’t help asking myself:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On the last episode of On Docs for 2019, host #USER# talks to #USER# about Kastner's film… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The pressure is on the City of Toronto to move its millions of people, but what is the best and most realistic plan… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Ontario watches more documentaries on TVO than any other channel. Really. Pick ANY channel you can get, and when it comes t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: On the eve of #USER# #USER# premiere of #USER#, TBay police confirm investigation into fake #HASHTAG# pain…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Migrant Dreams can be streamed anytime on the #HASHTAG# YouTube channel: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: "There is a silent genocide happening in the Amazon right now. I hope this film opens a window for audiences to get a gli…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I've watched Ep 1 of this season and I think even seasoned TO city-watchers are gonna learn some stuff. (I don't know if I…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Traffic on the Nile builds, signaling #USER#' arrival into Luxor - the 'world's greatest open-air museum'.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Barenaked Ladies musician Kevin Hearn buys a painting by Norval Morrisseau, doubts about its authenticity rais… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Wouldn't miss it! On tonight's episode of Political Blind Date, see #HASHTAG# Chief #USER# and Councillor (&amp; fo…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: ICYMI: Get into the spirit of the new season of #USER# #USER# by catching up on Director, Writer and Executive P…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Also be sure to check out "KENK: The Interactive Graphic Novel" which expands the backstory of Igor Kenk. Tap to br… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[River Silence, the feature documentary from Brazilian-born, Toronto-based filmmaker Rogério Soares about the profou… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Done your dinner? For dessert, why not tune in and learn about the politics and policies that influence the food you ea…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nestled in the Charlevoix region of Quebec is gardener Frank Cabot's fabled Les Quatre Vents, one of the world's mo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# film COPPERS makes the Top 10 Canadian Films list #USER#. Congrats to filmmaker Alan Zweig #USER# for a c…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week on #USER#, #USER# spoke with #USER#, director of TVO Original #USER#, and Carmen… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomorrow on Political Blind Date, #USER# and #USER# explore one of the biggest issues threatening th… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Missed the broadcast? "The Gardner" is now streaming online at #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After making your donation, check out #USER# - now streaming on the #HASHTAG# YouTube! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coming in April, TVO Original "Tripping The Rideau Canal" is a 4-hour journey in real-time along the Rideau Canal.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Be smart, but not too smart.  Play sports, but not those sports. Follow your dreams, but not in that field.   Watch… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tonight #USER# premiers its third season on #USER#, featuring Toronto city councilors #USER# and #USER#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This week on #HASHTAG#, host #USER# speaks with Shawney Cohen and #USER# about Rat Park, their new Vice St… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In a new episode of #HASHTAG#, Conservative MPP #USER# and Ontario Green Party Leader… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I cannot wait for the third season of #USER# airing next week on #USER#! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tune in tonight at 9:00 PM! #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donations from people like you help us make award-winning films like the TVO original 17 And Life Doesn't Wait. Wit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Better Man is available to stream anytime on the TVO Docs YouTube or at #URL#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Funding cuts have forced the City of Toronto to make hard choices about its budget shortfall. #USER# believe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Great TV tonight watching #USER#’s Political Blind Date with my MPP #USER# and OMAFRA PA #USER# as they t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Looking forward to watching this tomorrow!  Councillor #USER# and I discuss transit needs in our communities.  Tun…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: After shocking audiences at #HASHTAG#, #USER# original doc #USER# returns to #USER# tonight at 6 PM, followed…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Apology can be streamed online at #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: From Etobicoke to Davenport, this episode hits close to home. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Here's a link to #HASHTAG# episode with Doug Ford and Jagmeet Singh from Season 1! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What can be done to make sure the farms that feed us survive and thrive? Conservative MPP #USER# and Onta… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: We're checking in on the race for best documentary feature at this year's #HASHTAG# with #USER#, TVO's executive produ…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ROMA held its annual conference this week, and one perennial complaint of Canadian cities was again on the agenda:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tonight, I hope you tune in to #USER# to watch my political blind date with #USER# at 9:00 PM. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# See the latest episode of TVO Original #USER# "The Food We Eat" with #USER# and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Indeed! Matter of fact when #USER# premieres on #USER# Feb 1 at 9pm EST, there will be some updates/amendmen…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This is the closest Toronto politics comes to an actual evidence-based argument for subways: the city is growing r… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Watch our panel on the #USER# original documentary #USER#, tonight at 8/11pm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tune in tonight for my #USER# with fellow Deputy Mayor #USER#. Join us at 9:00 pm on #USER#. #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amy Winehouse was a once in a generation musical talent, but her chaotic life stole headlines. Watch "Amy" tonight… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When it came into being, most residents wanted to call #HASHTAG# something else. But thanks to a quirk of democra… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscar®-winning set and costume designer, photographer, writer and painter Cecil Beaton was not only a dazzling chro… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Migrant Dreams" examines the lives of a group of strong, vibrant migrant women who resist systemic oppression and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["In the Season 3 premiere... Shelley Carroll and Gary Crawford meet as a progressive and a fiscal hawk debating civ… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: If you haven't seen #USER#'s documentary #USER#, you can stream from the #USER# link below. Fellow federal publi…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can private capital be the answer to complex social problems?  Watch TVO Original “The Invisible Heart” tonight at… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: If you care about docs, here's the super-savvy #USER# with the full lowdown on the 5 #HASHTAG# nominees, in conversation wit…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tune in tomorrow night at 9pm where #USER# talks revenue tools for big cities like Toronto with #USER# on #USER#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TVO Original #USER# airs tonight at 9pm on #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tune into #USER# with #USER# on SiriusXM channel 167 #URL# at 3:00pm today to hear her…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join On Docs host Colin Ellis live on January 20 at #USER#  as he chats with director Jamie Kastner followi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# tonight at 9pm #USER#. One of those stories that if it weren’t true, you’d never believe it. Available o…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Join us for a special screening of the #HASHTAG# "There Are No Fakes" at #USER# January 20th at 6pm. The… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Had a great time taking #USER# to visit some of my favourite small family farms in the #HASHTAG# area including…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TVO Original "Coppers" is one of #USER#'s top 10 Canadian films of 2019!   Read more at:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Catch a special New Year's Day marathon of The Nile: 5000 Years of History, hosted by Professor #USER#, beg… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Your Must-Watch this Weekend: TVO Original #USER# unravels a complex, stranger-than-fiction tale that leads to a lucrati…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: “Coppers” is such a powerful film from the #USER# team. I’m thrilled to see it on this list! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark your calendars! The third season of TVO Original Political Blind Date premieres Tuesday, January 21 at 9pm on… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Tomorrow night at 9pm! Who is tuning in?   #USER# #USER# #USER#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Hi Michelle, Here is a link to There Are No Fakes on YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: THERE ARE NO FAKES Review  #URL#   There Are No Fakes – screening this weekend on #USER# – is a haunting por…]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
