<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[World Cup a dream come true for Amir #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘You should be DISGUSTED!’ BBC QT audience member SAVAGES politicians over Brexit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hamza, Farhan lose in Philadelphia Squash Open pre-quarters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Cleese insists he is not a racist after saying London is 'not an English city any more' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[KP reports another polio case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["The President is using his bully pulpit to lie, to deflect and to distract, and to do it all out loud," says CNN's… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN's ChrisCuomo says the White House's request to hide the USS John McCain during the President's visit to Japan i… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leon Redbone death: Singer-songwriter and early musical guest on Saturday Night Live dies, aged 69 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Semenya?s absence overshadows Stockholm Diamond League #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Royal RIFT: ‘Animosity over Meghan, status and money’ saw Royal Family tensions soar #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["I think that Mueller needs to come in and testify, regardless of whether he's just going to say the same things he… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[West Indies playing with Hope ahead of Pakistan opener #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[R Kelly charged with 11 new sex abuse and assault counts involving one individual, reports say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mass puffin die-off linked to climate change, researchers say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zlatan inspires LA Galaxy to victory #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ramiz propels Eaton CC into KG Cricket semis #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[?Water coolers in Lahore parks should be fully operational? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[S Africa hold England to 311-8 in WC opener #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton assails President Trump in a commencement speech, calling for accountability over Russian interfere… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Skepta, Ignorance is Bliss review: The grime star has turned yet another corner #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Godzilla: King of the Monsters review – deeply confusing sequel is dismaying to watch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Virtues review, episode 3: Taut, tense and at times quite terrifying  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Potter author JK Rowling to release four new books next month #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Body constituted to probe KHA affairs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[?PHF forensic audit report expected near end-June? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Moby cancels 'all upcoming public appearances for foreseeable future' after Natalie Portman dating remarks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BBC Question Time audience member hits out at Brexit - 'The public didn't understand!' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Raptors fans fill Jurassic Park to watch Game 1 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Committee formed for amendments to constitution #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shah says he can qualify for Tokyo 2020 if supported #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Malik out of WC opener #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[City of Girls by Elizabeth Gilbert, review: A funny, bittersweet, moving coming-of-age story  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Skipper of cruiser that sank Budapest tour boat arrested #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump promise of new Mexican tariffs brings protests #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AO Clinic set up MA Shah Trophy final with Qasmi Gymkhana #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brexit Party MEP explains KEY fact MPs missed as she SHUTS DOWN pro-EU BBC QT panel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A New York school district plans to install facial recognition software in schools to boost security. But the state… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Irishman delayed because 'young' Robert De Niro doesn't look threatening enough after CGI #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["42 minutes and 3 seconds later, the simple acknowledgment of a simple fact was swirling down the memory hole."  On… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Westminster CHAOS: Brexit Party SURGES AHEAD of Tories in shock general election poll #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glastonbury 2019 timetable: Full line-up, stage times and clashes announced #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We tell our kids that hard work always pays off. What happens when they fail anyway? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Starry Messenger, Wyndham's Theatre, review: Matthew Broderick excels in Kenneth Lonergan's play #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ontario First Nation declares state of emergency due to wildfire #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A woman has been arrested after her 1-year-old son died from acute exposure to fentanyl and heroin, among other dru… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Friends of the late Anthony Bourdain have declared June 25 "Bourdain Day" to celebrate and remember the legendary c… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A judge has ordered a Nantucket bar to produce surveillance video from the night of an alleged groping incident inv… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Golf training programme for Mashal kids launched #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry’s OUTRAGE at royal reporter for 'five virgins' headline – 'Watch yourself' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sacha Baron Cohen says Pamela Anderson's 'kidnap' scene in Borat caused Baywatch star's divorce #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fishing brown bear picture among winners of nature photography contest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SNL star Kate McKinnon tricks public into thinking she's Reese Witherspoon in Big Little Lies-themed Billy on the S… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney threatens to stop producing films in Georgia in protest at abortion laws #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kimberly Guilfoyle, senior Trump 2020 campaign official, on new tariffs threat on Mexico: "Tariffs work and he's em… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Ma' review: Octavia Spencer's on unsettling form in enjoyably creepy horror  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigel Farage issues BOLD promise on action he will take if UK doesn't LEAVE on October 31 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mohammad Amir fit for WC debut, says Sarfraz #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A lesbian couple in South Carolina is challenging the state's practice of letting taxpayer-funded foster care agenc… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ottoman Secret by Raymond Khoury review: A dystopian thriller that wears its smartness on its sleeve  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feds' firearms focus on guns 'designed to hunt people' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patti Smith interview: 'Mozart was a punk rocker' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Graduation speeches are supposed to leave students full of hope and awe for the future. But this speech left one st… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Queen’s lady-in-waiting SCOLDS garden party guest for BREAKING royal protocol #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EU panic: Barnier's Brexit team ‘TERRIFIED’ of Verhofstadt ‘causing TROUBLE’ - shock video #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Normal People: Sally Rooney's hit novel being made into TV show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 92nd Scripps National Spelling Bee had an epic ending -- with eight co-champions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mashrafe to play WC opener despite injury #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rosanna Arquette interview: 'If I went after every guy that pinched my ass, it would be ridiculous' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[37 best film twists of all time, explained: From The Prestige to Psycho #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 people are dead and 21 missing after a sightseeing boat capsized in Hungary #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Philippines ships 69 containers of garbage back to Canada #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LaCroix made sparkling water cool. But with fierce competition from Coca-Cola, Pepsi, and Costco, sales have dipped… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[37 actors who almost died on set, from Charlize Theron and George Clooney #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How 'Rocketman' recreated Elton John's remarkable wardrobe #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From village cricket to WC for Shadab #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Festival T20 match at NSK #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Children without measles vaccine shouldn’t be allowed in schools: N.B. education minister #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Her deported dad couldn't attend graduation. So she wore her cap and gown to meet him on a border bridge.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tonys 2019: When are they, who is hosting, and how to watch the ceremony #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pakistan vs West Indies: Low on confidence, Pakistan look to make winning World Cup start #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saeed to head PHF constitution committee #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[German Chancellor Angela Merkel urged Harvard graduates to "tear down walls of ignorance and narrow-mindedness" in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Osaka, Thiem battle through at Roland Garros #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[San Francisco Ballet, Sadler's Wells, review: Sunny, athletic and assured #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what the Alberta wildfires look like from space #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sinkane – Dépaysé, album review: Most poppy and psychedelic work to date #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Osaka survives as Djokovic and Serena stroll #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pascal Siakam has 32 points in Raptors' historic NBA Finals win over Warriors #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Research shows that frozen fruits and vegetables can have just as many vitamins -- and sometimes more -- as compare… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pakistan seek Champions Trophy inspiration against West Indies today #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stokes stars as England thrash South Africa #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The new live-action Aladdin seeks to break Hollywood stereotypes, with mixed results #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This time, it was an accident.  That's what Air Force officials said after yet another drawing resembling male geni… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louisiana lawmakers passed a bill barring abortions once there is a detectable fetal heartbeat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wie blasts ?racist? comments from golf coach Haney #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Sometimes people are surprised because I was born in India,” says Sen. Michael Bennet of Colorado. Before his… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England thrash S Africa in World Cup opener #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A NOAA research vessel on a 13-day mission to test its equipment unexpectedly discovered a mid-1800s shipwreck in t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bashir, Khalil fail to reach Munich World Cup finals #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liverpool boss Jürgen Klopp says Brexiteers ‘MISUNDERSTOOD' 2016 vote in anti-Brexit rant #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
