<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Igbo Teacher Praised By Borno Governor Promoted To Assistant Headmistress After Visiting A School And Found Only He… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shaq vows to make life change after Kobe Bryant’s death #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eucharia Anunobi recounts how a hotel cleaner at a church camp allegedly used a toilet brush to wash glass cups… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Buhari is the number one person who gives hate speech in the country – Aisha Yesufu… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CBS responds to Gayle King’s outrage over viral Kobe clip #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : RCCG/CAN Protest Timi Frank commends Pastor Adeboye, says Buhari will answer for his actions at ICC… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid truth of Patrick Mahomes #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Polities Trump’s $4.8 Trillion Budget Plan Includes Cuts To Farm Subsidies, Food Stamps And Medicaid… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Anita Joseph’s fiance, MC Fish grabs her boobs in new video #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chilling 911 calls from Kobe Bryant’s helicopter crash released #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Southeast security network We have written FG – Governors Forum #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The insane transformation of Chanel West Coast #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid truth about Jennifer Lopez #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : EFCC reacts to trending photo of ‘Port Harcourt cell’, releases image #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant’s body has been returned to his family #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Full Video S3x of Lady who sleeps with her friend’s father for sleeping with her boyfriend #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alan Walker, K-391 &amp; Emelie Hollow – Lily download #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Bryant opens up about losing Kobe &amp; GiGi This is Painfull #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Koshoni, ex-Chief of Naval Staff is dead #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The real meaning behind Billie Eilish’s Bad Guy lyrics That’s cool #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez has a message for her Super Bowl Halftime critics she doesn’t care. #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Femi Fani-Kayode exposes real identity, religion of Living Faith suspected bomber in Kaduna… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How much dose Tom Hanks worth? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did these musicians sell their souls for a paycheck? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Campaign Spent $1.8 Million On Trump’s Own Businesses, Records Reveal #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Senate adjourns plenary to mourn Senator Ignatius Longjan #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best and worst Super Bowl LIV commercials you either love them or hate them #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Botched Bachelor bikini editing job sparks huge outrage #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : APGA warns Senator Orji, Abia speaker to resign over alleged N150m fraud investigation… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Dickson’s appointees storm Bayelsa Govt house over unpaid workers salaries #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fact concerning Joaquin Phoenix metro and Rooney Mara’s connection #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rita Dominic looks beautiful and stylish in this monochrome ensemble (photos) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eminem brings the house down with surprise Oscars performance #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Kwara State Police Command has launch manhunt for masterminds of ATM vandalization in Ilorin… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nnamdi Kanu Said, I Wonder Why A Right-thinking Govt. Will Deploy Battalion To My Home Town #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bobbi Kristina’s ex lover cause of death has actually been disclosed #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Omashola Reveals The Package He Received From Tacha (Watch Video) 2020 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inexpensive Effective Marketing Tools With for Small Business #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez net worth: how much dose she own #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Publisher of Cross River Watch journalist, Jalingo appears before new judge for fresh plea… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : The Academic Staff Union of Universities threatens Kano University management over alleged financial… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Federal Ministry Ogoni $1bn project: Magnus Abe warns Nigerian govt, HYPREP #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how really big is Nina Dobrev house and Where does she live #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Guetta – Titanium ft. Sia Free Mp3 download #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update: Body of UNIZIK staff, Engr. Emeka Chiaghana found buried in shallow grave three months after he was abducte… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders Walks Back Promise To Release ‘Comprehensive’ Medical Records #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lizzo dons a tiny black thong swimsuit and bares her bum as she twerks in Miami #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wedding Diaries: Shweta’s One Caption Form Dad Amitabh Bachchan Says It All #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Lai Mohammed condoles with Lawan, Okorocha over Senator Ignatius Longjan’s death… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Does Saoirse Ronan have a boyfriend? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Stop The Threat, We Obeyed Supreme Court On Bayelsa Like We Did On Imo’ – INEC tells Oshiomhole… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Coronavirus I don’t want to die – Amaechi #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid truth of Shakira’s ‘husband’ Gerard Pique #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Emergency Agency warns Abuja residents of imminent flood, provides toll free number… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lady Gets Dumped By Her Boyfriend After Seeing The ‘Okro Soup’ She Cooked For His Family #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus death toll rises to 427 with more than 20,000 people worldwide infected by the flu-like virus… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid truth about Joe Pesci’s criminal ex-wife Claudia Haro #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump wins the Republican Iowa caucus by 97.1%, showing Republicans are united in their choice for 2020 pres… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Market Research with Low Budget for Small Business Owners #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Boko Haram No true Muslim kills for God – Arewa Forum #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Davido First Babymama Shade Him, After He Shared New Photos Of Chioma And Their Son #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What happened to Sassy after she left Black Ink Crew #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid truth about Kate Middleton’s shady uncle #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump Blasts Jury Member, Justice Department Over Roger Stone Trial #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US news : Shots fired at Trump’s Mar-a-Lago resort in Florida #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Did these athletes sell their souls for a paycheck? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Papa John admits what we suspected all along that its true #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With Impeachment Over, Critics See Trump ‘Retribution Tour’ He is Happy Now #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Biafra Igbo group Tells Nnamdi Kanu not to attend parents’ burial #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The reason why Luke Perry was left out of the Oscars ‘In Memoriam’ tribute #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abacha’s $308 million loot to return to Nigeria as FG and US sign agreement, what will they use the money for, stor… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Fayose asked to explain whereabouts of N400m meant for reconstruction Ado-Akure road… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sia – Cheap Thrills ft. Sean Paul free mp3 download #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where does Jennifer Lopez live and how big is her house? bigger and bigger #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Toby Okechukwu has urged President Muhammadu Buhari to quickly address the security challenges facin… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What was Kirk Douglas’ net worth at his time of death? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Moment Late Kobe Bryant Daughter, Gianna’s Jersey Gets Retired full video #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We Hope Hicks Return To White House As Senior Adviser #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Ganduje vs Emir Sanusi: Northern Elders decry President Buhari’s refusal to reconcile Kano sons… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shakira – who boasts a net worth of $300 millio, Who won the battle of the 2020 Super Bowl halftime stage?… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The truth about Adam Sandler and Jennifer Aniston’s relationship #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid words of Chicken Girls #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Presley Gerber responds to backlash over face tattoo #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chelsea Stars Tammy Abraham And Fikayo Tomori Pictured Hanging Out With Davido In Dubai (Photos Below)… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[viral video As A Beautiful Girl Proposes To Her Boyfriend In School And He Accepts #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Singer Paul Okoye calls out the Nigerian Copyright Commission, accuses them of ‘kidnap’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Polities Impeachment Trial Rigger For Donald Trump is Mitch McConnell’s New Legacy #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The real reason this Southern Charm star was spotted working at Costco wow #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The reason Princess Beatrice’s wedding will be so different #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rose McGowan slams Natalie Portman’s ‘offensive’ Oscars dress #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : 2020 UTME No extension after Jan 17 as JAMB records highest registration ever #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Polities Highly Anticipated Iowa Caucuses Poll Shelved Over Possible Errors #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Insecurity Nothing wrong in asking President to resign – El-Rufai to Jonathan in 2012… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The truth about Florence Pugh’s relationship with Zach Braff criticism #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsaid truth about Beyonce #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Customs seizes 256 bags of contraband rice concealed as beans #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Boko Haram Christian corps member abducted alongside freed Winners Pastor refuses freedom… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Coronavirus WHO counters use of garlic, salt, in preventing infection #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The solution, Lagos State Government Rolls 65 New Buses After Okada And Keke Ban #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigeria news : Jonathan’s ex-aide, Okupe, 2023 No difference between PDP, APC in terms of corruption, greed… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
