<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Oscars Star 'Gary From Chicago' Gets Candid About Troubled Past: 'I'm a Changed Man' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ladies of 'The Talk' Turn Back Time by Channeling Some of Cher's Classic Looks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscars 2017: Dwayne ‘The Rock’ Johnson Almost Took Envelopegate Into His Own Hands #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britney Spears Wears Skimpy Shorts and Sports Bra for Intense Workout: Watch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sandra Bullock and Bryan Randall Have Talked About Throwing a ‘Secret Wedding’: Details #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian’s Ex James Harden: ‘I Didn’t Like all the Attention’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katie Holmes: I Want to Give Suri a ‘Stable, Innocent Childhood’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Maksim and Val Chmerkovskiy Jokingly Reveal Their Plans to 'Use' Baby Shai for 'DWTS' Votes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zendaya's Dog Has a Better Life Than Us: Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Upton FaceTimes With Her Dog Harley: See the Funny Pic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tyrese Is Married! Actor Reveals He Quietly Wed on Valentine’s Day — Watch the Sweet Video #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Janet Jackson’s Brothers Tito and Jackie Say Her Son Eissa Is ‘Beautiful’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Study Claims Subway’s Oven-Roasted Chicken Is Only 50 Percent Chicken, According to DNA Test #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Gets Tattoo Honoring Her Late Father Removed as Sister Kim Mocks Her: Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey Considers ‘Possibility’ of Running for President After Donald Trump’s Win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Harden: I Didn't Like 'All the Attention' That Came With Dating Khloe Kardashian #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elementary School Science Teacher Proposes to Math Teacher During Class: Watch Their Fifth Grade Students Go Crazy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Adorable Tilda Swinton Look-Alike Dog Ended Up in the Oscars ‘Mean Tweets’ Segment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Widow of Slain Navy SEAL Receives Extended Standing Ovation During President Trump's Speech to Congress #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orlando Bloom Cuddled With Katy Perry's Dog One Day Before Split News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys Imitates Gwen Stefani, Adele on 'Wheel of Musical Impressions' Sketch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry, Meghan Markle Will ‘Be Engaged by the End of Summer,’ Says Pal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adam Levine Calls Blake Shelton and Gwen Stefani's 'Voice' Arguments Like a Sportscaster -- Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: 'The Flash's Grant Gustin Spills on Barry and Iris' Big Romantic Milestone: 'It's Really Sweet!' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carrie Fisher's Dog Gary Turns 5: See the Cute Photo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: David Cassidy Reveals Greatest Fear About His Dementia Struggle on 'Dr. Phil' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Battle of the Leopard Print Coats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: 'Jane the Virgin's' Justin Baldoni Turns on the Flirtatious Charm on 'Madam Secretary' -- Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: 'Criminal Minds' First Look! Garcia Finds a Thoughtful Way to Cope With Reid's Imprisonment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casey Affleck Breaks Silence on Sexual Harassment Allegations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince William Pitches a Tent While Blindfolded With the Help of School Children: Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katy Perry and Orlando Bloom Are Taking a Break From Their Relationship #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rihanna Delivers Inspiring Speech About Giving Back as She Accepts Harvard University's Humanitarian Award #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: 'Bachelor' Nick Viall Reveals His Next Big Move (and It's Different Than 'Dancing With the Stars') #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Backstreet Boys Talk Fatherhood and Seeing Nick Carter as a Dad: 'It's Trippy!' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mel Gibson, Adrien Brody, French Montana and More Partied Together Before the 2017 Oscars #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sienna Miller Says She and Ex-Fiance Tom Sturridge 'Still Love Each Other' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gigi Hadid Pays Tribute to Palestinian Roots in First Ever 'Vogue Arabia' Cover: 'It Means the World to Me' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Adorable Golden Retriever Can't Stop Hugging Her Owner's Legs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surprise! Tyrese Reveals He Got Married on Valentine's Day With Sweet Video #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys Serenades a 'Voice' Hopeful -- Is This the Coaches' Favorite Contestant Yet? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Donald Trump's Speech to Congress: Watch the Livestream #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Bachelor' Dolphin Trainer Alexis Waters Says She's Going to 'Paradise'…And Wants to Date Chad Johnson! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shirley MacLaine Is Still ‘Processing the Horror’ of Younger Brother Warren Beatty’s Oscar Mix-Up #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gwen Stefani Snapchats Son Apollo's Adorable 3rd Birthday Celebration at School -- Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casey Affleck Addresses Sexual Harassment Allegations After Best Actor Oscars 2017 Win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Moonlight' Star Mahershala Ali Used to Be a Rapper! Listen to His Songs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biggest Celebrity Breakups of 2017 -- So Far! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orlando Bloom and Katy Perry 'Taking Respectful, Loving Space' After One Year of Dating #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga Will Reportedly Replace Beyonce at Coachella #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Corinne Olympios on Whether She Was Drunk on 'The Bachelor' -- Plus, Would She Do 'Paradise'? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kristen Stewart Compliments Karl Lagerfeld: ‘He Is Who He Is for a Reason’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: The Contestants Struggle to Get Into Character on 'America's Next Top Model' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Savannah Chrisley Throwing Shade at Bella Thorne Over Chandler Parsons? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian's Exes Lamar Odom and French Montana Grab Dinner Together #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt Reaches Out to Jennifer Aniston Amid His Split From Angelina Jolie #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt Rocks Silver Fox Hair in First Trailer for Netflix's 'War Machine': Watch! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Throwback Tom Brady Pic Is Just Too Much #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Transparent’ Star Amy Landecker 'Devastated' Donald Trump Revoked Transgender Students’ Bathroom Rights #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Alice is Haunting Quentin in This 'Magicians' Sneak Peek, Plus Olivia Taylor Dudley Teases What's to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Accountants Resposible for Best Picture Flub Will Not Work Oscars Again, Academy Says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift’s Cutest Moments With Her Cats Meredith and Olivia: Watch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sarah Silverman Explains Why She Chose Her Career Over Motherhood: 'You Can't Be a Woman Without Sacrifice' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ashley Tisdale Slams Body Shamers After Oscars Party Appearance: 'I'm Not Pregnant, I'm Happy' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Emma Watson Give Sweet Romance Advice to Strangers in New York City #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katie Holmes Reveals How She's Giving Suri Cruise a 'Stable, Innocent Childhood' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Admits She Wasn't 'Ready' to be With Boyfriend Mac Miller When She First Met Him #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Larry Birkhead Blocks Daughter Dannielynn From Reading About Anna Nicole Smith: ‘It’s Getting a Little Tough’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's What Justin Bieber Wants for His 23rd Birthday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PDA Alert! Celebrity Couples Who Can't Keep Their Hands Off Each Other #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casey Affleck Addresses Sexual Assault Allegations After Best Actor Oscars 2017 Win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: 'How to Be a Latin Lover' Stars Salma Hayek and Eugenio Derbez on the Worst Pick-Up Lines Ever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Dancing With the Stars' Season 24 Cast Announced -- See Who Will Be Vying for the Mirror Ball Trophy! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kourtney Kardashian's Daughter Penelope Rocks a Lip Ring From Aunt Kim For the Oscars! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway: Reactions to Oval Office Couch Pic Were 'Vicious' and 'Venomous' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zayn Malik Supports Girlfriend Gigi Hadid in Matching Hilfiger Gear During Paris Fashion Week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Mellencamp: My Ex Meg Ryan 'Hates Me to Death' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lopez Helps Her Backup Dancers Get Engaged Mid-Concert -- See the Sweet Video #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Dancing With the Stars' Season 24 -- See the Official Cast Photos! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Meet the New 'Flip or Flop' Pairs Getting Their Own Spinoffs! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kendall Jenner, Andrew Garfield, and Taylor Lautner Have Impressive Hidden Talents: Watch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande on Boyfriend Mac Miller: I’ve ‘Loved and Adored’ Him Since I Was 19 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chris Pratt Surprises Jimmy Kimmel's Audience, Debuts 'Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2' Trailer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rachel Dolezal, Former NAACP Leader Who Claimed to Be Black, Says She May Soon Be Homeless #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Reveals She Works Out in Her Garage, Impresses Sisters Khloe and Kourtney With Her Jump Rope Skills #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stephen Colbert Savagely Mocks Donald Trump's Congress Address for 12 Minutes Straight #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ricki Lake Says Her Ex-Husband Christian Evans Died by Suicide: ‘I Wanted to Save Him’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscar Show-Stealer 'Gary From Chicago' Got Out of Prison Just 3 Days Before Academy Awards, Served 20 Years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Faith Hill and Tim McGraw Rock Sleek Matching Ensembles at Film Premiere: Pics! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Beauty and the Beast' Will Feature a Gay Character in Disney's Live-Action Remake #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lala Kent Is Returning to ‘Vanderpump Rules’ — but There’s a Catch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt and Jennifer Aniston 'Have Been in Touch': 'They're Friends' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Catherine Zeta-Jones Says Her Kids Want to Go Into Showbiz, Reveals Her Own Personal Oscar Record #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey Ponders Running for President in Wake of Donald Trump's Win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Which Celebrity Pet Is Your Perfect Match? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lance Bass' Foster Puppies Nurse Him Back to Health After Emergency Appendectomy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rob Lowe Shares Touching Memories of His 'Closest Friend' Bill Paxton: 'There Will Be No Replacement' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sofia Richie Snapchats From the Hospital After Severe Food Poisoning: 'I Feel Like I'm in a Horror Movie' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democratic Women Wore White to President Donald Trump's Congress Address: Find Out Why #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Janet Jackson's Brother Jackie Dishes on Her 'Beautiful' New Son Eissa #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
