<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Good Girls Stars Tease Season 2's "Sexy Twists" and Surprising Revelations Who doesn't love "sexy twists"? That's w… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande and Ex-Boyfriend Big Sean Reunite 4 Years After Split Thank u, next? Not so fast! Ariana Grande raise… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Jordyn Woods Told Khloe Kardashian and Kylie Jenner After Cheating Scandal Jordyn Woods is opening up about he… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Haley Struggles to Master Baby Basics in Modern Family Directed By Julie Bowen Modern Family's Julie Bowen has a ne… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Danielle Staub Postpones Wedding to Oliver Maier Days After Announcing Engagement Danielle Staub's upcoming nuptial… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do It for the 'Gram! The LADYGANG Gals Prove You Can Take Envy-Inducing Social Media Snaps Anywhere The LADYGANG ga… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Fans Think Taylor Swift and Katy Perry Are Collaborating Are Taylor Swift and Katy Perry teaming up for a new s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Riverdale's Luke Perry Hospitalized After Stroke Luke Perry was hospitalized in Los Angeles on Wednesday after suff… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Denies She's Exploiting the LGBTQ Community By Performing at Manchester Pride Ariana Grande is addres… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 100 Star Bob Morley Addresses "Fat Shame" on Social Media, Opens Up About Depression The 100's Bob Morley has a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amanda Bynes Checks Into Mental Health Facility After Relapse Amanda Bynes is getting help. The 32-year-old actress… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordyn Woods Breaks Silence on Tristan Thompson Cheating Scandal Jordyn Woods is breaking her silence amid cheating… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Reveals the Songs That Helped Her Heal After "Bad Breakups" Never underestimate the power of music. It… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Comes Love, Then Comes Marriage? Inside the Future of Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez's Red-Hot Romance Jen… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons' Dan Reynolds Reveals How Hateful Criticism Contributed to His Depression Dan Reynolds isn't biting… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wynonna Earp Fans Rally to Save Show With Billboard in Times Square Fans of the hit Syfy series Wynonna Earp have b… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Accuses Jordyn Woods of Lying About Tristan Thompson Cheating Scandal Khloe Kardashian is not buyi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zayn Malik Confuses Fans With Gigi Hadid Love Tweet What's going on between Zayn Malik and Gigi Hadid? The on-again… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Won't Believe How Much Money Property Brothers' Drew and Jonathan Scott Made Last Year Drew Scott and Jonathan… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teresa Giudice Tackles Affair Allusions, Joe Giudice Deportation on The Real Housewives of New Jersey Reunion Teres… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Kinney Likes a Shady Comment About Lady Gaga on Instagram For some Hollywood shade, look no further than Tay… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the First Minute of Pretty Little Liars: The Perfectionists Get ready to have a cello cover of "Bad Romance"… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Reveals the Songs That Helped Her Heal After "Bad Breakups" Never underestimate the power of music. It… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You'll Never Guess Kate Middleton and Prince William's Nickname for Princess Charlotte Princess Charlotte's nicknam… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Says Tristan Thompson to Blame for Breakup, Not Jordyn Woods Khloe Kardashian has had a change of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why the Jonas Brothers Needed to Break Up to Come Back Stronger--and Closer--Than Ever We're a sucker for a reunion… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bekah Martinez Shares Photo of "Beautiful Little Girl" One Month After Giving Birth Bekah Martinez is giving everyo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Affleck and Lindsay Shookus Step Out for a Stroll in NYC Ben Affleck and Lindsay Shookus were recently spotted… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Maddie Poppe and Caleb Lee Hutchinson Are Hitting All the Right Notes After American Idol Nearly one year later… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[George H.W. Bush's Service Dog Sully Begins New Role at Military Hospital 3 Months After President's Death George H… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Beauty Supplement Is the Reason People Can't Stop Complimenting Our Skin Around here we're always on the hunt… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Courteney Cox Recreates Classic Friends Scene in Real Life Could this be any cuter? Sometimes life imitates fiction… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers Reunite for First Song 5 Years After Split: Watch Them Perform "Sucker" The rumors are true: The Jon… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DJ Khaled to Host 2019 Nickelodeon Kids' Choice Awards: See the Complete List of Nominations The 2019 Nickelodeon K… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pete Davidson Kicks Out Show Heckler Over Mac Miller Mention When a fan crosses the line, Pete Davidson doesn't pla… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kristin Cavallari Tested Jay Cutler's Knowledge of Her Company &amp; It Went Just as Hilarious as You'd Think Jay Culte… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Priyanka Chopra Became One of India's Leading Female "Trailblazers" Aside from Miss World 2000, movie and TV st… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Something That Happened: The History of Bradley Cooper and Jennifer Esposito's Shockingly Short Marriage "Ha" That'… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Real Housewives of Atlanta's Peter Thomas Arrested for Alleged Check Fraud Former Real Housewives of Atlanta star P… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[90 Day Fiancé Star Larissa Dos Santos Lima Reveals Her Boyfriend's Identity 90 Day Fiancé star Larissa Dos Santos L… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Have to See Nicki Minaj's $450,000 Rolls-Royce Nicki Minaj is the proud owner of a new Rolls-Royce, worth an es… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grey's Anatomy Cast Tells All: Who's the Funniest? Who Cries the Easiest? Who Gets the Crankiest? The cast of Grey'… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pink Shares Sweet Photo with Kids at First Show of New Tour Pink spent time with her two cutest fans before taking… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Justin Bieber Celebrated His 25th Birthday It seems like a big group of people came down with a bad case of Bie… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here Are the Frontrunners to Be the Next Bachelorette: Inside the Decision-Making Process "A decision has not been… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Selma Blair's Multiple Sclerosis Diagnosis Helped Her Find "Humility and Joy" In October, Selma Blair announced… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See What Tyler Henry Really Thinks About His Khloe Kardashian, Tristan Thompson &amp; Jordyn Woods Prediction Did Tyler… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Travis Scott Take an Adorable Phone Call From Kylie Jenner on Carpool Karaoke Kylie Jenner makes a small came… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 Things to Know About Playboy's 2019 Playmate of the Year Jordan Emanuel Playboy is revealing the lucky girl who w… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katherine Helmond Dead: Who's the Boss? and Soap Star Was 89 Katherine Helmond, who starred on the sitcoms Soap and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons' Dan Reynolds Reveals How Hateful Criticism Contributed to His Depression Dan Reynolds isn't biting… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Botched Doctors Have Heartbreaking News for One Famous Patient Paul Nassif and Terry Dubrow made back-to-back s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pink Shares Sweet Photo with Kids at First Show of New Tour Pink spent time with her two cutest fans before taking… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bachelor Nation's Jade Roper and Tanner Tolbert Reveal Her Past Miscarriage Bachelor in Paradise's Jade Roper Tolbe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Sends Heartfelt Message to Her Fans: You Saved My Life Ariana Grande is sending some love to her loya… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Do the Kids of the Grey's Anatomy Cast Think of Their Parents' Success? What's it like to have a parent on one… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran Reportedly Marries Cherry Seaborn in a Secret Winter Wedding Ceremony Love is in the air for Ed Sheeran… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Miley Cyrus Infiltrate the RuPaul's Drag Race Work Room Miley Cyrus is living the life on RuPaul's Drag Race.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zachary Quinto and Miles McMillan Break Up After Almost 6 Years Together Zachary Quinto and Miles McMillan are no m… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Maddie Poppe and Caleb Lee Hutchinson Are Hitting All the Right Notes After American Idol Nearly one year later… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Jenni "JWoww" Farley's Impossibly Tough Year Last year on Feb. 27, Jenni "JWoww" Farley awoke to an Instagra… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Jude Law Engaged? Girlfriend Phillipa Coan Sparks Rumors With Diamond Ring Will Jude Law be off the market soon?… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle's Half-Sister Samantha Markle Slams Her in New Documentary Meghan Markle "doesn't have a heart" and i… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the Kardashians Really Think of Jordyn Woods' Red Table Talk Interview Now that Jordyn Woods has spoken, what… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brie Larson Is Our Fashion Hero! See Her Best Looks Before Becoming Captain Marvel Not all heroes wear capes on the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael J. Fox Opens Up About Health Scares Amid Parkinson's Disease Battle It has been more than 20 years since Mi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Christina Perri Reveals She "Almost" Relapsed in Candid Message About Her "Hardest" Year Yet Christina Perri has be… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's Pauly D Like You've Never Seen Him Before: Performing Ballet Game of Clones, the latest crazy concept reality… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 of the Biggest Bombshells From Jordyn Woods' Red Table Talk Interview Jordyn Woods has opened up about the cheati… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel, Madea, Dumbo &amp; More: Which March Blockbuster Are You Going to See in Theaters First? February has c… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Files $50 Million Lawsuit Against Amber Heard Johnny Depp is taking Amber Heard to court over her alleg… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[90 Day Fiancé's Colt Johnson Has a Divorce Party at Strip Club After Larissa Split 90 Day Fiancé's Colt Johnson is… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Shows Her Sporty Side During Belfast Visit With Prince William Kate Middleton and Prince William kic… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fyre Festival's Andy King Spills New Details on That Infamous Oral Sex Scenario Did anyone expect Andy King to be t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Mayer Reveals the Intimate Thing He Must Do Every Day John Mayer is getting personal with Ellen DeGeneres. The… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Noah Centineo Was Finally on Good Trouble and Oh Boy Oh how we have missed you, Jesus. Noah Centineo made his Good… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Says She Had ''One of the Best Days of Her life'' With Long Island Medium's Theresa Caputo Kim Karda… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will Gendry Take the Throne? Game of Thrones Star Joe Dempsie on Those Fan Theories... Move over Jon Snow and Daene… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers Reunite for First Song 5 Years After Split: Watch Them Perform "Sucker" The rumors are true: The Jon… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers Have Secret Concert Days After Releasing New Song The Jonas Brothers are just burnin' up with ex… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bachelor's Whitney Bischoff And Husband Ricky Angel Expecting First Child Together Former Bachelor star Whitney… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Married at First Sight's Danielle and Bobby Welcome Baby Girl And baby makes three! Married at First Sight stars Da… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Claims Amber Heart Cheated on Him With Elon Musk Johnny Depp is accusing ex-wife Amber Heard of "spendi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Royal Bartender! Kate Middleton Pours a Pint of Beer in Ireland Anyone up for a royal pint? Duchess of Cambridge Ka… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hailey Baldwin Sends Her ''Lover'' Justin Bieber a Sweet Message on His 25th Birthday Hailey Baldwin has a special… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matthew McConaughey's 3 Stylish Kids Make a Rare Red Carpet Appearance Alright, alright, alright--it's the McConaug… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Won The Masked Singer? Well now we know what happens when someone wins The Masked Singer! Tonight's two-hour fi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medium Tyler Henry Responds to John Oliver's Recent Criticism of Hollywood Psychics Tyler Henry isn't fazed by skep… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Esposito Sounds Off on the Bradley Cooper "Ha" Comments Jennifer Esposito is clarifying what she meant whe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Travis Scott Deletes Instagram Account After Denying He Cheated on Kylie Jenner Travis Scott has deleted his Instag… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cardi B Channels Her Inner Cowgirl in Sexy Pink Outfit Yeehaw! Cardi B took a fashion turn to the Southwest over th… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones Final Season Posters Revealed: Who Takes the Throne? The final season of Game of Thrones is upon us… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Will Be Honored at the 2019 iHeartRadio Music Awards Taylor Swift continues to cement her reputation a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sophie Turner and Jessica Chastain Harness Their Superpowers Dark Phoenix Trailer Sophie Turner is looking for answ… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordyn Woods' New World: How Her Entire Life Changed in an Instant Two weeks ago Jordyn Woods was a name familiar t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus and Liam Hemsworth Cuddle Up on the Red Carpet The look of love! Newlyweds Liam Hemsworth and Miley Cyr… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Nikki Bella's Romantic Date Night With Dancing With the Stars' Artem Chignvintsev Things are going strong be… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's Going on With The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills and a Dog Named Lucy? As her new tagline indicated, it se… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brie Larson Meeting a Mini Captain Marvel Will Make Your Day Mini Me, is that you? Brie Larson chatted with a young… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Sends Heartfelt Message to Her Fans: You Saved My Life Ariana Grande is sending some love to her loya… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
