<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest iOS 13.3.1 Beta Includes Toggle for Disabling U1 Ultra Wideband Chip #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LastPass to Drop Support for Native Mac App and Replace it With Universal Web App #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Avelina Lésper: Critic apologises for shattering artwork at Mexico fair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt calls out Congress and impeachment hearings in Oscar speech #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When a homeless couple moved in with a millionaire #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tekashi 6ix9ine Plans to Leave NYC After Prison with Top-Notch Security #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's The Big Frigin' Difference? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYPD Abandons Paper Memo Books for New iPhone App #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EU Lawmakers Vote Overwhelmingly in Favor of Common Charging Standard, Despite Apple's Protestations [Updated] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Should schools be allowed to ban slang words like 'peng'? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super Bowl 2020 Sign Language Artist Condemns Fox for Excluding Her Performance On Air #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyonce and Blue Ivy Wearing Adidas x Ivy Park Gear #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), February 07 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ecuador president says women 'only report harassment from ugly men' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook apologetic after a 'technical issue' calls China's leader 'Mr. Shithole' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Madoff Says He's Dying and Deserves Release from Prison #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys &amp; Boyz II Men sing touching tribute to Kobe Bryant at Grammys #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best VPN for Netflix in 2020: Deals and how to watch American Netflix in the UK #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Washington State’s Department of Transportation Tweets That It Maybe, Just Maybe, Found Bigfoot. ‘We Will Leave Tha… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fake 'kitchen hacks' with billions of views #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), January 17 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grab a futuristic Tempur-Pedic mattress on sale for Presidents Day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zsa Zsa Gabor's Husband Says Bernie Madoff Should Rot in Prison #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), January 21 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deals: Low Prices Hit 13-Inch and 16-Inch MacBook Pro (Up to $300 Off) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon cancels its Mobile World Congress plan over coronavirus fears #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samsung's new foldable phone already sounds way better than the Galaxy Fold #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), January 15 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[L.A. Politicians Officially Demand MLB Turn Over WS Titles To Dodgers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Porto footballer quits match over racist abuse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kristin Chenoweth Scared Of Deadly Coronavirus, Traveling With Mask #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best hookup apps and online dating sites to help you get it on #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best dating sites to find a connection by this weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mama June Not Making Money Off New Reality Show 'From Not To Hot' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Reportedly Working on 'AirPod Pro Lite' Earphones #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus forces Huawei to postpone developer conference #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Australia weather: How much rain did it take to put out NSW fires? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Safeguard your online privacy with PureVPN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Protesters take their '.org' sale criticism offline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Valentine's Day gifts your husband wants — but would never buy for himself #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Excitement for 'Mulan' builds in sneak peak for upcoming trailer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 inspirational 'Harry Potter' quotes to live by #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the camp became centre of Nazi Holocaust #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 04:30 (JST), January 27 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shanina Shaik's Divorce to DJ Ruckus Will Be Official Next Week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Japan's economy shrinks at fastest rate since 2014 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 04:30 (JST), February 03 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Strava for iOS Gains HealthKit Integration for Importing Apple Watch Workouts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All in good time: Why Brazil wants its teens not to have sex #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We found these ergonomic Tempur-Pedic pillows on sale for super cheap #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 of the best Bluetooth speakers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s Always a Good Day to Bask in the Platonic Love Between Leonardo DiCaprio and Brad Pitt #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WTF is a Theragun? A look at the best massage guns for percussive therapy. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Look at the Sizes of That Thing.’ Colorado Sheriff Department’s Confusing Boulder Description is Ruling Social Med… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pitbull Canceled on Steven Tyler Event Due to Kobe Bryant Tragedy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus Closes Out Doors' 50th Anniversary 'Morrison Hotel' Party #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHK WORLD RADIO JAPAN - English News at 20:00 (JST), February 03 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['She's more qualified than you are for your job': Seth Meyers blasts Pompeo over bizarre NPR tantrum #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amy Schumer Shares IVF Results and Thanks Fans as She Continues Journey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[San Francisco Giants Hire First Full-Time Female Coach in MLB History #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google's Super Bowl ad will totally make you cry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway Invokes MLK Jr.'s Name to Blast Trump Impeachment Trial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom and Jerry: 80 years of cat v mouse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kelly Rowland Proudly Sports Beyonce's New Adidas x Ivy Park Gear #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I used emoji to order groceries #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 Mazda CX-9 review: When fashion trumps function - Roadshow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PnB Rock Totals Car in Alleged Street Race, Arrested For DUI #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[23andMe CEO lays off 100, attributes sluggish sales to consumer privacy concerns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Shares New 'Slofie' Videos Highlighting iPhone 11 and 11 Pro Cameras #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple to Show Off Apple TV+ Show 'Mythic Quest: Raven's Banquet' at PAX South #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump impeachment: All eyes on moderate Republicans in witnesses battle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bradley Whitford Says Stephen King's Diversity Oscar Tweet is Ignorant #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Captain America' Actress Claims Self-Defense in Mom's Murder #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chuck Liddell Hopes Cowboy Cerrone Beats Conor McGregor At UFC 246 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lee Harvey Oswald's Final Uncashed Paycheck, Up for Auction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EA Retiring Tetris Apps for iOS in April 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Was the Fastest Growing Premium Smartphone Brand of 2019 in India #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tim Cook Shares Behind-the-Scenes Look at Apple TV+ Show 'Little America' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess Who This Happy Kid Turned Into! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Find your lobster with a little help from Match #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Felicity Huffman &amp; Daughter Wear Masks at Airport Amid Coronavirus Scare #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cleveland Browns Mascot Swagger Dead At 6 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wrapped Up Stars ... Hot And Dry! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Belgium's ex-King Albert II admits fathering child after DNA test #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘I Cracked Up So Hard.’ This Woman’s Romantic Dinner Date Is Precisely What Her Dreams Were Never Made Of #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kangaroo Island: Tree climber helps save koalas #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 of the best automatic cat feeders to keep your pet fed and happy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Stops Signing iOS 13.3 Following Release of iOS 13.3.1 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This deepfake of Robert Downey Jr. and Tom Holland in 'Back to the Future' is unreal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blueface Says Tekashi's Bodyguards Are Smart for Passing on the Job #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seth Meyers pokes fun at Trump's weird obsession with badgers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Joins the FIDO Alliance to Help Develop and Promote Authentication Standards #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy S20 leaks again, this time on Samsung's own website #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top Stories: 5G iPhone and iPad Rumors, AirPods Pro Lite?, HomePod Turns Two #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nikki Bella Showing Off Her Baby Bump After Pregnancy Reveal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Davos 2020: What is the World Economic Forum and is it elitist? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Works Yummy Food Truck with James Corden #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Truth About Meghan Markle and Ellen DeGeneres' Alleged Interview #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best BT broadband deals in the UK #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pamela Anderson &amp; New 'Husband' Split 12 Days After Secret Wedding #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
