<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Gov. Bruce Rauner and JB Pritzker to Face Off in Illinois #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quick challenge for Mississippi's 15-week abortion ban #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shooting reported at St. Mary's County high school in Maryland #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maryland school shooting is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Is The First Day Of Spring is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kirk Korver is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[USS Juneau discovered: 4 Belmar sailors went down with the ship in WWII #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India confirms killing of 39 workers kidnapped by IS #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump furious over leak of warning to not congratulate Putin #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[39 Indians killed in Mosul; news updates: Kin of one of Islamic State's victims says govt gave false promises… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White Rhino is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[white rhino is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guillermo Haro is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Note: Trump's congratulatory tone with Russia rings alarms for some #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Fourth Nor'easter Is Wreaking Havoc on the East Coast. Here's How Much Snow to Expect From Winter Storm Toby #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maryland School Shooting is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[weather radar is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jacksonville Alabama is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shooting is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billionaire Pritzker Wins Democratic Nod for Illinois Governor #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US, South Korea announce annual military exercises to begin on April 1 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica Suspends CEO Amid Facebook Data Scandal #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spring is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Package found in Austin serial bombing investigation may be break in the case #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[France's Sarkozy detained over allegations of bribery by Libya #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Minnesota police officer charged in fatal shooting of Justine Damond #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Equinoccio de Primavera is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern white rhino: Last male Sudan dies in Kenya #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opm is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Package bound for Austin explodes at Texas FedEx facility, second explosive device found, police say… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[spring is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica Suspends CEO Alexander Nix After Video's Release #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica Faces UK Search as EU Weighs Response #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maryland high school shooting: 16-year-old victim remains in critical condition #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['We're Losing the Fight': Tuberculosis Batters a Venezuela in Crisis #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hotels is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Day of Spring 2018 is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shuttles to FIU not running smoothly on first day back after bridge collapse, students say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Britney Spears is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dairy Queen is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Calls Putin to Congratulate Russian President on Election Win #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aubrey Oday is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lehigh Valley forecast is for 9-15 inches of snow, but actual count may bedevil experts again… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Winter storm: "Four'easter" to hit East Coast -- live updates, forecast, power outages, school closings… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police Respond to Sixth Explosion in Texas as Serial Bomber's Terror Continues #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Trump-related lawsuits: Porn star, Playboy model, harassment accuser #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Great Mills High School is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Source: Nikolas Cruz' brother arrested for trespassing at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three students, including gunman, critically injured in Maryland high school shooting #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[39 Indians killed in Mosul; news updates: Congress demands financial aid for kin of Islamic State's victims… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cambridge Analytica suspends CEO as Facebook data outcry intensifies; Zuckerberg called to testify… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sheriff: Lake Wales teen beaten to death by friend with baseball bat #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York Today: Latest Updates on the Snowstorm #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reports of serious damage as tornado rips through Alabama university campus #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Package found in Austin serial bombing investigation may be break in the case #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What authorities are doing in response to Austin serial bombings #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Oliver trolls Mike Pence with gay bunny book that shoots to No. 1 on Amazon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Minneapolis police officer Mohamed Noor turns himself in on murder, manslaughter charges in Justine Damond killing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Explosion at FedEx facility in Texas probed for connection to Austin bombings #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2nd suspicious package found at FedEx after blast, police chief and FedEx say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senators Reject Effort to Cut US Support for Saudi-led Campaign in Yemen #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quick challenge for Mississippi's 15-week abortion ban #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's US visit is a shopping trip for war #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Package bound for Austin blows up at FedEx building near San Antonio #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weinstein Co. Bankruptcy: Grim Last Days for Troubled Studio Outlined in Court #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sudan, last male northern white rhino, dies in Kenya #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Austin Bombing Suspect Is Identified As Mark Anthony Conditt; Died In Standoff #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Summer Zervos is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When is the First Day of Spring is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Austin bombing suspect dies after detonating explosive as SWAT team closed in, police say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baltimore Weather is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Day of Spring is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Myanmar's President, a Close Friend of Suu Kyi, Retires #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First day of Spring 2018 is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Congratulates Putin on Re-Election, but Fails to Mention Meddling in US #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Weather forecast is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officer who fatally shot Justine Damond is charged with murder #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dodgers lose NLCS hero Justin Turner to broken wrist, forced to improvise with season approaching… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Texas Bombing is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iraq tragedy: 39 Indians killed in Mosul by IS; Swaraj gives proof; updates #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is it really spring? 4th nor'easter in 3 weeks closes schools, delays flights #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[hotels is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Student gunman dies after Maryland school shooting; two other students injured #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Trump won't call Putin's election win a 'sham' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Congratulates Putin on Re-Election, but Fails to Mention Meddling in US #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tensions mount as another package bomb believed bound for Austin explodes at FedEx facility #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Illinois Primary: Democratic Congressman Leads Tight Race, GOP Governor Survives #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Illinois governor is projected to narrowly defeat conservative challenger in Republican primary… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Austin bombing suspect is dead, sources say #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mueller pens Trump in as he slips restraints elsewhere #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Illinois congressman holds off challenge from far left #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India says it has confirmed 39 Indians missing in Iraq since 2014 are dead #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump congratulates Putin on his reelection, discusses US-Russian 'arms race' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# trends amid Cambridge Analytica scandal #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Explosion at FedEx near San Antonio could be linked to Austin blasts, FBI says #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kidnapped Dapchi schoolgirls freed in Nigeria #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Austin bomber is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber is trending on Google. Read the latest here: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Package bound for Austin detonates at FedEx facility, second explosive package intercepted, police say… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Illinois Primary: Democratic Congressman Leads Tight Race, GOP Governor Survives #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
