<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Tiger Woods Shoots 5-over to Close out Disappointing 2020 Genesis Open #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kurt Zouma Says Jose Mourinho Told Him He Was 'Rubbish' at Chelsea #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Embiid, Simmons say success a matter of time #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Like father like son: Shareef O'Neal heads to LSU #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Magic leads tributes to Kobe at All-Star Game #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Yu Darvish Says Astros Should Lose 2017 World Series, Rips Players' Apologies #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Ryan Garcia Scores Vicious 1st-Round Knockout Win over Francisco Fonseca #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Chelsea vs. Manchester United: Odds, Live Stream, TV Schedule and Preview #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Oilers' Kassian suspended for kicking opponent #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  The fourth quarter of the All-Star Game will never be the same again #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  La Liga Table 2020 Week 24: Standings and Final Scores After Sunday #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Common Says Dunk Contest Was Expected to Be a Tie: 'Somebody Didn't Do It Right' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Reds' Bauer calls Astros hypocrites and cheaters #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Zach LaVine Says LeBron James Is His Dream Teammate in 'First Take' Interview #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Minor leaguers getting minimum salary increase #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Vanessa Bryant Posts Instagram for 'My Forever Valentine' Kobe Bryant #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Tiger Woods Tied for 45th in Genesis Open After Shooting 73 in Round 2 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Blues' Jay Bouwmeester Has Defibrillator Put in Chest After Cardiac Emergency #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Adam Silver Says He Expects 'Return to Normalcy' for NBA's China Relationship #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Cavaliers Owner Dan Gilbert Returns to Work, Talks Recovery from 2019 Stroke #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Tyson Fury's path to Deontay Wilder rematch: Bravado, bravery, controversy #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Ex-Michigan State PG Keith Appling Arrested for Possession of Heroin #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Neymar Praises 'Special' Jadon Sancho Ahead of PSG's UCL Clash with Dortmund #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Derrick Jones Jr. Says Aaron Gordon Can Have Dunk Contest Rematch After Loss #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Rams, Broncos Reportedly Decide to Send Fewer Coaches to 2020 NFL Combine #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  2020 Slam Dunk Contest Participants: Format, Odds and Predicted Winner #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Chelsea Boss Frank Lampard on Decision to Drop Kepa: 'I Just Expect Reactions' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Cardinals' Steve Keim Compares CFL Signing Chris Streveler to Taysom Hill #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Champions League 2020: Odds, Live Stream, TV Schedule for Last-16 Ties #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Fixing WWE Raw and SmackDown's Worst Booking Decisions for the Week of Feb. 15 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Cavaliers Rumors: John Beilein May Step Down as HC During All-Star Break #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Redskins releasing CB Norman after 4 seasons #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  All you need to know about this year's Daytona 500 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kyle Juszczyk Defends Jimmy Garoppolo Amid Criticism for 49ers' Super Bowl Loss #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Donny van de Beek Plays Down Real Madrid Links: 'If It Happens, It Happens' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Follow live: Team LeBron vs. Team Giannis in All-Star format that honors Kobe #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Irate fans caught in 'horrific' traffic want refunds #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Baker urges MLB to protect Astros from beanballs #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  WWE's Sasha Banks Reportedly Will Appear in 'The Mandalorian' Season 2 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  N'Golo Kante Says Chelsea Not Looking for Revenge Against Manchester United #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  NBA All-Star Game 2020: LeBron vs. Giannis Rosters, TV Schedule and MVP Odds #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Buddy Hield Wins 2020 NBA 3-Point Contest: Scores, Highlights and Reaction #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Avenatti found guilty in Nike case, faces 20 years #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kawhi Leonard Debuts New Balance Signature Shoe During 2020 NBA All-Star Game #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Antonio Brown Talks Roethlisberger, Brady, Raiders, NFL Return on Breakfast Club #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Giant Killers: Which teams could surprise in the first round #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  What Man City's UEFA ban means and what happens next #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Series goat Darvish says Astros should lose title #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Paul Scholes Says Sir Alex Ferguson Would Not Have Let Paul Pogba Train Alone #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Rivers concerned after George reinjures hammy #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Blues' Bouwmeester undergoes heart procedure #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Red Sox Rumors: Sign-Stealing Report Expected by End of February #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Tiger balloons to 76, says he felt 'stiff' at Riviera #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Shaquille O'Neal's Son Shareef Announces Transfer to LSU from UCLA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Bam Adebayo Wins 2020 NBA Skills Competition: Recap, Highlights, Reaction #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Bronny James, Sierra Canyon Beat St. John Bosco 67-39 as BJ Boston Drops 18 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  UFC Fight Night 167 Results: Blachowicz Beats Anderson via 1st-Round Knockout #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Overwatch League 2020 Week 2: Carpe's Top Plays, Prize Money #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  An early look at the sneakers for All-Star Weekend #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Real Madrid's Vinicius Jr. Wants to Follow Raheem Sterling's Goalscoring Example #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Rhea Ripley Beats Bianca Belair, Retains NXT Title at WWE NXT TakeOver: Portland #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Texans' Watt has 'best day,' marries NWSL's Ohai #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Bracketology: Indiana stays on right side of the bubble #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  NBA Slam Dunk Contest 2020: Participants, Format, TV Schedule and Predictions #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Walker: Tatum 'best player on the court' vs. Clips #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Analysing How Jadon Sancho Can Become English Football's Most Expensive Signing #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  MLB, MLBPA Reportedly Discussing New Rules to Prevent Electronic Sign-Stealing #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kobe Bryant, David Stern Honored by Pau Gasol, Sue Bird Before Rising Stars Game #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  EPL Winners and Losers After Sunday's 2020 Week 26 Premier League Results #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Barack Obama Reflects on Kobe Bryant's Death at NBA All-Star Weekend #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  'It's just like ripping open a scab': Dodgers' sign-stealing anger is bursting through #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  How LaMelo Ball Fits with NBA's Worst Teams #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Nets' Spencer Dinwiddie: Knicks 'Probably Not Going to Be That Good' Next Year #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Zinedine Zidane: Eden Hazard 'Ready to Play' for Real Madrid After Injury Layoff #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Alex Rodriguez Reportedly Candidate to Buy Mets After Failed Steve Cohen Sale #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Who's next for Jan Blachowicz and Corey Anderson? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Daytona 500 2020: Start Time, Date, TV Schedule, Live Stream and More #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  NBA All-Star Game MVP award named for Kobe #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Rudolph: Garrett slur claim a 'bold-faced lie' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Silver expects 'normalcy' soon for NBA in China #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  NXT TakeOver Portland: Live results and reactions #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Real Madrid vs. Celta Vigo: Odds, Live Stream, TV Schedule and Preview #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kawhi Leonard on Winning ASG's 1st Kobe Bryant MVP Award: 'This One Is for Him' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Quique Setien on Lionel Messi: 'There Will Be a Time When We Have to Rest Him' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Thiago Silva Says PSG 'Have No Fear' of Borussia Dortmund's Erling Haaland #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Dusty Baker Worried About 'Premeditated Retaliation' Against Astros for Cheating #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Antoine Griezmann, Barcelona Escape with Narrow Win vs. Getafe #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Julian Nagelsmann Talks Rejecting Real Madrid, Future Premier League Interest #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Trump makes grand entrance at Daytona 500 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Former Heat, Raptors Star Chris Bosh Not Named Finalist for 2020 Basketball HOF #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kawhi lights-out from beyond arc to claim MVP #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Two California Little Leagues ban use of Astros #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  What's up with Tiger and a big-time final group on Sunday at Genesis #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Barcelona Hasn't Made Approach for Angel Rodriguez, Says Getafe President #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  NBA Power Rankings: Where Every Team Sits at the All-Star Break #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Damian Lillard Gets Engaged to Girlfriend Kay'La Hanson at NBA All-Star Weekend #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Kobe, Stern honored at All-Star Celebrity Game #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Mikel Arteta: Nicolas Pepe's Price Tag Has Put Player in 'Difficult Position' #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  Antoine Griezmann Discusses Lionel Messi Relationship After Getafe Win #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[So,  The greatness of this All-Star Game will carry us #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
