<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the New Salem Season 3 Trailer #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dad Sets Inspiring Example for Daughter, World in General #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beyoncé will headline this year's Tidal X benefit show because who else can? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talking self-driving cars, IPOs, and what’s next, with True Ventures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Trade Desk finishes strong at $30.10 per share after its first day on NASDAQ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Global Over The Top Market By Content Type, By Platform, By Deployment Model, By Service Type, By User Type, Compe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Corey Feldman: What If I Had Committed Suicide After Today Show Performance? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chris Pratt Finally Snaps: Find Out Why! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt "Married a Lunatic" &amp; "Lives on Whiskey," Celebrity Sources Say #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is technology really the solution for developing countries to prosper? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pogoplug unlimited cloud storage service is shutting down on September 28 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Waze launches Bluetooth beacons to avoid tunnel blackouts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Little girl's pep talk gives us serious confidence goals #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[App Developers: It’s Time to Focus on Retention Strategies (Report) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rob Kardashian pulls off platinum blonde as well as his sisters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stephen Colbert skewers Donald Trump Jr. for his idiotic Skittles analogy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Clarity Connect™ cloud contact center solution for Office 365 and Skype for Business is now available #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blizzard is phasing out the ‘#URL#’ name #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CenturyLink Schedules Third Quarter 2016 Earnings Conference Call #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This running back has the NFL's funniest Twitter avatar by far #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beats has a new pair of stylish wired headphones for you wireless haters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter’s new transparency report is disclosure done right #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: The N-Word is HILARIOUS...When Don King Says It #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch This Ash vs. Evil Dead Behind the Scenes Trailer Tour! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The State of Communications and Collaboration in the Enterprise--How Companies are Embracing Digital Transformation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jana Kramer: Is Husband Mike Caussin a Sex Addict? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the new C-level executives born of smart cities #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DigitalTown looks to ease pain of smart city transformation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chan Zuckerberg Initiative commits to investing $3 billion to cure diseases #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney is already lowering box-office expectations for Star Wars: Rogue One #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Protests erupt in Charlotte following the shooting of Keith Lamont Scott. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kailyn Lowry: Buh-Bye Javi Marroquin, Hello New Boyfriend! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This may be the perfect wireless headphone design (for now) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aria Systems launches automotive recurring revenue platform #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WhatsApp Adds User Tagging to Group Chats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity is threatening America’s military supremacy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 reasons chatbots can’t replace B2B customer support agents yet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HP's Sprocket might not be the best instant printer, but it's definitely the most fun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warner CEO Jeff Bewkes Says DC Films Have Room for Improvement #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joby proves that selfie sticks can, indeed, get sillier #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg's new $3 billion goal: Curing all disease #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Angelina Jolie and Brad Pitt Divorce: How Much is at Stake? #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists teach machines to hunt and kill humans — in Doom deathmatch mode #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Want to know how many times ancient humans migrated out of Africa? Check their genes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CodeFights Unveils Code Arcade To Make Honing Your Skills A Thrilling Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tinder's iMessage app involves swiping but not dating #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Londoners wait in line for hours to get a taste of In-N-Out Burger #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UPCOMING WEBINAR: Customer Generated Content – 7 Things Marketers Should Know #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Escape prison with the hero of ‘Shawshank Redemption’ in this 8-bit film #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rome set to drop 2024 Olympics bid, improving LA's chances #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blizzard kills the classic #URL# brand after 20 years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emma Watson takes her fight for gender equality to universities #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why ‘there’s a chatbot for that’ is now a thing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We now know exactly how many times Trump has tweeted his favorite insults #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bots are waging passive-aggressive war on Wikipedia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg and Priscilla Chan announce $3 billion initiative to ‘cure all diseases’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Megawati Instructs PDIP Members to Support Ahok-Djarot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tumblr Now Supports Apple Live Photos on the Web #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to keep your Google Allo messages secure and private #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Instagram Introduces “Save as Draft” Feature #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[22 Celebrity Weddings We Did NOT See Coming #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Star Wars: Battlefront’s Death Star DLC is out — watch us play #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blizzard is getting rid of the #URL# name #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 16 countries in the 'Overwatch' World Cup #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uncharted 4: A Thief’s End new multiplayer DLC makes murder photogenic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Dark Tower TV series featuring Idris Elba is in the works #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rocana to Lead Customer Experience Forum at TC3 Summit 2016 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Instanet Solutions adds another 12,000+ subscribers Deep in the Heart of Texas #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Grand Admiral Thrawn in a New Star Wars Rebels Clip #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[QUIZ: Which cocktail garnish fits your personality? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Dodgers just trolled Madison Bumgarner with these t-shirts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook Announces Several Measurement Products, Integrations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jason Calacanis on the new #URL#, the state of the media and what's interesting to investors #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YouTube Announces #HASHTAG# ‘Get Out the Vote’ Campaign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon hires CEO of conversational commerce startup Angel.ai #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oliver Queen Surveys Star City in Arrow Season 5 Poster #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the Phantasm: Ravager Trailer #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gwent: The Witcher Card Game gets stress tests #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DreamWorks Cancels Horror Movie Haunted, Fires Director #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don King uses N-word while introducing Donald Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 great 'Survivor' moments, as told by two former castaways #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chelsea Handler calls Angelina Jolie 'a f*cking lunatic' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why You Should Never Take A Photo Of Your Boarding Pass #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Brangelina breakup has made 'By the Sea' into a too-real masterpiece #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Climate change poses a major security risk to the U.S. today, intelligence report warns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook Announces Several Measurement Products, Integrations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Tension Experience: A live theater show that seriously messes with your head #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Up close with Oakley Radar Pace, the wearable that may help you forget Google Glass #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ReplyBuy brings artificial intelligence concierge service to sports and entertainment market #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Head back to 'Shawshank Redemption' prison in 8-bit-style short #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYC bombing suspect's eBay and YouTube accounts give insight into his mind #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Visit to the X-Mansion for the X-Men: Apocalypse Blu-ray Junket #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even your toaster is about to be smarter than you #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Microsoft releases new Windows 10 preview with Maps improvements and USB Audio 2.0 support #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Global Cloud Services Brokerage (CSB) Industry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Fallen Movie Trailer is Finally Here! #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Insider Tips for Maximizing Your Budget with Media Tours #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chelsea Manning prepares defense against charges stemming from suicide attempt #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An artist fixed that Jumanji set photo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indonesia's taxman going after Google and other tech giants - The Straits Times #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
