<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[November Horoscopes: What to Wear According to the New Moon: Scorpio season is here! ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, covering up is not the solution to my pre-school daughter being body shamed: Last... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: Prince Harry Could Propose To Girlfriend Meghan Markle!: It looks like things... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. Revealed Ghost Rider's Origins While Leaving Us With So Many M... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rapper K'naan wants to tell Somali-American tale in HBO show: MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — For ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gifted Trailer Is Here: Watch the Movie That Brought Chris Evans and Jenny Slate Toge... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Val Kilmer -- Michael Douglas is Wrong ... I Don't Have Cancer!: Val Kilmer says he's... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brownstein and Saunders, mutual admirers, co-host reading: NEW YORK (AP) — It's not h... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Dad Of The Year' Gives Fellow Airplane Passengers Halloween Candy — So They Can Help... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NFL's Josh Huff -- Arrested for Gun And Weed: Philadelphia Eagles' Josh Huff was arre... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp joins 'Fantastic Beasts' sequel: LOS ANGELES (AP) — Johnny Depp is about ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Set to Star in Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them Sequel: Muggles an... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe Taylor Swift &amp; Tom Hiddleston didn't break up at all &amp; they're just fooling us:... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lindsay Lohan Adopts a Strange Accent in Her Everyday Life and No One Knows Why: Lind... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louis C.K. On Hillary: ‘We Need A Tough Bitch Mother Who Nobody Likes’: Louis C.K. is... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Golden Globes: Campus Shooting Doc 'Tower' Ruled Ineligible for Animation Award, Spar... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Crown' offers rare portrait of young Elizabeth II: The series comes from the pen... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Didn't Return To Social Media After All…: Looks like Kim Kardashian is... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeremy Calvert Posts Photo of Daughter with MASSIVE Gun, Hears it From Critics:  Tee... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hollywood's 2016 Halloween Costume Superlatives: See Our Picks for Most Creative, Cut... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stars Share Throwback Halloween Pics: Who's Who?!?:  Some celebrities get into the H... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E! Will Try Its Hand At Daytime TV As KUWTK Ratings Decline: Their kash kow has run o... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessica Simpson and Hubby Eric Johnson Give Us Some Grease Realness for Halloween: Lo... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Cena Dressed as Nikki Bella for Halloween &amp; Left Little to the Imagination: See ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dancing With the Stars' Emma Slater and Sasha Farber Celebrate Their Engagement With ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Election Day nears, big numbers for news networks: NEW YORK (AP) — It's been such ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pam Anderson -- Issues Sexual Assault Warning Attacks Rideshare App Drivers (VIDEO): ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is Us' Sterling K. Brown Has a Familiar Warning About Tonight's New Episode: At ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chris Brown -- I'm Poppin' on My ATV ... Screw My Neighbors (VIDEO): Chris Brown is a... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Celebrity Beauties—and the Beasts—of Halloween 2016: From Disney to horror movies... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The real conversations people are having about the election: It feels like this elect... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney Star Ryan McCartan Was Hospitalized On Halloween!: Talk about scary! While the... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The top 10 books on Apple's iBooks-US: iBook charts for week ending October 30, 2016 ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Twitter is preparing me to explain anti-Semitism to my son: On a recent idyllic l... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Rock Works Up A Sweat Dancing As Pikachu For His Daughter Jasmine: A video posted... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See The First Trailer For Gifted, The Movie Where Chris Evans &amp; Jenny Slate Found Lov... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amelia Earhart -- Survived Plane Crash ... Died as a Castaway: Amelia Earhart did NOT... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louis C.K. Says He's Voting for Hillary Clinton to Get a Mother in the White House: "... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miranda Kerr Opens Up About Post-Divorce Depression: The model split from Orlando Blo... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama reveals private living areas of White House: President Barack Obama likes to sa... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Val Kilmer Says He Doesn't Have Cancer: ''I Love Michael Douglas but He Is Misinforme... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Higgins' wedding stress showcases his not-so-eligible Bachelor side: Ben Higgins ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey -- James Packer Tells Team, 'F*** Off' ... I'm Getting Married!!!: Maria... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tony Bennett, Muppets set for Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade: Tony Bennett, Sarah McL... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Lupita Nyong'o Lip Sync Enrique Iglesias and Gente De Zona's "Bailando": Yes, L... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: In 'Loving,' the revolution power of a true love: Jeff Nichols' "Loving," abo... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Make your own mulling spice mix now, and you'll be so glad on chilly nights: Drinking... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Country star Kenny Chesney honored with 1st of 2 awards: NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Coun... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Simmons -- Stick A Fork In The Cubs ... They'll LOSE TONIGHT!! (VIDEO): Close yo... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samuel Goldwyn Writing Awards Winners Unveiled: The screenwriting prizes were handed ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jose Fernandez -- Marlins Jersey Will Stay Retired ... Despite Cocaine, Booze Evidenc... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry, but people with hearing loss don't 'look' deaf: Have you ever noted your heari... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can an epidural prevent postpartum depression?: I started having the flashbacks just ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Mila Kunis' Last Few Weeks of Her Second Pregnancy: Mila Kunis and Ashton Kutc... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We see you Justin Theroux, with your subtle Brad Pitt shade-throwing ways: Justin The... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gwen Stefani on Why Her Marriage to Gavin Rossdale Was “Extra Hard”: And why the sing... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey and Nick Cannon's Divorce Has Been Finalized: While Mariah Carey has cur... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dance Moms' Abby Lee Miller isn't going to jail on fraud charges — yet: Abby Lee Mill... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge decides whether to exclude deposition from Cosby trial: NORRISTOWN, Pa. (AP) — ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vicki Gunvalson's Daughter Briana Has Been Diagnosed With Lupus: So heartbreaking… On... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Did Taylor Swift Write "Better Man" About? We Investigate the Lyrics for Little B... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An old school candied yam recipe will take you straight back to childhood: 'Tis offic... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin credits his wife Hilaria with making him a more patient parent: Part of ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel takes mind-bending turn with "Doctor Strange": BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — Wh... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's really not fair that RHOC's Briana has to brave so many health issues: For over ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chris Brown's Daughter -- Selena's Family Beaming After Royalty Homage: Chris Brown's... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Larsa Pippen Calls Police on Scottie Pippen: Recording of 911 Call Revealed!:  It's ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shay Mitchell Releases Emotional Farewell Video to Pretty Little Liars: We're not cry... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch The Flash Online: Check Out Season 3 Episode 5:  The Flash Season 3 Episode 5 ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scottie, Larsa Pippen -- Battle Royale Over Fortune &amp; Prenup: Scottie Pippen and wife... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tyga Is Making Good On His Promise To Repay His Massive Debt To Jeweler Jason Arasheb... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Prince Harry's Relationship With Meghan Markle: Watch to Get the Scoop!: Is a ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Danielle Jonas Shares Adorable First Photo of Her Two Daughters Together: It looks li... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why John Oliver compared schools to a Tyler Perry movie: Despite the fact that laws a... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Young Thug -- I'm Turnt Up and Free to Lean in Hollywood (VIDEO): Young Thug carried ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kendall Jenner Just Spent $52K On A Couch Because Life Is Unfair…: Lifestyles of the ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Larsa Pippen -- 2nd 911 Call ... Help, Scottie's Breaking Stuff! (AUDIO): Larsa Pippe... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: Mel Gibson roars back with bruising 'Hacksaw Ridge': Is "Hacksaw Ridge" Mel G... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[High School Fakes The Deaths Of Four Students In Order To Teach Safe Driving Lesson —... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Missing Evan Peters on American Horror Story This Season? This Might H: Looks like Pe... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teen Cannibal Austin Harrouff Told Police After Attack: 'Help Me, I Ate Something Bad... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Farrah Abraham Sparks Controversy After Supposedly Giving Her Daugther A Weight Loss ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Clintonworld Thinks About the Latest Abedin-Weiner Scandal: “If Weiner hadn’t ta... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessa Duggar Offers Pregnancy Update, Prepares For Spurgeon's 1st Birthday!:  It's a... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Somebody at the F.B.I. Trying to Throw the Election?: A series of tweets from a lo... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp enters Rowling's magical world in 'Fantastic Beasts' sequel: Johnny Depp ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry Has Fallen Hard for Girlfriend Meghan Markle as Their Relationship Gets ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ryan McCartan Spends Halloween in the Hospital: ''Life Is Precious But Fragile'': Thi... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Can Now Shop Directly From Your Instagram Feed: "Link in bio" captions be gone. T... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WikiLeaks Reveals John Podesta Pockets $7,000 a Month from Major Clint: The Clinton c... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Instagram Could Become an E-commerce Powerhouse: The social-media company just ro... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey Hasn't Missed a Beat Since Her Breakup: How the Star Is Already Moving O... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Donald Trump a Manchurian Candidate?: A series of explosive reports provide new de... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mariah Carey And Nick Cannon's Divorce Official Days Before James Packer Split: Just ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Artisan chocolate will forever change the way you look at candy bars: We've never met... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heroic Father Enables Daughter to Trick or Treat on Board Airplane:  Good news, read... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch This Is Us Online: Check Out Season 1 Episode 6:  This Is Us Season 1 Episode ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel takes mind-bending turn with "Doctor Strange": BEVERLY HILLS, Calif. (AP) — Wh... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ace of Diamonds Strip Club -- Mally Mall's Monkey Not Kosher with Health Dept. (VIDEO... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kris Jenner Sexes It Up for Halloween, The Internet Reacts:  Kris Jenner dressed up ... #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
