<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Arrow Gives its Hero an Ending Fit for a Queen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bandai America Launches New PAC-MAN Tamagotchi #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DC UNIVERSE Announces Original Unscripted Gaming Mini-Series, DC UNIVERSE All Star Games #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What To Read &amp; Watch on DC UNIVERSE Before The Theatrical Release of Birds of Prey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TELEVISION AND COMIC INDUSTRY EXECUTIVES TO JUDGE AND MENTOR TOP 10 FINALISTS IN DC UNIVERSE’S DCYou Unscripted FAN… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Book Breakdown – Shadow of the Batgirl Makes Us Happy and Hungry #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: The Super Sons…in the 31st Century?!? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Secrets and Adventure Abound in Amy Reeder’s Amethyst #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McFarlane Toys and Warner Bros. Launch New DC Multiverse Toys #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DC Introduces New Sourcebook for The Last God #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Dr. Quinn Dives Into the Joker’s Past #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Batwoman’s Meagan Tandy Fights Villains…and Long Buried Feelings #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Green Lantern: Legacy Reminds Us that Heroism is Found Close to Home #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mortal Kombat Gets Animated With ‘Scorpion’s Revenge’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oni Press Returns To The Tea Dragon Society In Final Installment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“Green Arrow &amp; the Canaries” Looks Towards the Future #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oni Press Announces Plans To Travel To Titan In 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conner and Palmiotti Return with Harley Quinn and the Birds of Prey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Daphne Byrne is a Creepy Victorian Nightmare #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Supergirl’s David Harewood Brings Back a Classic DC Villain #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wizard World Presents An ‘Animation Celebration’ In Cleveland, March 6-8 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Leafy Kind of Love: DC Collectibles Celebrates Harley and Ivy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kieron Gillen Teams With Jim Rossignol &amp; Jeff Stokely For ‘Ludocrats’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Event Leviathan: Checkmate Delivers More Espionage Action this April! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warner Bros. To Open First Ever Harry Potter Flagship Store In New York #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Star Wars: Rise Of Skywalker’ Dominates Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ARCHIE COMICS March 2020 Solicitations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Celebrate Valentine’s Day with this DIY Wonder Woman Bookmark #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Batman Casts A Giant Shadow Over 2019 Comic Book Sales! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Bitter Root’ Series In Development For Film #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SWAMP THING: TWIN BRANCHES TAKES ROOT AT DC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Breath Of Fire: Official Complete Works’ Hardcover Edition To Be Released By UDON Entertainment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Why are Gotham’s Villains So Terrified? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DC UNIVERSE MEMBERS TO RECEIVE EARLY ACCESS TO “BIRDS OF PREY” BEFORE THEATRICAL RELEASE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to Watch and Read on DC UNIVERSE This February #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Grant Morrison’s The Green Lantern Returns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unlocking the History of the Multiverse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Tynion Brings Batman to a New “Action-Horror” Era #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Birds of Prey Theatrical Release Sweepstakes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Book Breakdown – Wonder Woman: Warbringer is Inspiring and Intense #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doomsday Clock #HASHTAG# Headed Back to Press! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Getting to Know Helena Bertinelli’s Huntress #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CAST OF “BIRDS OF PREY” JOIN DC UNIVERSE MEMBERS AT SPECIAL DC UNIVERSE FAN SCREENING IN NEW YORK’S TIMES SQUARE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: The Suicide Squad is in Trouble…Again… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019’s Techno-Virus Thriller DCeased Continues in DCeased: Unkillables! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking News: The CW Renews All Five of its Current DC Shows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McFarlane Toys Partners With CD PROJEKT RED On Cyberpunk 2077 Figures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Bad Boys For Life’ Holds Top Spot At Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Comics’ Greatest Talent Celebrates Diana in Wonder Woman #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Robert Kirkman &amp; Marc Silvestri’s ‘Stealth’ In Development With Universal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THE JOKER 80TH ANNIVERSARY 100-PAGE SUPER SPECTACULAR #HASHTAG# Hits Stores April 29, 2020! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Fire Power’ Prelude Graphic Novel To Hit In April #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arrow’s Producers Answer Our Burning Questions About the Finale #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drawing Inspiration From DC: The New Frontier #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Bad Boys For Life’ Threepeats At Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Birds of Prey’s Black Mask is Even Crazier and Scarier in the Comics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watchmen: The Ends Are Here #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Birds of Prey and DC’s Radical Tradition of Girl Gangs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Bad Boys for Life’ Tops Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dark Secrets and Nightmares Await Inside The Low, Low Woods #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cass Effect: Sarah Kuhn and Nicole Goux Talk Shadow of the Batgirl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What If SARAH from SARAH’S SCRIBBLES Grew Up? Author’s Answer is FANGS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Dead Body Road’ Floors It Down The Fast Lane Toward A  New Story Arc #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Laurel &amp; Hardy Meet The Three Stooges! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘The Flash’ #HASHTAG# Features a Series of Decade Variant Covers by Comics’ Greatest Artists #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Easter Egg Hunt: A Post-Crisis World #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CATWOMAN 80TH ANNIVERSARY 100-PAGE SUPER SPECTACULAR #HASHTAG# Arrives April 15, 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: A New Aquababy is On Its Way! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Metropolis…Wrecked by the Legion of Doom? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Batman #HASHTAG# Headed Back to Press! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DC UNIVERSE ANNOUNCES TOP THREE FINALISTS OF DCYou Unscripted FAN CONTEST #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back to Press for The Last God #HASHTAG# and Far Sector #HASHTAG#! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Batman: The Adventures Continue’ Arrives from Paul Dini, Alan Burnett and Ty Templeton! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘1917’ Conquers ‘Star Wars’ At Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gisele Lagace’s ‘Sticky Dilly Buns Volume 1’ And The Final Volume Of ‘Menage À 3’ To Be Released By UDON Entertainm… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fire Power #HASHTAG# &amp; #HASHTAG# Will Hit Stores In June #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Stravaganza’ Epic Conclusion To Be Released February 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking News: The CW’s Superman &amp; Lois Gets a Series Order #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bringing Excitement, Joy and Kangas to Diana: Princess of the Amazons #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Caity Lotz on Grief, Change and Raising Hell on Legends of Tomorrow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Punchline is a Hit as Two DC Titles Go Back to Press Ahead of On-Sale #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oni Press Announces ‘Rogue Planet’ From Cullen Bunn And Andy MacDonald #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to WATCH AND READ on DC UNIVERSE In January 2020! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Birds of Prey’ Grounded At Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Diana: Princess of the Amazons Shows that Even Heroes Need Friends #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonathan Hickman &amp; Mike Huddleston Launches New Image Comics Series ‘Decorum’ This March #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marv Wolfman and Riley Rossmo Pay Tribute to The Silver Age of Flash #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Norroway—The Queen On The High Mountain’ To Hit Shelves This August #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DC MULTIVERSE McFarlane Toys Sweeps #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DARK NIGHTS: DEATH METAL – Melting Faces This May! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Mega Man Star Force: Official Complete Works’ Hardcover Release Announced #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What To Read &amp; Watch on DC UNIVERSE Before The Theatrical Release of Birds of Prey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Female Furies: Rise and Rage Against the Man(chine) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Very Batman Holiday Sweepstakes! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Setting Madness to Music: Hildur Guðnadóttir is Joker’s Hidden Star #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Boys are Back in Town #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Rise Of Skywalker’ Wins Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shadow of the Batgirl Transforms a Teenage Assassin into a Superhero #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Rise Of Skywalker’ Holds On To Box Office #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[King, Gerads and Shaner’s Highly Anticipated ‘Strange Adventures’ Secures DC’s Black Label Treatment #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
