<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The reason we launched our #HASHTAG# campaign earlier this year because of the staggering amount of people who… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 600,000 members of so-called ‘Generation Rent’ are facing an “inevitable catastrophe” of homelessness whe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Too many people are stuck with the impossible choice between taking time off sick when unwell and being able to pay bills or buy…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Mental, physical or financial #HASHTAG# - we can help current &amp; former bank workers with all of these - #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poor families are deeper in poverty than they were seven years ago and the umber of children in poverty has doubled… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Money doesn't need to define you, but it does help, and unfortunately we need it to live! If you need support with money…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Millions of customers could save up to a £1bn a year on the cost of their landline, broadband, TV and mobile packag… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Working-age carers have a higher rate of poverty than those with no caring responsibilities, and women of working a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the mercury drops across the country, some people receiving benefits experiencing particularly cold weather in t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Relatives of a man who starved to death after his benefits were stopped are demanding action to prevent future deat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[National charity #USER# has launched its latest digital innovation for unpaid carers in a drive to recognise the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: "Don’t patronise and advise on a condition you know nothing about. Don’t take up spaces reserved for disabled people. And don’t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: What does it mean to be middle class? #USER#, director of #USER#, knows the struggle of identity. #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The average amount that Housing Benefit is capped by is £51 a week, it is also around £51 for Universal Credit caps.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mental health nurse Nicole Richards had been renting privately for years and had always found it impossible to save… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you care for 20 hours or more a week, you have a higher risk of being in poverty than if you care for fewer than… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Northern Ireland Housing Executive put the number of rough sleepers at 38 . Of these, 16 were in Belfast – up f… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The impact of poverty in 21st Century Britain is the focus of a new exhibition which showcases those trying to help… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Families already living under the poverty line have been pushed deeper into poverty since 2012 says #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Our interactive map helps bereaved people to find a funeral director local to them, who is committed to being open and t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: At #USER# Race to the Top and hearing some zingers:  'The ability to avoid discomfort is the very definition of…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The #USER# warns the poverty gap jumped 30% between 2012/13 and 2017/18 - which "should sound alarm bells for a go… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If the Government wants to “level up Britain”, as Boris Johnson has repeatedly vowed, then they need to break “the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thousands of vulnerable people on low incomes – particularly those with mental illness – are at risk of destitution… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poor housing, poverty and isolation all contribute to the experience of pain and desperately need to be addressed w… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[80.1% of food banks reported that picking up parcels from the food bank was the most common way for people to recei… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17-year-old Rachel Ojo - chair of the UK's Youth Parliament - is calling on the government to do more to tackle pov… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The amount of money being paid to private accommodation providers by councils (for temporary accommodation services… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People who are homeless experience some of the worst health outcomes in England and die 30 years earlier than the g… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reductions in interest rates have led to cheaper mortgages, reducing poverty rates for people buying with a mortgag… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 properties were repossessed every day in Q2 2019 in England and Wales, or one every 1 hour and 40 minutes says #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The housing minister says that there’ll be more money for a fund considered important in tackling homeless, if the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The weekly household income is £100 a week less for people who are caring says #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Being impoverished #HASHTAG# costs you more to live #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT #USER#: Being impoverished #HASHTAG# costs you more to live #USER# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: This is exactly why great charities like #USER# are so important, so that people can navigate UC &amp; get the suppor…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.#USER# in England and Wales dealt with 2,616 debt issues every day in the year to December 2019.  Help wi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In-work poverty is a condition that can be hard to escape. This matters a great deal for social renters who – with… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# You can read more about what the quality of work means for our health on our website: #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over 60% of independent food banks required new clients to have a referral from a third-party agency but most indic… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.#USER# has rounded-up some top tips to help your Universal Credit application and jobcentre visits to go as… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Millions of households will see their energy bills fall in April after the energy regulator, Ofgem, lowered the def… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Concerns have been raised over "deposit-free" renting being mis-sold to tenants who do not understand the costs inv… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Of the almost £1.1 billion spent on temporary accommodation by councils in England last year – 86% of it went to pr… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 in 10 households that have their benefits capped are single-parent families, at 66% of single-parent capped house… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Between April 2018 and March 2019, councils spent almost £1.1 billion on temporary accommodation – a rise of 9% in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Families and campaigners have demanded a public inquiry after a government watchdog found that at least 69 suicides… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["My big worry is that when the money for mum’s care runs out then I’ll be made homeless as the council say they won… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One in five people in the UK is now living in poverty: working single parents are experiencing the sharpest rise, b… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The benefits freeze is set to end in April – with MPs agreeing a rise in line with inflation yesterday – but charit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new study shows that families already living under the poverty line have been pushed deeper into into destitution… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you over State Pension age and struggling financially? Help may be available to you through Pension Credit.  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: We take a holistic approach to applications for support, taking time to look at all the factors in a case &amp; how best t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Underneath a constant in-work poverty rate is a tremendous amount of churn: half of those living in in-work poverty… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Over the next 12 months, the Government will be making changes to welfare benefits &amp; other policies.  Universal Credit…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The energy price cap will fall from £1,179 to £1,162 for the summer period (April to September), due to lower whole… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.#USER# is calling on the government to:  - Uprate the value of frozen benefits CPI +2% for four years - R… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Across Scotland, the average amount of Pension Credit people are missing out on is £52 per week, without taking int… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The benefits freeze finally comes to an end in April. Find out what the new rates are.  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# essential household items is a key part of the #HASHTAG#  Get help here:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The overall scale of annual temporary accommodation placements has oscillated within a fairly narrow band over rece… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Government is facing pressure to reform benefits rules after it was found that some older people are at risk of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one should experience destitution – more than 1.5 million people were destitute at some point during 2017, inclu… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At the moment, an annual levy is imposed on gas and electricity bills to fund renewables such as offshore wind. The… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Are you caring for a child with a life-limiting condition and facing financial hardship as a result of a life-changing…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: An absolute pleasure to discuss an investigation on #HASHTAG# with Anthony Amis #USER#, #HASHTAG# in Stoke with Lia…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Free school meals could be made available to all children regardless of what their parents earn, if new rules go ah… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The number of people sleeping on our streets has more than doubled since 2010 to an estimated 4,677 people. The num… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[75% of independent food banks started operating in the past 9 nine years, with over a third opening over 2012 to 20… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A new report has revealed the extent in which poor health can be caused by rough sleeping – as well as stressing th… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The NHS worker, who lives in Bristol with his daughter Laura, says the DWP didn't inform him that his payments woul… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Over the last five years, poverty rates have risen for children and pensioners. Poverty rates are highest in London… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# are immensely grateful to have supporters like Daniel. The 11-year-old spend his pocket money on a trolley lo…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sixth former Tahiyat launched her "Smile Bags" campaign to bring a little cheer to the homeless people she sees on… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As the recent BBC documentary showed, Universal Credit can function as a punitive system that drives people into cr… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one should be in poverty, especially for more than two years – but currently 7% of individuals have been in pove… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Charity #USER# have posted pictures online of touching notes they found from a homeless man, after he recei… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Net lending to individuals and housing associations in the UK grew by £140 million a day in November 2019 says #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dozens of suicides of benefit claimants have been investigated by the government in recent years, it has emerged as… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[336 people a day were declared insolvent or bankrupt in England and Wales in July to September 2019. This was equiv… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thousands of people in Scotland are struggling to keep up with their energy bills, new research by #USER# h… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[93% of households that had their benefits capped include children, with the figure at 94% for Housing Benefit, and 92% for Universal Credit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 1997, over a third of households lived in council housing, compared with just one in 10 today. The number of hom… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["This winter has definitely been the toughest I have faced since I've been on the streets. The weather has been hor… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The DWP said that at Christmas only 69 cases in the Universal Credit managed migration pilot had moved across – wit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carers who have to sleep in their workplace, in case they are needed overnight, should be paid minimum wage for the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: At Race to the Top conference, #USER# talks about the role of white leaders in overcoming white privilege. #HASHTAG#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Borrowers paid a staggering £140 million a day in interest in November 2019 says #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[290,000 households have been capped at some point between April 2013 and November 2019.   220,000 have had their Ho… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The benefit freeze finally ends on 6 April 2020 after a decade of cuts and caps. Here's the full list of new benefi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The £73 standard weekly allowance for universal credit, the government’s flagship benefit claimed by 2.3 million pe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Thank you to #USER# for raising the issue of #HASHTAG# in the House of Commons this week.   Pension Credit is…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Children who have only known or lived intermittently in poverty up to the age of 14 are more likely to suffer from… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Poverty amongst older people is rising – now affecting 1 in 5 older people in Wales.   £214 million of Pension Cred… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Social worker’s in-work poverty rates remain elevated compared to non-SRs even when we look at households with the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Today we're launching Learning for Living, a free digital tool which boosts confidence and skills amongst unpaid carers.   It…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do you want to help tackle UK poverty? We are looking for a Safeguarding Officer who does #HASHTAG#  Apply here:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Although growing employment has protected some working-age adults from poverty, in-work poverty has risen, because… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Any charities looking to refer cases? #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# #USER#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Today, #USER# appeared to agree with High Court that it's an 'injustice' to deny bereavement benefits to cohabiting p…]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
