<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Axcept – The fastest automated UI testing tool #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mojo Vision's miniature display actually made me excited about AR          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Unintended Consequences of IoT (Internet of Things) Deployment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emerging Collaborative Tribes, Networks and Collectives  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three Tips on Organizational Change #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lazy Jar – It's like a gym where you only pay if you don't go #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This War of the Worlds uses holograms, giant Martians to make you feel tiny          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Video Friday: Robot Blows Up a Land Mine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Trust Can Be A Competitive Advantage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Optimization Chip Tackles Machine Learning, 5G Routing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hubble Sees a Galaxy Bucking the Trend via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TunnelHero – The world's most personal and secretive VPN service #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ProveSource – Turn your website into a busy place using social proof #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Human Reflexes Help MIT's HERMES Rescue Robot Keep Its Footing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Now sort out Stamp Duty Boris so we can get the property market moving!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CoinsCrate – Track cryptocurrency prices, markets, volumes and much more #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Even if You Predict the Future Perfectly You Still Won’t Capitalize On It #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don Draper is (Finally) Dead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# – Send spoiler anonymously over call and WhatsApp to your friends as GoT airs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Proxyman – A modern and intuitive HTTP debugging proxy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The New ‘Golden Age’ of Medicine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[City Life Awaits Drones in Final Year of NASA Research via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Klokki for Mac – Rules-based automatic time-tracking #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Storyling – Learn Languages With Captivating Stories #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Local – Hyperlocal Quora with focus on small businesses and freelancers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DeepMind Deploys Self-taught Agents To Beat Humans at Quake III #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Branding Compass – Quickly discover the best words, colors, fonts and visuals for your brand #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PowerPrice – An intelligent price and inventory management system #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jezero Crater, Mars 2020's Landing Site via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lead Pilot – Get interest leads for your business on autopilot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Docompile – Automate documents easily using a powerful API #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# – Enabling personalized micro conversions through conversational interfaces #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best Father's Day gifts to combat dad bod          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Watch Active review: A cheaper, round-faced alternative to the Apple Watch          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NuCode – No code community and product discovery app #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cronhooks – Schedule one time or recurring webhooks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# – Turn static websites into web apps #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matterbase 2.0 – An better time-based workflow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Produck – Work management platform for PMs and Makers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John F. Kennedy and the Race to the Moon via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Combining lean startup and agile with a design-led approach reduces business risk #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fine art of inNOvation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are You Ready for the Biggest Economic and Social Shift of the Past 100 Years? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UC Berkeley's "Hyper-Aggressive Pogo-Stick" Robot Now Works Outdoors #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remindee – Remind &amp; convert past visitors, months after their visit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Listouts – Out your lists as social proof to boost conversions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One Thing You Won’t Find in Any Book on Entrepreneurship #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PerShop – Shop All Your Favorite Brands in One App #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Varjo XR-1 is an AR headset so fast, Volvo test drives cars while wearing it          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carrom – HR, Benefits and Payroll for remote teams #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SLS Begins Insulation Process for Booster Segments for Second Flight via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top 20 Innovation Articles of April 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Intuition is Essential for Innovation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Travel at (Nearly) the Speed of Light via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abyssale – Automatically generated banners ads #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Testvox – Provides mobile app functionality, performance and compatibility tests #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smooper – Connect, Consult &amp; Hire Social Media Experts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Video Friday: This Robot Is Learning to Slice Onions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ezylead – All your sales leads in one app #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zenpost – A content marketing team in your pocket #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mindwave – Journal for founders &amp; makers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Foster an Appetite for Risk by Using Ambiguity as a Resource #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HQ – Eliminate tab switching to boost productivity #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Digital Transformation Is Human Transformation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Day Into Night on the International Space Station via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spocket – Dropshipping marketplace serving 30,000 merchants #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the HyQReal Robot Pull an Airplane #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Instantly Design – Magical AI-powered logo maker #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# now sort out stamp duty Boris please!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[signmesh – Collect and share knowledge to build the culture of innovation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: How will brands create value in the new consumer ecosystem? #USER# explores. #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keyn – Securely login without remembering a single password #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Watch comparison: Series 3 vs. Series 4 which should you buy?          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# – The easiest way to organize your work, team and projects #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Innovation Goes Wrong, We Shouldn’t Blame Technology, But Ourselves #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grow – The platform for personal Growth #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[iRobot Completely Redesigns Its Floor Care Robots With New m6 and s9 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Affable StoryTeller – Clip and Save Instagram stories before they disappear #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gist – Turn data into browsable, interactive visualizations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AlgoDaily – Software career strategy and interview questions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Innovation is the Means, Not an End in Itself #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Preface – Find freelancers and get estimates for your project #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surround Sound - Orion Service Module for Artemis 1 Undergoes Acoustic Tests via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HodlBot – Create any crypto portfolio, backtest performance, execute it automatically #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: What. a. win!  England have beaten New Zealand to reach the #USER# final 🙌🌹  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# https…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smartlook – Qualitative analytics for websites and mobile apps #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Art of Physician Entrepreneurship #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buddy the Social Robot is Somehow Not Dead Yet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boooom – Design Management and Leadership Jobs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Brand New Logo – Online logo maker that creates professional logos for everyone #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secalerts – Alerts of vulnerabilities (CVEs) that match your software stack #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[nReal's Magic Leap-like AR smartglasses cost $499, arriving by end of year          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA is Going Green, in Space via NASA #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon is working on a wearable that can read your emotions, report says          #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tanzania’s Homegrown Drone Industry Takes Off on Bamboo Wings #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiny Robots Carry Stem Cells Through a Mouse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Is there something wrong with your app at the moment? Can't add my flight?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[StudioYou – Scheduling, sales, and marketing tool for fitness studios and gyms #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[International Intrapreneurship Conference at Orange #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Convertify – Convert your website to an app (iOS &amp; Android) #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
