<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[the United States senate is the most ruthless gang on the planet.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[some of the faces I see on here would stop an eight day clock.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[when they passed out the brains were most of you hiding under the table.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[where have all the articles gone about the dark and deep state and the shadow government and the military industrial complex,,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One-third of Americans don't believe 6 million Jews were murdered during the Holocaust #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I will be talking about the modern evolution of the mind, the new culture, the new… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I will talk about why the world is the way it is and how we can change it working… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[why are so many of you brain dead, is it the water and food and poor air quality or what, I am asking you all to he… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight we are going to cover the war powers act with Mr Ken Scott, and so... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Esoteric practice is the only thing that will save us.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kiler and I want to meet others who are esoteric.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adrenochrome &amp; Child Protective Services: Trafficking, Killing &amp; Selling the Blood of Our Children - DC Dirty Laund… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An original piece by Kiler Davenport - Wondering #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[most of you will never escape to the esoteric inner core.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[all of you pent up lame brains . hated hat show we did last night .]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[one of a creative work by Kiler Davenport. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[all of you are swimming in weapons of mind destruction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the Lords over this land or in full command.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[APRI Presents Kiler Davenport needs co host for the round table, pm me if you are interested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how does it make you feel to be a slave to the state and in complete bondage to this new world order.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Phil and I took the chopper up last night a little drunk of course, or at least I was.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[when the grid goes down and all is lost you will be all by yourself, and where will your children be, where will yo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this show tonight just might save you life or the lives of loved ones, the call in number is 646-716-8423, we go li… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[you want your children to be in special needs class just feed them sugar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the deep state is in full control of the United States and all of you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I am going to have Ken Scott on air and it will be a very powerful show, e will be… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how many of you have ever reached the esoteric zone.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we have developed a program to override fb censorship and get these post out there all over the world, will you work with us on this.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[sugar in vast amounts will cripple you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the democrats are digging themselves a very deep and dangerous hole and they will all fall off in it very soon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[why are most mof you so afraid to work on plans to over come this new word order that has enslaved you are your chi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# tonight we will be covering the matrix and what it is , we will talk about escaping the mat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how many of you will help us turn this country around.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are looking for shock jocks at the station, pm me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight we will be talking about the war powers act and much more with Ken Scott, we... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we have the bat cave rigged with explosives and two other exits,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Just uploaded "APRI BROADCASTING 2019 PRESENTS: KILER DAVENPORT LIVE WITH HOST KILER D..." to #USER# #URL# Tune in now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this is my second page in case I am blocked on fb, please donate what you can, and help us raise this money for my… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I will be talking about the lesser Gods and the main Gods and how strange all of t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this impeachment process will work out perfectly for the president.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[most of you cannot shake your nwo programing and indoctrination, the propaganda has worn you down to clueless numbs… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[when you shoot, make sure you shoot to kill.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kiler will be going into surgery on Oct 24th, and we all need to call the hospital and keep them on their toes. I w… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight we will talk about what is going on in the middle east and what you should be doin… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[between the programming, indoctrination and propaganda , America is on its knees.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[our constitution has become nothing but an old worn out piece of paper, our bill of rights is no more, how can we s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kiler is trying to give you the wisdom to stay alive during these coming events.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tonight I will talk about the millions and millions of men and women who are attracted to young kids and why. I hav… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are looking for smart witty fun and exciting personalities for the talk show pm me if interested.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this is a very important test, how many of you can see this post.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[new name for the new station,   ( crusty balls broadcasting ). what do you think.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are going live in 2 min, the call in number is 646-716-8423. call in if you want to chat about anything.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“It takes 10 years to become a master.” - Kiler Davenport #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[yall come on over and enjoy. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[fighting with this new world order is not about winning or loosing, it is about how you play the game.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I am going to explore the mind of God, esoteric universe, and human communication,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[most of you will die in the first three weeks of a grid down event, or be killed , you have to plan, are you locked… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my doctor took me off Xanax cold turkey and its killing me]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have developed a very diabolical plan along with Philip Anderton and we would love to have you all on the mission… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tonight I will cover how all religions are myth and fantasy with a twist of truth, I will cover the reasons that Am… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are looking for a co host that is not afraid to tackle any issues or subject.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have been targeted , I am a TI, they are trying to make me crazy and I am fighting it as much as I can, they are… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tonight on the show I will be covering religion, the most powerful scam on earth. the call in number is 646-716-842… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I will roll the dice and see where we go, I go live at 6 pm pacific time, the call… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tell me the truth from the bottom of your heart, what are we as a people, as a nation doing to overcome this new wo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# In recent years, an ever-increasing number of alarming rumors have been... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are looking for co host who are not afraid to tackle the really hard issues.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this post goes out to all of you clueless flag waivers and ignorant voters who still believe in the electoral syste… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[stop poisoning your children with sugar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[why are you all so afraid to talk about the millions of adults that like to pleasure themselves with kids from 12 to 17.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[you ladies should tune in to the show, we defend women on the show against MGTOW ( men going their own way ) its re… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are looking for very liberal out of the box co host.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[most of you seen clueless and brainless to the dangers we are all facing.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are building one of the most powerful alternative radio networks in the nation.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we seek no rewards for building this super station.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I will talk about how my doctor took me off Xanax cold and hard, and how I am suff… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I am just going to rant about life and living, we will have some fun, the call in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight I will talk about the top gun 25 on the move group and our goals and objectives. I… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[does anyone want to go live on air with me today, its my day off but I feel good and want to go live, if you want t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[because of our intense investigative reporting fb has closed the gate as far as folks seeing our post, let me know… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#   tonight John and I will talk about the power of one, and the... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#   do you ever feel like a little fish on the end of a big hook, will guess what you are, yo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[if you want to feed your tumor just give it sugar.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight we will talk about why the world is in the state it is in and what we as a people… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[can anyone see this post please respond.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are about 30 minutes from our bat cave with enough guns and ammo to hold off an army. we are ready for the momen… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One of Kiler Davenports art works. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I am dealing with the walking dead here, zombies, sheeple people, the massive passive, there have to be some of you… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we are here for your guns, oh really how far up your ass do you want it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[why don'y most of you seem concerned that the new world order is enslaving us all.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the same clueless shit is on my feed today.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I have come to bring you out of your deep sleep and give back to you what is truly yours.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[how many of you are stupid enough to let them round you up and put you in reeducation camps.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Create a free business account. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL#  tonight we will talk about the possibility of escaping the matrix, the call in number is 6… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we have the tools to set this massive ship on the right course.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[if you have to be taken make sure and take about 25 - 30 of these mother fuckers with you. feet first.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[don't you all grasp that fb is rigging this platform to eave the seeds of propaganda and corruption, the clueless a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[we have no freedom here to talk to the world, they have us confined to a very small space.they  ( fb ) do not want… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my show goes live in 42 min, the call in number is 646-716-8423]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
