<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Joshua Generation #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lasers etch a 'perfect' solar energy absorber #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tomb Containing Three Generations of Warrior Women Unearthed in Russia]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elon Musk promises 'awesome' update to Neuralink brain implant]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Texas mom who wanted to ‘transition’ 7-year-old son to girl loses again in court]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter Executive Revealed to Be 'Psyops' Soldier Linked to Spreading Disinformation Across Social Media: 'A Threat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CIA Files Reveal Claim Nazis Had 2,500mph Flying Saucer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RED ALERT: Internet to be “policed” by communist China under new UN crackdown targeting online speech]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hal Turner Radio Show - The Horror of China's Bio-Weapon Virus, Caught on Camera. This May Be you within 14 days .… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Belgian Mayor, Working Against EU Pedophile Ring, Found Dead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Superstar DJ Avicii Found Dead After Exposing Pedophile Ring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Prepare You The Way of The Lord #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Gates predicted Coronavirus-like outbreak in 2019 film]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus causes Chinese economy to stop #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Helen Sharman: 'Aliens exist and could be here on Earth' - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The End Of Your World Is The Beginning Of Mine #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China stops sales of cough medicine to flush out coronavirus patients - Strange Sounds #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Majesty of the Lord Jesus Christ #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - God's Plan #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enormous swarm of locusts 37 MILES long and 23 miles wide sweeps through east Africa causing devastation – The Sun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hebrew inscription on a jar could redraw borders of ancient Israel - Archaeology - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Geopolitical Deployment of Biological Weapons - Global ResearchGlobal Research - Centre for Research on Globali… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon Alexa Tells Woman To Kill Herself To Save The Planet! - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Mysterious New "SARS-Like Virus" That Is Killing People In China Has Now Spread To Japan #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China's police now have laser rifles that can 'set a whole person on fire' up to a kilometre away]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elon Musk says an 'awesome' Neuralink update is coming soon - CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Winning Team #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York UN Office Recruits Paramilitary Troops for 'Disarmament' and 'Reintegration' of US Civilians - David Harri… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virus-hit Wuhan has two laboratories linked to Chinese bio-warfare program - Washington Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Russ Dizdar, Are Christians Less Wrong About Ritual Abuse? |440| - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DragonFire Laser Directed Energy Weapon system - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Atlanta police begins no-chase policy effective immediately #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“D-Wave Quantum Computer Systems founder Geordie Rose says to watch out for a "Tsunami of Demons" coming through so… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YouTube is censoring Transgender Regret Videos! An LGBTQ lobby is reporting vids to stop awareness! - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney introduces kids to world of demons, witchcraft in new ‘The Owl House’ show]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google critic, 66, now suggests his wife's fatal car crash was not an accident]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Warning Signs of a Spiritual Narcissist #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mother Teresa's Charity Investigated for Child Trafficking #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spain explosion: Huge blast kills one after 'chemical emergency' at Tarragona factory]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Native American Women Are Being Sold into the Sex Trade on Ships Along Lake Superior - VICE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[San Francisco: A Dystopian Nightmare of Addiction, Homelessness and Criminality #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Russia won't have gay marriages as long as I am president, vows Vladimir Putin]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Now Faith #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike Pence Has Secret Closed-Door Meeting With Pope Francis, Receives 'Angel Of Peace' Medallion And Signed 'World… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chernobyl shocker as fungi that eats radiation found inside nuclear reactor]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Is Mystery Russian Spacecraft Cosmos 2542 Suddenly Stalking a U.S. Spy Satellite? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ron Paul Institute for Peace and Prosperity : Will This Billionaire-Funded Think Tank Get Its War With Iran? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twenty-three nations embrace Trump peace plan, 7 in Middle East #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fiona Barnetts Statement Ritual Abuse In Australia Reaching the top of the Pryamid #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hal Turner Radio Show - Iran hacked the "Federal Depository" website ... posted a warning (Prelude to FALSE FLAG BA… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RUMOURS OF WAR: Thousands Of Pro-Iranian Militia Storm US Embassy In Baghdad Shouting "Death To America" As Preside… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5G PROGRAMMED to KILL ALL LIFE - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mom who ‘hanged her two kids and had sex with family dog’ says children ‘wanted to die’ ahead of trial for murder –… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Remains of Ariz. Girl, 11, Are Found in Parents' Attic After She'd Been Missing for 2 Years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CORONAVIRUS is a Patented Virus - USAHITMAN Conspiracy News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hubei sets up over 300 5G base stations - Xinhua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - Go With The Wind #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Epstein investigation 'stinks to no end' – Lionel - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus - Cats and dogs ‘thrown from tower blocks’ in China after fake news rumours animals are causing spread #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats Going After President Trump For Corruption Is Like A Skunk Accusing A Rabbit Of Having Bad Breath! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kundalini Demons Invading Churches -Beware of Unholy Laughter, Drunk in the “Spirit”, and Other Strange Manifestati… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Servant of the LORD: Isaiah 53:1-12 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UFO sightings across US 'will rise in 2020' with creation of Space Force - Daily Star #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nigerian pastor who praised God in ransom video beheaded after refusing to deny Christ - The Christian Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA Admits Space &amp; Planets Are Fake! "Is All CGI" Meet The Artists - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Giddyup!’: US airport security agent pulls Native American woman’s braids like reins]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - SCADs #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Big Wobble : Monster Bomb Cyclone: Storm "Dennis The Menace" Hurricane Force Colossus To Rival The Most Intense… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The race to Mars: USA, Europe, Russia, China and the UAE are all headed for the Red Planet in 2020]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Snowden says don't use Wifi, I explain why - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The North Atlantic has turned into a virtual Bomb Cyclone express lane - Strange Sounds #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Putin says Robots are coming to steal your soul - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are UFOs Real? - Government's UFO Program - Government Secrets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Entire Russian Government Has Resigned, Reports Say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hallmark to cut 400 jobs weeks after conservative boycott over kissing brides ad - The Christian Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Common Denominator #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Father's Business #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China's blatant propaganda: Coronavirus patients party it up with dancing - WND #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Rima Laibow - The Globalist Agenda: The Great Culling - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Out For Something Incredibly Nefarious With Globalists Openly Pushing Plan B To Cool The Planet In This Day A… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China Death Count Tops 1,000 As Masked President Xi Warns 'Prepare For Long &amp; Grim' Virus Battle]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wireless Radiation Produces Antibiotic Resistant Bacteria, Increases Pathogenic Bacteria – Huna Varuna #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The Day After You Die #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Muslim Teen Accused of Starting Aussie Grass Fire Laughs As He Leaves Court on Tuesday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The End Of Smartphones: Working Prototype Of Smart Contact Lens Unveiled]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[POPE BOWS DOWN TO THE ORDER OF THE ILLUMINATI - KISS FEETS AND HANDS - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wildfire Jihad: Muslims in Australia Among Nearly 200 Arsonists Who Set Fires - DC Clothesline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grandmother’s prayer closet survives powerful tornado that flattened home, killed many - The Christian Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google will ‘de-rank’ RT articles to make them harder to find – Eric Schmidt — RT World News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5G LED GENOCIDE COVER UP IS GETTING UNCOVERED - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patent Approved for Anti-Gravity Spacecraft using Mass Reduction &amp; Non-Conventional Propulsion « Helios Journal™ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Killer 5G warning: Expert warns superfast broadband could cause CANCER in humans - Daily Star #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Vatican’s Alliance With China: More Evil Than We Thought #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5G Network Uses Same EMF Waves as Pentagon Crowd Control System #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nuclear waste recycled into diamond batteries with 'near-infinite power']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# - The White Horse Rider #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Julianne Hough writhes and groans while getting BIZARRE energetic treatment]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Paula White: Christians Must Pray That “Satanic Pregnancies” End in Miscarriage]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Electrosensitivity: 'I didn't believe people had it, then it happened to me' - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI Busts Massive Fentanyl Ring Running Out of Dept of Consumer and Regulatory Affairs in D.C. #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
