<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yes be on the show.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah greg is going to block the door. want her to look at his face when he kisses me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# never seen a girl that doesnt wear under shirt. i  wear one under my school blouse]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# while cam going to be wearing givenchy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ciji has a shape. ciji doesnt have a boyish body. move on she doesnt want you and youre mad about it. dont date actors.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# only if you guys come meet. only if  khloe ciara kim kylie kendall olivia sees my face.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ciji is going to do chores by helping her mommy in the kitchen. ciji is a seapup. move on ben thank you thank you thank you]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# forgot im roasting some frogs. having a boiling pot. seafood boil chicken pig feet potatoes turkey necks. corn]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# dont think we are going to see yourself on say yes to the dress. get your dead mo to sow you a dress.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yes im a pup. my body not changing for nobody. ben needs to worry about his bust open pee hole. his dick don't even work.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# cam need to air his dick out and get his head straight.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ciji going to pull out all of her teeth lay it out where the bed suppose to go at robert's house. shes not staying w you!!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yall going to watch the video. say something positive. she got good grades. she speaks so well. she speaks several languages]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# i know my parents john and traci is giving me tlc. how you ask? we go to the fairs and state fairs. have a great time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# cam would take kia and that little girl to a fair. all would be doing is walking around the whole fair the whole time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# im going to post it too. talk sports net. but let me shoot this marvel global initiative video w misss unionjack'd first.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# unicorn onsie when i go trick or treating.yes participate ciji. be on the show..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# kia cecil the dead mo wouldnt even hold his degree in their hands. they wouldnt do it. but they came for the cake.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah 3 guys. whose the 3rd old guy. see you when im 15 in two yrs. cam robert and i are enemies.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# he didnt kiss kia during chosen whatever.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ben is a joke ciji would be a jester if she takes ben seriously so will I. Know you get it that in fact I'm on Ciji side.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# i was raise in the projects. we all had a draw full of under shirts. thats a damn shame.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# even if kia had her own money he still wouldnt aloow them to buy food or drink. maybe share a drink. they just content.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# going to the library to read some stories w the kids. got to shoot a video w my uncle joe about assualt. hear my story]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# one problem after another. when i threw glass at you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# take over the garden. im going to prepare for winter harvest. 3 dates..]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# coming to see how that little girl. if they have time. my cousin and i might go to a spin class.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# that foot is going to go straight up khloe's broken pussy hole. yes i'm not mad cuz i'm a seapup.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# hear about me being shook and being harass. you know mickey the day i puked on his italian leather]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# my name is ciji agreed. i came to an agreement for those folk who are concern. i agreed on ciji.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# she has a freaky daddy/uncle cover her titties up cameron. im going to make a phone call.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# no im not  fucking cam . cecil is a peeping time and a freak. little nasty ass freak.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# you know all i have to is think of the photo of kia wearing the same dress that she wears on the stage of the strip club]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# To the point where she won't survive. I'm not bluffing. My job is to wake Ciji up and rest in peace.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# im not doing that. im just unbuckling his pants.just the buckle. hes not the only one w that inside his pants.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# a boil pot as in a sichuan boiling pot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# not fucking mickey thx for the suggestion,]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# no ones seeing my face. im not suppose to meet anybody.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Like I said if Khloe steps foot in my backyard. My foot is going to be so far up her cat. It's going to be painful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah im just so weird. tee tee want to talk to you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# she practically naked under her under armor shirt. she dont even had a bralette.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# She's not going to be ugly or not have a shape. She's a seapup!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# my brother going to dj on thursday. pal and i going to perform our spoken word. dont forget to watch my parents interview.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# cam in love for the very first time in a long time. since that prom date.hes not going to kiss kia in public.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# drugs charges he had who's serving 30 yrs to life out and getting a job instead of harassing ciji.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# i wear under shirts under my uniform blouse. i dont know who doesnt. ciji aint slow cuz of her shape.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# could only imagine cecil fucking a girl in a fema trailer. if my pinned take me to a community of fema trailers.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# robert that ol selective friendly ass bitch should be focus on advocating getting those addicts that had the exact same]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# there's no such thing as kim giving me the eye. If anything weird happens to Ciji. Then I won't be resting in peace.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# why why im not changing my name.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# so she could know that he wont have that look with her mo. of course she going to look.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yeah im dumb as fuck.  lets date old guys. kia got assualted twice. yeah they was rough w her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ben youre going to move on thank you. shes not shape like bull dagger. think for yourself. dont think 4 me. too powerful]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# if they sees my face they become presence so to speak. i'm never changing my name.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# that little girl needs to wear an under shirt or an bralette. you going to turn her be careful.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# now i gotta deal w kia not applying for fema to get an apartment to have just so fat sloppy ass junior to ho up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# in two yrs. my 15.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# the staples wouldnt hurt so much if she had a under shirt. little girl walking around with no under shirt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# might be wearing sweat pants.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# no wearing a bralette to cover her titties up.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# so why you so happy. if we have time yeah im going to kiss him. we visiting her school.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# just want to hear him say kiss me. say get off your knees. dont worry we broke up. hes not the only one w that dick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# no telling what cecil did to her the first time.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# im not weird. stop calling me out my name.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# my name is going to always and forever be ciji so i slapped his wife and told her to keep my name out her mouth. wasnt enough]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# was blocking my way to see my paw paw. going to the mid west. see my brother and i. then in florida.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# i want him to be right there when i tell and show cuz i got proof of him laughing at my brother getting upset over his toy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# cam dont have the sense to let it be just him and i. have cecil coming in the room. cecil and cam ran a train on her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# my first name ciji isnt going to change. believe that!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# flying back w my cousin i think. going to have lunch w that little girl daddy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ben is a joke. no i dont take him serious. im not going to have a flat ass cause im not attractive to him. move on ben]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# If Khloe ever sees my face shes going to be kicked so far up in her pussy. and its going to hurt I grant you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# she ain't getting on no rides she aint getting no stuff animal. he definitely aint buying any food for her.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ciji aint turning into a boy. just cuz you mad. go to kmart get that girl a couple of bralettes. wont boys looking.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# which its the truth. so if you saying bad shit then you know im getting good grades.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ciji aint staying with you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Like I said Khloe or whomever aka Olivia Your stupidity isn't worth the risk. Ciji is going to wake up Catholic.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# shes the cream of the crop. ciji is as fine as wine. no she doesnt have a new look. ciji has a beautiful shape.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# my name is going to match my teeth. agreed.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# yep my older autistic brother is talking. got jimmy.  andy interview on sunday cuz they seen my brother. then halftime]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# those halter maxi dress. yeah she did. she wore that dress.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# shes a seapup. thank you ben for moving on.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# that little girl bare breasted.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# shes not going to have a boy shape ben thank you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# mr robert needs to fix a crackhead teeth so that could find them a job. cuz im going to have my interview on set.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# saying ciji dumb as fuck. dont worry about her. cam would do it.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# get her back when i staple a piece of paper on her bare chest.  kia shut up and share a cold drink w your baby at the fair]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# cam need to be booked for fraud. gentle giant the hell i was wrong.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# only if they come meet me.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# she has an uncle or daddy that have a problen looking at little girls. shes naked under her shirt.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# im going to post it after pookie toot your own horn.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# My foot would be so far up your broken ass cat. you dont know how much you're going to be in. Don't fucking try me!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# we going to celebrate lent. huh tee tee. going to have a mardi gras. going to meet the court off rex zulu and como]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# be eating frogs on a stick.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# call me by my first name ciji. where i met aaron if thats true. didnt pimp my sister]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# kiss cameron just pretending. if theres time going to talk to him to see where his head at.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# or thinking how cecil is going to convince cam to holler at my cousin aka claudia clawdeen big sister.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# or take a local zamba class.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# air his dick out after that escort. cant believe he put his dick into a bust open pussy. that girl bust open.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# chynasti is going to be born on dooms day. thats what is going to be like for kia.]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
