<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Says Tristan Thompson to Blame for Breakup, Not Jordyn Woods #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian Accuses Jordyn Woods of Lying About Tristan Thompson Cheating Scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Will Be Honored at the 2019 iHeartRadio Music Awards #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kristin Cavallari Tested Jay Cutler's Knowledge of Her Company &amp;amp; It Went Just as Hilarious as You'd Think #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Botched Doctors Have Heartbreaking News for One Famous Patient #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Nikki Bella's Romantic Date Night With Dancing With the Stars' Artem Chignvintsev #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Priyanka Chopra Became One of India's Leading Female &amp;quot;Trailblazers&amp;quot; #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle's Half-Sister Samantha Markle Slams Her in New Documentary #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katherine Helmond Dead: Who's the Boss? and Soap Star Was 89 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Do the Kids of the Grey's Anatomy Cast Think of Their Parents' Success? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medium Tyler Henry Responds to John Oliver's Recent Criticism of Hollywood Psychics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Fans Think Taylor Swift and Katy Perry Are Collaborating #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Travis Scott Deletes Instagram Account After Denying He Cheated on Kylie Jenner #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's Going on With The Real Housewives of Beverly Hills and a Dog Named Lucy? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amanda Bynes Checks Into Mental Health Facility After Relapse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers Reunite for First Song 5 Years After Split: Watch Them Perform &amp;quot;Sucker&amp;quot; #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Sends Heartfelt Message to Her Fans: You Saved My Life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Sends Heartfelt Message to Her Fans: You Saved My Life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande Denies She's Exploiting the LGBTQ Community By Performing at Manchester Pride #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Won't Believe How Much Money Property Brothers' Drew and Jonathan Scott Made Last Year #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[90 Day Fiancé Star Larissa Dos Santos Lima Reveals Her Boyfriend's Identity #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons' Dan Reynolds Reveals How Hateful Criticism Contributed to His Depression #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[90 Day Fiancé's Colt Johnson Has a Divorce Party at Strip Club After Larissa Split #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Jordyn Woods Told Khloe Kardashian and Kylie Jenner After Cheating Scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus and Liam Hemsworth Cuddle Up on the Red Carpet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here Are the Frontrunners to Be the Next Bachelorette: Inside the Decision-Making Process #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Kinney Likes a Shady Comment About Lady Gaga on Instagram #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Courteney Cox Recreates Classic Friends Scene in Real Life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matthew McConaughey's 3 Stylish Kids Make a Rare Red Carpet Appearance #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Justin Bieber Celebrated His 25th Birthday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will Gendry Take the Throne? Game of Thrones Star Joe Dempsie on Those Fan Theories... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bachelor Nation's Jade Roper and Tanner Tolbert Reveal Her Past Miscarriage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wynonna Earp Fans Rally to Save Show With Billboard in Times Square #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Married at First Sight's Danielle and Bobby Welcome Baby Girl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael J. Fox Opens Up About Health Scares Amid Parkinson's Disease Battle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordyn Woods Breaks Silence on Tristan Thompson Cheating Scandal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Fosters' Sherri Saum Arrives in Roswell, New Mexico With Secrets to Share #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Royal Bartender! Kate Middleton Pours a Pint of Beer in Ireland #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 Things to Know About Playboy's 2019 Playmate of the Year Jordan Emanuel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 100 Star Bob Morley Addresses &amp;quot;Fat Shame&amp;quot; on Social Media, Opens Up About Depression #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Affleck and Lindsay Shookus Step Out for a Stroll in NYC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the Kardashians Really Think of Jordyn Woods' Red Table Talk Interview #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teresa Giudice Tackles Affair Allusions, Joe Giudice Deportation on The Real Housewives of New Jersey Reunion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Miley Cyrus Infiltrate the RuPaul's Drag Race Work Room #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brie Larson Meeting a Mini Captain Marvel Will Make Your Day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Travis Scott Take an Adorable Phone Call From Kylie Jenner on Carpool Karaoke #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why the Jonas Brothers Needed to Break Up to Come Back Stronger--and Closer--Than Ever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grey's Anatomy Cast Tells All: Who's the Funniest? Who Cries the Easiest? Who Gets the Crankiest? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Esposito Sounds Off on the Bradley Cooper &amp;quot;Ha&amp;quot; Comments #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bella Thorne Splits From YouTube Star Tana Mongeau After 1 Year #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Says She Had ''One of the Best Days of Her life'' With Long Island Medium's Theresa Caputo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See What Tyler Henry Really Thinks About His Khloe Kardashian, Tristan Thompson &amp;amp; Jordyn Woods Prediction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You Have to See Nicki Minaj's $450,000 Rolls-Royce #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Real Housewives of Atlanta's Peter Thomas Arrested for Alleged Check Fraud #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Mayer Reveals the Intimate Thing He Must Do Every Day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the First Minute of Pretty Little Liars: The Perfectionists #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeran Reportedly Marries Cherry Seaborn in a Secret Winter Wedding Ceremony #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pink Shares Sweet Photo with Kids at First Show of New Tour #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Riverdale's Luke Perry Hospitalized After Stroke #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hailey Baldwin Sends Her ''Lover'' Justin Bieber a Sweet Message on His 25th Birthday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pink Shares Sweet Photo with Kids at First Show of New Tour #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's Pauly D Like You've Never Seen Him Before: Performing Ballet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bekah Martinez Shares Photo of &amp;quot;Beautiful Little Girl&amp;quot; One Month After Giving Birth #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jonas Brothers Reunite for First Song 5 Years After Split: Watch Them Perform &amp;quot;Sucker&amp;quot; #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brie Larson Is Our Fashion Hero! See Her Best Looks Before Becoming Captain Marvel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Jude Law Engaged? Girlfriend Phillipa Coan Sparks Rumors With Diamond Ring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Jenni &amp;quot;JWoww&amp;quot; Farley's Impossibly Tough Year #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Good Girls Stars Tease Season 2's &amp;quot;Sexy Twists&amp;quot; and Surprising Revelations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Selma Blair's Multiple Sclerosis Diagnosis Helped Her Find &amp;quot;Humility and Joy&amp;quot; #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ariana Grande and Ex-Boyfriend Big Sean Reunite 4 Years After Split #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[George H.W. Bush's Service Dog Sully Begins New Role at Military Hospital 3 Months After President's Death #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bachelor's Whitney Bischoff And Husband Ricky Angel Expecting First Child Together #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel, Madea, Dumbo &amp;amp; More: Which March Blockbuster Are You Going to See in Theaters First? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Maddie Poppe and Caleb Lee Hutchinson Are Hitting All the Right Notes After American Idol #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Something That Happened: The History of Bradley Cooper and Jennifer Esposito's Shockingly Short Marriage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Haley Struggles to Master Baby Basics in Modern Family Directed By Julie Bowen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zachary Quinto and Miles McMillan Break Up After Almost 6 Years Together #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Maddie Poppe and Caleb Lee Hutchinson Are Hitting All the Right Notes After American Idol #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordyn Woods' New World: How Her Entire Life Changed in an Instant #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Danielle Staub Postpones Wedding to Oliver Maier Days After Announcing Engagement #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You'll Never Guess Kate Middleton and Prince William's Nickname for Princess Charlotte #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Comes Love, Then Comes Marriage? Inside the Future of Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez's Red-Hot Romance #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fyre Festival's Andy King Spills New Details on That Infamous Oral Sex Scenario #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Reveals the Songs That Helped Her Heal After &amp;quot;Bad Breakups&amp;quot; #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sophie Turner and Jessica Chastain Harness Their Superpowers Dark Phoenix Trailer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Claims Amber Heart Cheated on Him With Elon Musk #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry's Latest Dad Joke Has Meghan Markle Laughing Out Loud #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Noah Centineo Was Finally on Good Trouble and Oh Boy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DJ Khaled to Host 2019 Nickelodeon Kids' Choice Awards: See the Complete List of Nominations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 of the Biggest Bombshells From Jordyn Woods' Red Table Talk Interview #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do It for the 'Gram! The LADYGANG Gals Prove You Can Take Envy-Inducing Social Media Snaps Anywhere #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Jonas Brothers Have Secret Concert Days After Releasing New Song #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Beauty Supplement Is the Reason People Can't Stop Complimenting Our Skin #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Won The Masked Singer? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Imagine Dragons' Dan Reynolds Reveals How Hateful Criticism Contributed to His Depression #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Files $50 Million Lawsuit Against Amber Heard #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zayn Malik Confuses Fans With Gigi Hadid Love Tweet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Game of Thrones Final Season Posters Revealed: Who Takes the Throne? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Shows Her Sporty Side During Belfast Visit With Prince William #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Reveals the Songs That Helped Her Heal After &amp;quot;Bad Breakups&amp;quot; #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
