<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Google gains confidence in RankBrain and deploys it for all search results #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YCombinator makes every SimCity player’s dream reality with new research initiative #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Misbah backs Amir to come good on England tour #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mystery Opponent Challenging Miz For IC Title On RAW, Cody Rhodes Confirmed As First PWG BOLA Entrant, WWE’s Camer… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Business News Roundup, June 28 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Steve Harvey’s Reaction to Kellie Pickler Almost Falling on ‘Celebrity Family Feud’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oculus discovers platform exclusives won’t wash with the VR community #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kevin Durant did Wizards a favor. Now they can focus on these free agents. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Historic Abortion Ruling May Not Bring New Clinics to Texas #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shark Week dropped its controversial Megalodon mockumentary — and fans are not happy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most underrated monsters of Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alphabet’s Sidewalk Labs plans to take over public transport in Columbus, Ohio #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EU will likely unite to avoid catching the UK’s Brexit fever, says former UK ambassador to the EU #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Went Home on ‘The Bachelorette’ Week 6? Spoilers Here! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Korea Box Office: ‘Independence Day’ Tops Slow Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No one gives a damn about Amazon ‘Dash’ buttons, but we’re about to get dozens more #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obduction revives the Myst experience for virtual reality #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scotland name Ruaidhri Smith for Afghanistan ODIs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hyperloop One gets an investment from Russia’s sovereign fund #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Game Of Thrones Always Wins Overwatch’s Play Of The Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordan Rodgers Says Relationship With Brother Aaron is ‘Complicated,’ Dishes on Behind-the-Scenes ‘Bachelorette’ D… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Salling Child Pornography Case Delayed as Former Glee Star Seeks New Representation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Citi North America nails predictive analytics for marketers: Art versus Science (VB Live) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Search still on for mystery driver #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The origin of the species: Orcs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adult Swim is premiering a new show on Vine before it hits the airwaves #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple Watch 2 Rumored To Feature GPS And Swim Tracking #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iniesta: Spain were too focused on Italy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There’s a Pokérap for Destiny’s exotics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyft Hires M&amp;A Banker Qatalyst Partners #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brexit could spell more trouble for Trump, who supported leaving #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brexit fears deal heavy blow to chemical stocks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Toro Rosso to run F3 racer Sette Camara in Silverstone F1 test #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Real Housewives of Orange County’s Kelly Dodd Reveals a Shocking Marital History #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Volkswagen to Pay $14.7 Billion to Settle Diesel Claims in U.S. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bachelorette Just Had Its Most Surprising Rose Ceremony This Season #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kendra Wilkinson-Baskett and Hank Baskett Reflect on Marital ‘Ups and Downs’ in Loving Anniversary Posts #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Activision gets dino-shooter Orion pulled from Steam over allegedly stolen assets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suge Knight Hits Chris Brown With a Lawsuit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[iPhone 7 in space black, Galaxy Note 7 fingerprint scanner &amp; more – Pocketnow Daily #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chelsea Handler Had Two Abortions When She Was 16: ‘I Happened to F–k Up Twice’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitch wants you to ‘Cheer’ your favorite broadcasters with premium emotes called ‘Bits’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gov. Brown, legislators to shake up state utilities commission #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calvin Harris Has Been Messaging THIS UK Reality Star As Things Heat Up Between Taylor Swift And Tom Hiddleston! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attention Asian startups: Apply for the Startup Battlefield at Disrupt SF! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Microsoft pays woman $10,000 for forcing Windows 10 installation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stephanie McMahon Makes Adweek ‘Most Powerful’ List, Who Was The Miz’s Mystery Opponent? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police find people from fatal crash mystery car #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Red Cross Apologizes For ‘Super Racist’ Pool Safety Poster #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oil, FX bounce from early lows as investors hunt for bargains #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More Clinton emails released, including some she deleted #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brad Neely’s weird Adult Swim cartoon premieres on Vine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This toy SpaceX rocket is (almost) as hard to land as the real Falcon 9 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hawks’ Budenholzer not guilty in DUI case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Project Fi update officially brings US Cellular band support #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6/27 Edition of RAW Rebellion: Talking Rollins ‘Shooting’ On Reigns, The Wyatts Haunting The New Day, Miz &amp; Demon … #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[iPhone 7 Rumored To Come In A ‘Space Black’ Finish #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zachary Quinto, Zoe Saldana Appreciate Rihanna’s ‘Star Trek’ Ballad After ‘Unimaginably Sad Week’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Slayer Shock is basically a procedurally generated Buffy The Vampire Slayer game. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mercedes DTM chief slams Audi’s Ekstrom over Norisring collision #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maradona calls on Messi to continue with Argentina #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nationals rally against Noah Syndergaard, batter Mets in series opener #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deadpool made after-the-trailer appearance in Japan just because he can #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Brexit may mean for British tech, and Silicon Valley #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miguel “Nacho” Mendoza from Chino Y Nacho Welcomes Son No. 4–and Shares Plenty of Heartwarming Pictures of the Bir… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: Google Will Release Its Own Non-Nexus Phone Later This Year #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kanye Who? Taylor Swift Escapes Nude Video Scandal In The UK #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Star Trek Beyond trailer features more Enterprise destruction and a new Rihanna track #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brexit: EU leaders are refusing to give Britain an easy way out #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pharmac poised to fund melanoma drug Keytruda subject to feedback #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ikea is recalling millions of dangerous dressers after 3 deaths #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hacker looks to sell 655,000 alleged patient healthcare records on the dark web #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘The Bachelorette’: Jordan Showed His ‘Entitled’ Side, Derek Cried (A Lot!) and Each Date was Awkwardly Boring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here’s what the European Union needs to do to avoid losing more member-states #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Agent admits ‘big club interest’ for AC Milan striker Bacca #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Eng-xit’ Sets A New Low For The National Team #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In 2002, Microsoft bought Rare. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s Crazy How Much Work Goes Into A Quality Cosplay Photo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maradona calls on Messi to continue with Argentina #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Airbnb files suit against San Francisco over rental laws #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brief from Brussels: EU rocked by Brexit vote #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Olympic swimming trials 2016 results: Katie Ledecky almost breaks her own world record while qualifying #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch The Division’s Underground DLC go full Diablo with random dungeons #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No One Wants To Speak At Donald Trump’s Convention! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Star Ocean: Integrity and Faithlessness review #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ford dealership steals art from indie game Firewatch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Labyrinth is now 30 years old. Here’s how this gloriously weird movie became a cult classic. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the ancient art of origami is inspiring cutting-edge technology #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge in Brock Turner Trial Hands Down Harsher Sentence in Similar Sex Assault Case: Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[600MHz reverse auction said to be nearing end #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calvin Harris — Damn Near Rips Door Off His SUV!! (VIDEO) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google’s virtual reality Cardboard Expeditions are now available to everyone #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Performing Company In Every State, Ranked By Return #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kris Bryant hits 3 homers as Cubs, Arrieta beat Reds 11-8 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NBA’s Thabo Sefolosha — NYPD Calls BS On Abuse … ‘Force Was Justified’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Wyatt Family Appearing On ESPN, WWE SmackDown Segment Announced, More On Tampa Bucs At RAW #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[W|W: The Wearable Weekly – PlayStation VR poised to dominate high-end virtual reality market #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber, Lyft could get new overseer in California #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Duncan Garner: I locked eyes with a monster – one of Moko’s killers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Windows 10 forced update is so aggressive, it got sued big time #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
