<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Iowa caucuses came ‘crashing down,’ under watchful eye of DNC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Questions swirl around whether Bloomberg will make Las Vegas debate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some anxiousness as moderates split Democratic vote #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump pushed CIA to find bin Laden's son over higher priority targets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aide defends Trump tweets: 'very effective way' to communicate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I want to give $100,000 a year to my kids but not to my stepdaughter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For years, Bloomberg fought claims of profane, sexist comments #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barr complained to president 'for weeks' about tweets, source says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump quoting Emerson to refer to himself as 'the King' sparks outrage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How country music star Tim McGraw stays fit on tour #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump speaks with Turkey's Erdogan amid growing tensions in Syria #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AOC lowers expectations on achieving Medicare for All if Sanders wins #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Master of false news gives right-wing Americans headlines they believe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Which are the least tax-friendly states in America? California doesn’t crack the top 10, but Illinois sure does #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi defends decision to rip Trump's State of the Union address #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vermont governor endorses Bill Weld for GOP presidential nomination #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Diversity test: 2020 Democrats seek their fortunes in Nevada #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump looks to rev up his base at Daytona 500 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump campaign manager tweets photo of big crowd near Air Force One from 2004 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate braces for fight over impeachment whistleblower testimony #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019's Social Security raise was downright pathetic, data shows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump impeachment lawyer scolds him for tweeting about Stone case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats say Trump administration skimps on virus fight #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Roger Stone asks for new trial in sealed motion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senators reaffirm Ukraine support at first meeting since impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iowa Democratic Party names new chairman after caucus chaos #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A struggling Elizabeth Warren spends 30 minutes on the press bus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They Documented the Coronavirus Crisis in Wuhan. Then They Vanished. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police detain Rashida Tlaib during low wages protest at Detroit airport #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Reid says Biden will do well in diverse Nevada's caucuses #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOP senator on Trump: 'Tweeting less would not cause brain damage' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rival Democrats accuse Mike Bloomberg of trying to 'buy' election #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barr-Trump relationship is facing its gravest threat yet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nikola reveals Badger electric pickup truck with 600-mile range #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warren urged to revive fighter persona after 'unity' pitch falls flat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AOC calls for 'turnout machine' as 12 Dem rivals eye her House seat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: A Presidency Increasingly Guided by Suspicion and Distrust #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nasty rivalry cast aside as Ted Cruz worked to save Trump's presidency #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Something has to be done': Trump's quest to rewrite history of Russia probe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Nevada, Amy Klobuchar's shifts on immigration are under scrutiny #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[William Barr's actions spark unease among U.S. prosecutors #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: Another case Trump meddled in, another Barr intervention #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders leads Democratic field in latest Nevada poll #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Investigation of Russia probe looks at '3 important things,' Gowdy says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump, Barr fuel DOJ turmoil over cases tied to White House #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders Is on the Rise. But How High Can His Numbers Go? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Family builds $3.8 billion fortune 1 pint of blood at a time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This man paid off his $300K house in 3 months. Here's why didn't invest the money #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I’ve Been Plastic-Free for 6 Years—Here’s What I Use Instead #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dairies are desperate to get Americans to drink milk again #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Twist in California’s Homeless Crisis: Evictions by the Evicted #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders tears into Bloomberg, says Dem billionaire can't beat Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McCabe: 'I don't think I will ever be free of’ Trump #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump expected to raise $10 million during Florida stop #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate Democrats pressure Trump to drop ObamaCare lawsuit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House uses Trump impeachment team arguments in suit seeking tax returns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bloomberg’s Billions: How the Candidate Built an Empire of Influence #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Doctors on the signs of heart failure everyone should be able to recognize #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WH Memo Justifying Suleimani Strike Cites No Imminent Threat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This warehouse of JDM jewels is tucked away in small-town Virginia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deep cracks emerge in Joe Biden’s firewall state of South Carolina #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former No. 2 U.S. intel official 'didn't want to be anyone's agenda' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ala. Senate contender's ad hits Sessions: 'Hillary still ain't in jail' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s soft touch with China’s Xi on coronavirus worries some advisers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Las Vegas precinct shows people waiting 3.5 hours for early voting #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Jerry Seinfeld found Steve McQueen's Porsche 917 on a used car lot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside the president's week of rage and retribution #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet the Nigerian Buttigeig fan whose 'It’s Lis’ tweet created a stir #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Powerful Ukrainian playing both sides of Giuliani's Ukraine project #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sally Yates blasts Trump for using DOJ as 'personal grudge squad' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats Look Ahead From Nevada and See a Common Enemy: Bloomberg #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump repeats the same stories, but the details often change #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emerging GOP climate change strategy aims to court young conservatives #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your foam coffee cup is fighting for its life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deporting 3 million 'was a big mistake,' Joe Biden tells Univision #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dem presidential hopefuls take aim at red Texas as Super Tuesday looms #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President gives command for Daytona 500 drivers to start their engines #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scandal-plagued Bronx politician plots against AOC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why claiming Social Security is really just a gamble #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1,100 ex-Justice Department officials call for Barr to resign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump, William Barr, Roger Stone made for turbulent week at DOJ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What is a million-mile truck actually worth? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fearful of Trump’s Attacks, Justice Dept. Lawyers Worry Barr Will Leave Them Exposed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is why you should never paint your house a dark color #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[District court judge sets Tuesday phone hearing in Roger Stone case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: The Democratic nomination contest doesn't look like any from the past #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prosecutor says Flynn review is ruse for new probe into former FBI men #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Graham requests DOJ, FBI interviews in probe into Russia investigation #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Defense secretary defends OKing Trump shifting of funds to border wall #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is Why Airplanes Make Weird Noises Before Take-off #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders' 'Medicare-for-all' in crosshairs of powerful Nevada union #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democratic campaigns warn of chaos ahead of the Nevada caucuses #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What you should know about walking for weight loss #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Campaign downplays report of possible Bloomberg-Clinton ticket #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In interview, Amy Klobuchar, Tom Steyer can't name Mexican president #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why would a billionaire charge the Secret Service $650 a night? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden Calls on Sanders to Show Accountability for 'Outrageous' Online Threats by Followers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barr calls for outside prosecutor to review the Flynn case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After split results, Democrats brace for a long primary. Just what Bloomberg wants. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's why more travelers are joining the 'do not tip' movement #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
