<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Valve Swears Half-Life: Alyx Is Actually, Legitimately Done #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don’t Let Back Pain Get You Down #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Aerosmith drummer Joey Kramer joins band on stage to accept award despite lawsuit drama: re… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Your waist size may be more important than weight for multiple heart attack risk #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Pigs Genetically Engineered With Human Cells May Pave The Way For Future Skin Transplants #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Two tested for virus in Scotland given all-clear #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Luxury travel: 50 wealthy tourists, eight countries … and one giant carbon footprint #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: China’s hero doctor was punished for telling truth about coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surprise! Your Medication Can Have New Side Effects Years After You Start It #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: There’s A Viral Theory That Jameela Jamil Has Munchausen, &amp; She’s Clapping Back]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stewart leaves ITN over social media ‘errors’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Does The Skin Need? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There’s A Viral Theory That Jameela Jamil Has Munchausen, &amp; She’s Clapping Back | Betches #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Men appear to be more vulnerable to the coronavirus: report #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Post Edited: Quarantined evacuees wrote a petition asking to be tested for coronavirus. Here’s why the CDC said no… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Stewart leaves ITN over social media ‘errors’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man’s year of cold sea swims ‘to get out of bed’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Chinese Authorities Confirm First Human-To-Human Transmission Of New Coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Infections from coronavirus exceed 20K as China vows new measures to prevent spread #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney+s Marvel TV Series Finally Gets a Release Date #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They’re each famous for different reasons. But as kids, these women wore the same uniform. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Lessons we should have learned from the liberation of Auschwitz and other Nazi camps #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A 2-year-old boy’s reaction to a Target ad is powerful reminder of why representation matters… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Scientists Predict Wuhan’s Outbreak Will Get Much Worse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Post Edited: Infections from coronavirus exceed 20K as China vows new measures to prevent spread #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First coronavirus death in Hong Kong as four more cities are locked down #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New post: Man’s year of cold sea swims ‘to get out of bed’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[We held a Q &amp; A about building a better world. The answers will boost your faith in humanity.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHS to stop ‘ineffective’ treatments #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your waist size may be more important than weight for multiple heart attack risk #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Day I Found Out My Life Was Hanging by a Thread #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China’s hero doctor was punished for telling truth about coronavirus #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fingerprint Test Can Tell If You’ve Taken Cocaine Even After You’ve Washed Your Hands #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Symptoms Of Motion Sickness #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An Open Source Effort to Encrypt the Internet of Things #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Robot Dog With a Job, a Noise-Canceling Car, and More News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New post: Palm Springs and Boys State: Inside Sundances Two Biggest Movies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Record number of severely obese children #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Joe Wicks to read Valentine’s bedtime story #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baltimore restaurants banned from including sodas, sugary drinks on kids’ menus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: A 2-year-old boy’s reaction to a Target ad is powerful reminder of why representation matte… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Men appear to be more vulnerable to the coronavirus: report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Patients pinned to floor and bullied #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Fingerprint Test Can Tell If You’ve Taken Cocaine  Even After You’ve Washed Your Hands #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A nonprofit and a bank are helping girls take over the tech world #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New post: Quarantined evacuees wrote a petition asking to be tested for coronavirus. Here’s why the CDC said no #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Post Edited: First coronavirus death in Hong Kong as four more cities are locked down #URL# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New laser-guided artillery round destroys moving target #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Disney+s Marvel TV Series Finally Gets a Release Date #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Mary Higgins Clark, bestselling author of suspense novels, dead at 92 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lessons we should have learned from the liberation of Auschwitz and other Nazi camps #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Broom Challenge trend takes over social media thanks to … NASA? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: National Television Awards: Red carpet in pictures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[National Television Awards: Red carpet in pictures #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could China’s New Coronavirus Become a Global Epidemic? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Difference Between Headaches and Migraines #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New post: First coronavirus death in Hong Kong as four more cities are locked down #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Need Help Sleeping? Try These Insomnia Tips! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two tested for virus in Scotland given all-clear #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pigs Genetically Engineered With Human Cells May Pave The Way For Future Skin Transplants #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Do I Need To Know About Viagra Connect #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: It’s Possible For Coronavirus To Reinfect Recovered Patients, Chinese Expert Warns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 great dog movies from the 1990s #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Visible: Out on Television’ sees TV’s major role in the march toward gay rights #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Actually, the US has a long history of separating families #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Valve Swears Half-Life: Alyx Is Actually, Legitimately Done #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drug shortages prompt FDA to form task force #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Jameela Jamil responds to allegations that she’s lied about chronic illnesses and accidents #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Gay conversion therapy’ to be banned #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: A nonprofit and a bank are helping girls take over the tech world #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosmith drummer Joey Kramer joins band on stage to accept award despite lawsuit drama: report… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Dungay inquest: shocking video shows prison officers restraining inmate before death #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Polar Bears Are Having Less Cubs And Losing Weight Due To Arctic Sea Ice Loss #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Wicks to read Valentine’s bedtime story #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New post: Infections from coronavirus exceed 20K as China vows new measures to prevent spread #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Luxury travel: 50 wealthy tourists, eight countries … and one giant carbon footprint #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mary Higgins Clark, bestselling author of suspense novels, dead at 92 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: A Robot Dog With a Job, a Noise-Canceling Car, and More News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Could China’s New Coronavirus Become a Global Epidemic? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Surprise! Many Gluten-Intolerant Folks Can Eat Sourdough Bread #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breastmilk offers lifelong health benefits. Let’s promote it better]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists Predict Wuhan’s Outbreak Will Get Much Worse #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: ‘Visible: Out on Television’ sees TV’s major role in the march toward gay rights #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Babies sleep better when they begin solid food early, study says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Case Of Coronavirus Reaches US, Health Officials Confirm #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: We held a Q &amp; A about building a better world. The answers will boost your faith in humanit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Palm Springs and Boys State: Inside Sundances Two Biggest Movies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Broom Challenge trend takes over social media thanks to … NASA? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quarantined evacuees wrote a petition asking to be tested for coronavirus. Here’s why the CDC said no… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ex-rugby player Christian Scotland-Williamson is chasing his NFL dream #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Skin Care Tips For Dry Skin #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: Polar Bears Are Having Less Cubs And Losing Weight Due To Arctic Sea Ice Loss #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New post: First Case Of Coronavirus Reaches US, Health Officials Confirm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Truth About Weight Loss Pills – Do The Ingredients In These Pills Work? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best way to treat dry mouth. Use SALIVA STIMULATING TABLETS SST 100 TABLETS it stimulates saliva production aga… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: An Open Source Effort to Encrypt the Internet of Things #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# New post: New laser-guided artillery round destroys moving target #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s Possible For Coronavirus To Reinfect Recovered Patients, Chinese Expert Warns #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chinese Authorities Confirm First Human-To-Human Transmission Of New Coronavirus #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jameela Jamil responds to allegations that she’s lied about chronic illnesses and accidents #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
