<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[His Novel’s Hero Is a Middle-Aged Canadian Catholic Professor. And a Suicide Bomber. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyon Bombing Suspect Says He Pledged Allegiance to ISIS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leader of Smithsonian’s African American Museum to Direct Entire Institution #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Punching Iran Over Its Foreign Policy Could Lead to a Faster Path to War #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Martha Graham’s Dance of Empowerment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘The Weekly’ Wants to Show You That ‘Reporters Are Not Robots’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney May Halt Productions in Georgia if Abortion Law Is Enforced #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[An Impeccable Oberon, Flexing His Power #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richard Prince and the New Meaning of High Art #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For Kishi Bashi, History Teaches Compassion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What’s on TV Wednesday: ‘Archer’ and ‘The InBetween’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Music Nearly Lost to AIDS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What’s on TV Tuesday: ‘Running With Beto’ and ‘Songland’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Court Denies Italy’s Request for Return of Disputed da Vinci Work #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Were You at Woodstock 1969? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Movies and TV Shows New to Netflix, Amazon and More in June #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[France Hands ISIS Suspects to Iraq, Which Sentences Them to Hang #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Hand of Native American Women, Visible at Last #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Resonance Records to Stream Its Trove of Historical Jazz Albums #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When a Ballerina Gets to Be Goofy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 Comedy Shows to Catch in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Merkel Tells Harvard Grads to Tear Down 'Walls of Ignorance' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Tibetan Collection Fights a Battle That Small Museums Often Face #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Pop and Spark of ‘Too Darn Hot’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to Do in New York This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: In ‘Good Omens,’ Angel and Demon Try to Save the World #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Central Park Five: ‘We Were Just Baby Boys’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Documents Suggest Prosecutors Quickly Changed Mind on Jussie Smollett Case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Central Park Five: ‘We Were Just Baby Boys’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York Art Galleries: What to See Right Now #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What’s on TV Thursday: Ava DuVernay on ‘Desus &amp; Mero’ and ‘BlacKkKlansman’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Classical Music Concerts to See in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Deadwood’: What to Remember for the HBO Movie #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Summer, Opera Grapples With Race #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iraq Sentences 2 More French IS Members to Death, 6 So Far #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Baltimore Symphony Musicians Are ‘Stunned’ After Concerts Are Canceled #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[22 Art Exhibitions to View in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Leader Who Was ‘Trump Before Trump’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Playlist: Cardi B Is Stressed, and 13 More New Songs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: The Searing Power of an AIDS Symphony #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With ‘NOS4A2,’ Joe Hill Finally Sinks His Teeth Into TV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Resistance Became Too Loud to Ignore #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Latest: Egypt's Leader Says Gulf Security Vital to Cairo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: India's Modi Faces Foreign Pressures in 2nd Term #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your House Is My House, Pakistan’s Rich Say to Its Poor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: Angel and Demon Cross the Aisle to Save the World. (Sorry, It’s Fiction) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pakistan Arrests 6 Men for Raising Funds for Outlawed Group #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyon Bomb Suspect Had Pledged Allegiance to IS #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Some Enchanted Ending: Debuts and Other Spectacular Feats at City Ballet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Tibetan Collection Fights a Battle That Small Museums Often Face #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turkey Frees American NASA Scientist Imprisoned for 2 Years #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Rockettes Fall Like Dominoes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Harvard Speech, Merkel Rebukes Trump’s Worldview in All but Name #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney May Halt Productions in Georgia if Abortion Law Is Enforced #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Things to Do With Your Kids in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida Cabinet Meets in Israel Under Media Objection #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India's New Government Signals Hindu and India-First Goals #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next Out of Prince’s Vaults: The Hits He Gave Away #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After a Scandal, the New Orleans Jazz Market Rises Again #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Time Is Up’: Pakistan’s Army Targets Protest Movement, Stifling Dissent #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Movies and TV Shows New to Netflix Australia in June #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At This Techno Club, the Party Is Political #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leonardo Drew Rides His Magic Carpet to a New Field #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leader of Smithsonian’s African American Museum to Direct Entire Institution #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UN Assembly Remembers Victims of Violence Against Religion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iraq Hands Over 188 Turkish Children of Suspected IS Members #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 Pop, Rock and Jazz Concerts to Check Out in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Latest: Florida Cabinet Meeting Underway in Jerusalem #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Sexual Assault Charges Filed Against R. Kelly #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry Potter E-Books Offer Hogwarts Lessons for All #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Modi Begins Second Term as India’s Prime Minister After Crushing Victory #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Queer Muslims Are Still Rare on TV. One Writer Wants to Change That. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Syria Rejects Arab Summit Statement on Iran Intervention #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Latest: Saudi King Says Islamic Summit Confronts Threats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What’s on TV Friday: ‘Deadwood: The Movie’ and ‘When They See Us’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tyler, the Creator Beats DJ Khaled to Hit No. 1 With ‘Igor’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Dance Performances to See in N.Y.C. This Weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pride Events: Here’s How to Celebrate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Broken Saucers in Alan Faena’s House Are Purely Aesthetic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Robert Mueller Should Testify on TV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: Twyla Tharp’s Enduring ‘You Can Have It All’ Vision #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where Subway Dancers Practice Their Art #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Art Festival Is Welcome, but Not the Huge Crowds #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oklahoma City Bombing Trial Judge Richard Matsch Dies at 88 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[David Letterman 2.0, the Non-Ironic Version #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Turkey, Keeping Alive a Language of Whistles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Their Beach Opera Won at the Biennale. But They Can Hardly Afford It. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[France Calls on Iraq to Spare Six of Its Citizens From Death Penalty #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There’s Great Dance on Broadway. Hello, Tony Awards? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Movies and TV Shows New on Netflix Canada in June #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two Transgender Activists Are Getting a Monument in New York #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘When They See Us’ Transforms Its Victims Into Heroes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pakistan Sentences 3 to 5-Year in Jail Over Terror Financing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How a City in Fear Brutalized the Central Park Five #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Still Pondering the End of ‘Game of Thrones’? Here’s What to Read About It #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Walt Whitman’s Big Birthday, 10 Glorious Relics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Review: In One Last ‘Deadwood,’ the Future Prevails and the Past Endures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Japan Announces Aid to Bangladesh During Leader's Visit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arab Leaders Meet in Mecca to Unify Ranks Amid Iran Tensions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Good Omens’ Unites an Angel and a Demon for Judgment Day #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
