<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[PopSockets, Sonos, and Tile Ask Congress to Rein in Big Tech - WIRED #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything to know about Trump’s Wildwood rally. Parking, security, standing in line. - #URL#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who is Sofia Kenin? Meet 21-year-old American who will play in Australian Open final - USA TODAY… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple averaged $1 billion in revenue per day in the holiday quarter - 9to5Mac #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Socialism has never been successful’: Trump rallies crowd in Iowa, where Bernie is on the rise - The Guardian… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA's Parker Solar Probe spotted 'stealth' outburst on the sun - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Is A Savage Burn? Mike Bloomberg Torched By ‘Jeopardy’ Great Ken Jennings. - HuffPost #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Temple Hills, Maryland: Man who'd been handcuffed fatally shot by officer in police car - CBS News… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[iPhone maker Foxconn will stay shut in China for another week at least - The Verge #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dominic Thiem vs Alexander Zverev - Match Highlights (SF)]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coco Gauff's fairytale run at the Australian Open comes to end after defeat by fellow American Sofia Kenin - CNN In… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here’s How Much Brands Are Paying for Sponsored Content on TikTok &amp; YouTube - Search Engine Journal… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What time is Jake Paul vs. AnEsonGib tonight? Live stream info for the YouTube stars’ fight - DAZN News US… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suspended Grammys chief Deborah Dugan alleges sexual misconduct in Recording Academy - The Guardian… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Royal Caribbean blames 'reckless' grandfather in death of toddler Chloe Wiegand - New York Post… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders surge worries some Democrats, but they fear a push to stop him would backfire - The Washington Post… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gayle King furious with CBS for viral interview clip about Kobe Bryant rape case - Page Six #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google’s upcoming call recording feature could also support transcription - The Verge #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple stock falls; a delay in production resuming at Foxconn would be 'shock to the system,' analyst says - MarketW… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Hears Arguments In New Jersey 'Bridgegate' Case - NPR #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ghosn's dramatic escape could bring much-needed reform to Japanese companies - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Protesters Mass in Baghdad, Demanding U.S. Leave Iraq - The New York Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Residents return to find homes razed after NSW fires, Canberra escapes worst fate]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYPD Cop and Fiancee Let Autistic Boy Freeze to Death, Police Say - The Daily Beast #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Forever 21 reaches $81 million deal to sell its retail business to US mall owners and Authentic Brands - CNBC… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In Trade for Betts, Another of Astros’ Vanquished Opponents Bulks Up - The New York Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Loneliness is on the rise and younger workers and social media users feel it most, Cigna survey finds - CNBC… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When Life Throws You Curveballs, Embrace the ‘New Normal’ - The New York Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LSU 'Get the Gat' video from Trump's White House tribute goes viral -- and features mystery woman - Fox News… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran plane pilot heard in leaked air traffic control audio talking about "missile" hitting Ukraine passenger jet -… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump To Address Anti-Abortion March For Life - NPR #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Third time's the winner, as Saturday Night Live finally takes advantage of Adam Driver - The A.V. Club… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein's sex assault trial is set to begin today, more than two years after allegations against him broke… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Greta Thunberg’s Message at Davos Forum: ‘Our House Is Still on Fire’ - The New York Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Davante Adams: Pressure’s really on 49ers - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump ordered to remove envoy in Ukraine in 2018 - video - BBC News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elementary school kids doused as jet dumps fuel before emergency landing - Los Angeles Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ADG Awards: ‘Once Upon A Time In Hollywood’, ‘Avengers: Endgame’ &amp; ‘Parasite’ Nab Top Film Prizes – Winners List -… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Retired diplomat who testified in Trump impeachment says it is the 'American way to speak up about wrongdoing' - CN… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael Avenatti Arrested by Feds at California State Bar Hearing - The Daily Beast #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chinese shares plunge as investors cut risks over virus outbreak - Al Jazeera English #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MLB: No evidence Astros used wearable devices to aid sign-stealing - KTRK-TV #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nevada Voters Begin Early Caucusing On Saturday. Here's What You Need To Know - NPR #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Israeli army: Hamas hackers tried to ‘seduce’ soldiers - USA TODAY #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How does the new coronavirus compare with the flu? - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump's former Navy secretary endorses Michael Bloomberg - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA's Spitzer Space Telescope is no more. Here's what's next for infrared astronomy. - #URL#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry and Meghan Markle to close office at Buckingham Palace - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden accuses Sanders campaign of sharing "doctored" video of the former vice president's comments on Social Securi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DC fire recruits under investigation for flashing 'OK' sign in photo, 'white power' symbol or 'circle game'? - Fox… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Parasite' Makes History With First South Korea Spirit Award Win - msnNOW #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ABC News - ABC News (Australia) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[VIDEO: This Valentina Shevchenko kick is like a video game cheat code - Business Insider - Business Insider… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike Bloomberg's Super Bowl ad focuses on gun control - CNBC #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Jonas and Sophie Turner are expecting their 1st child - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Macy’s to close 125 more stores, shut down data center in Lorain - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook's Twitter and Instagram accounts hacked - BBC News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With USWNT Headed to Olympics, Lavelle Has Another Grand Stage to Continue Her Rise - Sports Illustrated… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Australian Open 2020 - Australian Open TV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Turkey quake kills at least 22, rescuers dig for survivors - Reuters #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It looks like Channing Tatum is no longer a single man - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stocks, Equities News: Stock Market Bulls Off Rails Again - Bloomberg #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. flu deaths hit 14,000, haven’t peaked yet, CDC says - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Break out the tumblers. The price of wine is dropping fast - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mighty Mice In Space May Help Disabled People On Earth : Shots - Health News - NPR #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran Acknowledges It Fired 2 Missiles at Ukrainian Jet - The New York Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Under Armour loses $15M, considers flagship NYC store - Fox Business #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney+ to launch a week earlier than planned in the UK - BBC News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Chiefs’ Defense Turned the Tide in Super Bowl LIV in Three Plays - Sports Illustrated… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus Shuts Macau, the World’s Gambling Capital - The New York Times #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I switched from Android to iPhone: Here's where Apple's phone wins and fails - PCWorld #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First US evacuee from China to have coronavirus mistakenly released from hospital - New York Post… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Warcraft III birthed a genre, changed a franchise, and earned a Reforge-ing - Ars Technica… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fed's first hurdle in 2020: Dispensing with 'QE Lite' - Reuters #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lori Harvey Robbed But Thwarts Rolls Royce Auto Theft - TMZ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber’s plan to turn billion-dollar losses into profits isn’t crazy - Ars Technica #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Myanmar ordered to prevent genocide against Rohingya by top UN court - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Quarantine: Ben awaits coronavirus all clear and gets Irish treats - Channel 4 News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Storm Dennis strikes UK sparking flood warnings and evacuations - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran satellite launch fails to reach orbit - #URL# #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billie Eilish has a history-making night at the Grammys - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Judge names Jason Garrett, Patrick Graham, Thomas McGaughey as coordinators - #URL#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mar-a-Lago intruder found not guilty of trespassing - NBC News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CVS Health beats on fourth-quarter earnings and revenue - CNBC #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Southwest prepares for another peak summer season without the Boeing 737 Max - CNBC #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why one stock-market bull says he’s taking the ‘offense off the field’ - MarketWatch #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['You're stealing our water': Germans protest against Tesla gigafactory - Yahoo Finance #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stocks could get another boost from the US jobs machine - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dell’s 2019 XPS 13 DE: As close as we currently get to Linux-computing nirvana - Ars Technica… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Veteran strategist eyes health care and financials in anticipation of ‘choppy and frustrating’ markets - MarketWatc… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New vulnerability in Android will make you think twice before using Bluetooth - #URL#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tinder to add panic button and anti-catfishing tech - BBC News #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yum Brands' stock tumbles as coronavirus and Pizza Hut's weak sales expected to hit 2020 results - CNBC… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He moved into his daughter’s dorm and targeted her roommates for sex trafficking, prosecutors say - The Washington… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World leaders gather for Holocaust commemoration, 75 years after the liberation of Auschwitz -… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The iPad is still finding its place ten years in - The Verge #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Angola corruption: Leaked documents implicate Africa's richest woman - Al Jazeera English #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Xiaomi Mi 10 could launch on the same day as Samsung Galaxy S20 - TechRadar #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Germany's economy has flatlined. The coronavirus could push it into recession - CNN #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[High-definition solar telescope produces its first stunning images of the Sun - TechSpot #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
