<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[RuPaul Gave Pete Davidson A Drag Transformation On "SNL" And It Was Everything #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What I’ve learned becoming a master inventor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nintendo apologizes for Switch production delays due to coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pop Culture Live with Alyssa Rosenberg (Feb. 17) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Call of Duty Mobile has passed 150 million downloads #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Russian DJ swept out to sea by wave at Bondi as his wife watched in horror #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UN official says airstrikes kill over 30 civilians in Yemen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Danielle’s Ex-Husband Marty Slams Melissa Gorga For Talking About Her For Attention #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 90,000 people sign petition urging TV channels to support sexual violence victims #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AI Weekly: Announcing our AI and security special issue #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is the reason Billie Eilish really reacted during Maya Rudolph and Kristen Wiig's Oscar medley #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Left-Leaning Documentaries Featured Prominently at the Oscars: 'Workers of the World Unite!' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UFC 247 Jon Jones vs Dominick Reyes LIVE: Stream, UK start time, undercard, latest tonight #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Garnett Lee joins Raw Fury to take care of business for indies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apparently Jared Padelecki Was Not The Original Dean On "Gilmore Girls" And I'm Sorry, What? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Posts Heartbreaking Video Comparing Her Baby Girl By Kobe To Late Gigi #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MIT CSAIL’s TextFooler generates adversarial text to strengthen natural language models #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Husband Pleads Guilty To Beating His Wife To Death On Cruise Ship #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ASU researchers debut ViWi-BT, an AI/computer vision mmWave beam guide #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The DeanBeat: Ubisoft’s Mythic Quest is a TV show that doesn’t look down on gamers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# launches esports viewing open beta and raises $1.8 million #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I'm Dying At Jimmy Fallon Thinking He Was Getting Canceled For Calling RuPaul A Drag Queen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Intel is latest to pull out of Mobile World Congress due to coronavirus fears #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[40+ Awesome PowerPoint Templates (With Cool PPT Presentation Designs) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden's New Hampshire Party Was... Well, Look For Yourself #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[France Reports First Coronavirus Death Outside Asia: Virus Update #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Skale Network to launch cryptocurrency tokens that withstand regulatory scrutiny #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mario Kart VR gets a new location in London #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AP VoteCast: Young, liberal voters key to Sanders' NH win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Northern Ireland police investigating 'republican plot to blow up lorry crossing Irish Sea on Brexit day' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HS girls basketball: Seminole Ridge wins district title for first time in program history #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber taps ClimaCell to improve ETA estimates with hyper-local weather data #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UN official says airstrikes kill over 30 civilians in Yemen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders declares victory in Iowa, says he can 'defeat the most dangerous president in modern American history' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buttigieg, Sanders and Warren campaigns submit caucus irregularity claims to Iowa Democrats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hired: AR/VR engineers replace blockchain programmers as hottest commodity #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IEEE calls for standards to combat climate change and protect kids in the age of AI #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17 Stupid Choices People Actually Made In Movies And TV Shows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Florida Weekly Fishing Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Golf Pool is an ideal fit on VR headsets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden Is Preparing For The Worst In New Hampshire #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Love affairs to remember: Two local couples recall their romantic reunions for Valentine's Day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020: Cloud gaming’s gathering storm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Freezing weather compounds crisis for displaced in Syria #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Corden And Rebel Wilson Hilariously Shaded "Cats" With Just 11 Words #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyft touts benefits of self-driving cars, but warns of ‘second order’ effects #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Write Powerful PowerPoint Presentations Fast With Outlines #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most Of The World Thinks These Movies Are Real Bad — Have You Seen Them? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It Seems Like We Really Are Getting That "Friends" Reunion Special On HBO Max #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jalen Smith comes to the rescue, saving Maryland from a disaster against Nebraska #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are These TV Parents Actually Good Parents? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden Was Fighting For His Campaign In Friday’s Debate After Taking A "Gut Punch" In Iowa #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billionaire Dem Argues For (Some) Money In Politics #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Self-Driving Mass Transit Arrives on American Streets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Nigerian Man Is Actually Behind That Pro-Pete Buttigieg Twitter Account #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google’s ClearGrasp AI model helps robots better recognize transparent objects #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ComPost Live with Alexandra Petri (Feb. 18) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McCabe, an ex-FBI official targeted by Trump, not charged #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glu Mobile gets ready to launch Disney Sorcerer’s Arena mobile game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[THQ Nordic opens Nine Rocks Games in Bratislava to create survival sim #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Red Dead Redemption 2 surpasses 29 million copies sold #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Galaxy S20, S20+, and S20 Ultra specs: What Samsung changed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[live: Storm Ciara triggers 'danger to life' Met Office warning as flights and trains cancelled with 80mph winds for… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Subscription strategies to drive your competitive advantage (VB Live) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple seeks patent for AR/VR video recording with multi-angle playback #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't Freak Out, But We Know Your Age Based On Your Favorite TV Characters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to Watch: TV Chat with Hank Stuever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Latest: Sanders claims Bloomberg will not excite voters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Payback: Trump ousts officials who testified on impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kirk Douglas rose from poverty to become a king of Hollywood #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amber opens support studio in Mexico’s Guadalajara tech hub #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most People Can't Identify 7/9 Of These Marvel Siblings – Can You? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Romance Over? Dog The Bounty Hunter’s Galpal Moon Angell Moves Out After He Proposed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Celebrity Tweets You Missed This Week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I Tried The Filter That's Supposed To Block Unsolicited Dick Pics And... It Worked? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dice Game of the Year: Untitled Goose Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BBC One goes off-air due to Storm Ciara #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tim Sweeney: Android is a fake open system, and iOS is worse #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber grows customers and revenues, but net loss widens #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Square acquires deepfakes research firm Dessa #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nielsen: Total TV shows and movies increased 10% in 2019 thanks to streaming wars #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enterprise VR startup ForwardXP forms game division and hires art director #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New operators Iana and Oryx helped me dust off Rainbow Six: Siege #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Raw Fury will publish noir adventure game Backbone #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Half-Life: Alyx launches for PC VR on March 23 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[19 Unpopular "Twilight" Opinions That Might Get You A Little Fired Up #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nvidia CEO: Coronavirus caution shaves $100 million from Q1 expectations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Most Shocking Moments From The 2020 Oscars! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are You And Your Significant Other As Much Drama As Peter And Lara Jean? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mookie Betts reportedly is a Dodger at last, and the Red Sox get a shortstop named Jeter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeremy Roenick won't return to NBC Sports after suspension #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple seeks to patent machine learning correction of GPS estimates #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opinions Live with Eugene Robinson (Feb. 18) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to watch the Samsung Galaxy Unpacked 2020 livestream #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Air Force suicides surged last year to highest in 3 decades #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kandi Burruss’ Mama Joyce Still Doesn’t Trust Her Husband Todd With Money #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If Apple’s 5G iPhone plans are still fluid, it’s in for quite a ride #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top Brazilian soccer club struggles to get past deadly fire #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do You Have The Same "Gilmore Girls" Opinions As Everyone Else? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HS girls basketball: Benjamin moves one step closer to ultimate prize with regional quarterfinal win #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
