<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Jose Urquidy Emerges as the Astros’ Unlikely World Series Savior #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Player With Shoulder Pain, and a League Happy to Turn Its Back #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump intends to uphold tradition of presidents and baseball #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katie Hill nude photos, affair allegations threaten rising California Democrat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michigan State, Mark Dantonio are in a five-alarm fire after latest blowout loss | Opinion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This new foldable phone design makes the Galaxy Fold look downright boring – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adele shows off slimmer figure at Drake's birthday party #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pedro Martinez thinks of Nationals as Expos, but knows 'it's not their duty' to promote Montreal past #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pixel 4's new security feature raises Android to iPhone's level. Time for rivals to catch up – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bros to Pros: The N.F.L.’s Quinnen and Quincy Williams #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Astros back in World Series thanks to rookie pitcher José Urquidy's big start #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle, Prince Harry's documentary: 6 things we learned about the Duke and Duchess of Sussex #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nissan’s Ariya concept lights up the Tokyo Motor Show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Astros top Nats 8-1 to tie World Series, led by Urquidy, Bregman #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unranked Kansas State pulls off shocking upset of No. 5 Oklahoma #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s Overreaction O’Clock: Very Early Takeaways on the N.B.A. Season #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Massive gaffe by Texas Tech player helps Kansas to first conference win under Les Miles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Philip Hammond tells Boris Johnson to 'stop throwing tantrums' and get on with Brexit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Devin Booker, Suns hands Kawhi Leonard, Clippers unlikely first loss of season #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson accuses MPs of 'sitting on their a***s' as he urges them to back early election #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Comey says he's 'not worried' about Justice criminal probe of FBI's spying on Trump campaign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More severely obese kids should get surgery, MD group says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No. 3 LSU grinds out win over No. 10 Auburn to set up heavyweight showdown with Alabama #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Labour slam Lib Dem plan for 9 December election as ‘opportunistic stunt’ as Tories call it ‘gimmick’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Virginia GOP deploys Justin Fairfax rape allegations in 2019 election #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Week 9 observations: Writing off Oklahoma as College Football Playoff contender ridiculous #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Simulated World Series: Adam Eaton delivers walk-off hit as Nationals win a true fall classic in Game 5 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Romney's 'Pierre Delecto' just one of DC's famous social-media lurkers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brandon Ingram putting burden on himself to carry Pelicans without Zion Williamson #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michigan used five-man sledgehammer to take down No. 7 Notre Dame #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dutch inventor unveils device to scoop plastic out of rivers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon set to appear as government witness in Roger Stone trial: Report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi raid involved Russia, Turkey, Iraq, Kurds, Donald Trump says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Kelly, former Trump chief of staff, says he warned president of possible impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Halsey and Evan Peters are Instagram official for Halloween #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From rovers on Mars to an orbiting Tesla, this decade revolutionized how we see space – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nearly down-and-out, Astros steal World Series momentum from Nationals after Game 4 rout #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASCAR at Martinsville 2019: Schedule, lineup, TV and more for First Data 500 playoff race #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Football Four: As Ohio State rolls and Oklahoma falls, Alabama and LSU ready for showdown #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump ordered Defense chief to 'screw Amazon' out of $10B contract, book reportedly says – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rugby World Cup: South Africa Edges Wales to Reach Final #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nationals manager explains decision to hold back top relievers in Game 4: 'You don't chase wins' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[J.K. Dobbins, Chase Young power No. 4 Ohio State past No. 13 Wisconsin #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg channels Obama, expands electorate as moderate 2020 alternative to Elizabeth Warren #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lib Dems and SNP offer Boris Johnson early Christmas present of 9 December election #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nationals' ice-cold offense can't find big hit as World Series lead disappears #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Winners and losers from Week 9 in college football led by Oklahoma, Ohio State #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former WH chief of staff says he warned Trump on impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kurt Cobain's cigarette-burned cardigan sells at auction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google Doodle celebrates Sylvia Plath, tortured American poet – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 5G wireless revolution, explained – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daniel Craig's reign as James Bond ends as last movie wraps filming #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buying a new mattress: 7 questions to ask before you shop – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big Green Eggs are tricky so let the Smartfire Controller babysit your BBQ – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 signs it's time to replace your mattress – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Tweet from #USER# has been withheld in response to a report from the copyright holder. Learn more.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mysterious space plane lands after record 780 days in orbit – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Parliament officials accuse authorities of 'stitch-up' over John Bercow bullying row #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fletcher Cox's 911 burglary call released, tells police: 'I'm about to blow his brains out' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump blasts ex-chief of staff John Kelly over claim he warned about impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michael Moore lauds Beto O'Rourke over gun control platform: 'We need to have some courage' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to watch Astros vs. Nationals: MLB live stream, schedule, TV channel, start time for World Series Game 4 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Female high school quarterback throws touchdown on her first pass in a varsity game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You shouldn't flip your mattress — here's why – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi DNA testing confirms death, Donald Trump says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Pittsburgh Steelers cornerback played music in helmet during NFL games #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown accuses Oakland Raiders of using him for financial gain: got me for 'ratings then rip my guarantees'… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bengals vs Rams live stream: how to watch today's NFL London Games 2019 from anywhere #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[J.K. Dobbins powers No. 4 Ohio State past No. 13 Wisconsin #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['We got our swagger back:' World Series is tied, but it's clear the Astros have taken control | Opinion #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicole Kidman showers Keith Urban with love, gifts and roses for 52nd birthday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nationals vs. Astros: What to Watch for in Game 4 of the World Series #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Furious rally might be biggest victory for Oklahoma in loss to Kansas State #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, ISIS leader, believed dead in U.S. military raid #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump impeachment trial: What it might look like #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Helping Alt-Meat Grow Some Muscle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Plot Against the President,' Lee Smith book, details Devin Nunes' fight against 'Paper Coup' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Indiana to consider creating a government corruption hotline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New York Jets cut offensive lineman Kelechi Osemele amid shoulder injury, surgery dispute #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google grappling with trust issues, CEO Pichai says – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Astros pour it on to beat Nationals in Game 4, tie up World Series #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Charles Kupperman lawsuit asks judge to decide on Trump impeachment subpoena #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American soccer star Christian Pulisic scores first-ever Premier League goals #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[He lost 475 pounds. Then did something more impressive #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With World Series all square, Nationals optimistic heading into Game 5: 'It’s a race to two wins' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ocean Cleanup expands to polluted rivers – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods, other golf superstars get stuck in Japan Domino's during severe storm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle 'begged' for tabloid attention before meeting Prince Harry: report #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opinion: Jim Harbaugh finally gets Michigan on track in demolition of Notre Dame #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet BotRide, the self-driving Hyundai Kona Electric – Roadshow #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Big-time players have Ohio State looking like the No. 1 team #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Roberts, Supreme Court chief justice, impeachment role prompts recusal rumblings #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Latest AirPods Pro leak points to some new colors for Apple's earbuds #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MWC19 Los Angeles: The value of blockchain in the telecommunications sector #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police sergeant removed as ICE liaison #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tony Blair: General election and second referendum could happen on the same day #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Game of Thrones' stars Emilia Clarke, Jason Momoa and Kit Harington reunite #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['That's what you get': Astros' Alex Bregman breaks out with grand slam in World Series Game 4 win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LSU makes case for No. 1 after defeat of Auburn #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeremy Corbyn hits out at ‘ridiculous’ Boris Johnson call for him to ‘man-up’ and back snap election #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
