<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Lucas Struggles With Flashbacks, Brad Squirms! Truth Coming Out! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Jennifer Devastated, Learns Her Dad, Bill Horton Died #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Carly And Bobbie Worried About A Mob War – Make Plans To Keep Children Safe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle Only Using Prince Harry For Fame, So Says, Legendary Feminist #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Humiliation, Revenge, and Shattered Lives Teased For 35th-Anniversar… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: Will Spinelli’s Return Rekindle Maxie Romance? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American Idol Premiere Recap 02/16/20: Season 18 Episode 1 "Auditions" #URL#  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: Michael Suspicious Of Nelle’s Story – What Will He Discover? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Thomas Panics Over Liam's Threat - Tries To Rush Hope To Altar #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Young and the Restless Spoilers: Billy Pushing Boundaries While Amanda Begins To Back Off #URL# htt…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers Monday, February 17: Flo Suggests Wyatt Go Back To Sally – Hope’s Words Stop Liam In…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Young and the Restless Spoilers: Melissa Ordway (Abby Newman) Wants Daughters To Find Husband Just Like Their Dad htt…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Young and the Restless Spoilers: Nick Offers Phyllis Wise Advice As Adam And Chance Pursuit Continues #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Nikolas And Liz’s Love Story Could Continue, It's Complicated! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Lani Attempts To Explain Her Actions To Eli, Professes Her Love #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Young and The Restless Spoilers: Is Ashley Abbot Staying Genoa City - Eileen Davidson Back For Good?  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Douglas Forrester Tells Hope Logan The Truth – What Will Thomas Do This Time?… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Thomas Proposes To Zoe - Hope Silences Liam - Wyatt’s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Young and the Restless Spoilers Monday, February 17: Phyllis’ Prison Threat, Chelsea Faces Proposition – Lola’s Miami…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: Peter Threatened As Multiple People Investigate Him – Will He Try To Eliminate His New Threat?…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YR Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Chaos At Newman Gala -  Phyllis Resorts To Blackmail - Abby Furious #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# They need someone new to come on the Soap!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: Peter’s Influence Grows In Strength – But Will He Ever Pay For His Crimes? #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Laura Wright And Wes Ramsay Still Going Strong - In Case You Were Wondering  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Can Finn and Ava Survive His Betrayal and Her Defense Of Peter? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Weekly Spoilers February 17 to February 21: Valentin and Lulu Battle – Lucas Struggles With Flashb… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Lani Crashes Gabi And Eli’s Wedding, Gets Her Payback! #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Finn and Violet Adjust To Lifestyle Changes - Single Dad Tries To Cope Without Anna #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: Jason Morgan And Sam Forced To Split By Parole Restrictions? #URL# https://t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Scott Clifton’s Son Looks Just Like His Twin! #URL# #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Brokenhearted Valentin And Anna Take Comfort In Each Other - New PC Couple? #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Young and the Restless Spoilers: Sharon's Cancer Treatment A Living Hell - Rey Is Her Rock, Nick Stands By Her… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Brooke and Quinn Continue To Battle While Shauna Watches Patiently #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives Spoilers: Sarah Horton Running Out Of Time – Who Will Step Up To Save Baby Mickey?  #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers Monday, February 17: Valentin Wants Suggests Compromise – Nelle Warns Michael – Brando Wants To…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blue Bloods Recap 02/14/20: Season 10 Episode 14 "The Fog Of War" #URL#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Young and the Restless Spoilers: Sharon’s Cancer Treatment A Living Hell – Rey Is Her Rock, Nick Stands By Her… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Recap Friday, February 14: Helena visits with Valentin – Nelle harasses Chase and Willow #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Kirsten Storms And Emme Rylan's Latest Project Will Blow Your Mind #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Zoe Gives Thomas An Ultimatum Before She Agrees To Marry Him #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives Spoilers: Lani's Bombshell - Gabi Attempts Murder At Wedding - Julie's Secret Forces the Hand of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives Weekly Spoilers February 17 to February 21: Rafe Arrests Gabi - Ciara Shares Her Killer Theory Wi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Days of Our Lives Spoilers Monday, February 17: Julie Collapses – Gabi Makes A Huge Admission – Sonny And Will Reminisce…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NCIS Los Angeles Recap 02/16/20: Season 11 Episode 14 "Commitment Issue" #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Days of Our Lives Spoilers: Ciara Assaults Rafe, Stops Ben’s Arrest #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[B&amp;B Spoilers: Thomas Uses Son Again, Sends An Unwitting Douglas To Hope With Important Message #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Thomas Pops The Question,  But To Wrong Woman - Douglas Freaks #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All My Children Alum Jill Larson Nabs Role In New Amazon Series #URL#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Yes, but he is being a good guy at the moment!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Recap Friday, February 14: Helena visits with Valentin – Nelle harasses Chase and Willow… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Katie Forced Into Bad Situation – Will Sally Continue To Trust Her? #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry Still Angry With Royal Family As They Prepare For Return to UK  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# True, but I hope it works out for him!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Blake Berris’ Fangirl Snags Galen Gering, Shawn Christian and Eileen Davidson #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# Recap 02/16/20: Season 1 Episode 12 "Take Your Choice" #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: Can Finn and Ava Survive His Betrayal and Her Defense Of Peter? #URL# https:…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Is Brooke's Hatred For Thomas Greater Than Her Love For Ridge - 'Bridge' Futur… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# No, it is not, I agree!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Lani Attempts To Explain Her Actions To Eli, Professes Her Love #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Michael Suspicious Of Nelle’s Story – What Will He Discover? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronation Street Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Abi's Arson, Freshco Fiasco, Ali Begs Maria To End Engagement… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: ‘The Bold and the Beautiful’ Spoilers: Thomas Shades The Truth – Hope Fears Psychological Attack #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Selfish Lulu Fails To Put Charlotte First - Fights With Valentin For Full Custody #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hawaii Five-0 Recap 02/14/20: Season 10 Episode 16 "Man Is A Slave Of Love" #URL#  #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Liam Vows to Expose Thomas’ Plan – Brooke Confronts T… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Liam And Hope Battle About Thomas - 'Lope' Almost Over! #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronation Street Spoilers: Roy Cropper and Nina To Have Big Storylines  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Zoe Struggles To Bond With Douglas – Young Boy Only Wants Hope #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# It's not one of the best dresses!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Young and the Restless Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Chaos At Newman Gala -  Phyllis Resorts To Blackmail… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# You met Days characters, that is interesting, my sis met some BB characters]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hallmark Channel News: First Preview For 'Love In Store' Released, Find Out What To Expect #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Rumors: Valentin Goes After Jax And Kills Him In Front Of Joss; But Is It Only A Nightmare – And Whose?…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Spoilers: Thomas Pops The Question, But To Wrong Woman – Douglas Freaks… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: General Hospital Spoilers: John J. York Recalls Time He Fell In Love With Wife Vicki #URL# #URL#…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Jennifer Devastated, Learns Her Dad, Bill Horton Died #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Is Finn Leaving Port Charles?  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I like Finn, hopefully, he stays!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Five Not To Be Missed Days Of Our Lives Weekly Spoilers February 17 to February 21 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The Young and the Restless Spoilers Friday, February 14: Phyllis Learns Vegas Secret – Adam’s Expensive Solution – Sick S…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives Spoilers: Lani’s Bombshell – Gabi Attempts Murder At Wedding – Julie’s Secret Forces the Hand of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I totally agree I do not get it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Young and the Restless Spoilers Monday, February 17: Phyllis’ Prison Threat, Chelsea Faces Proposition – Lola’s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I feel bad for Lola!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Five Not To Be Missed Weekly General Hospital Spoilers February 17 to February 21 #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Sonny and Will Leave Town After Victor’s Part In Will’s Conviction Revealed #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Jeff Kober Hints Major Changes Coming To General Hospital #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All My Children Alum Jill Larson Nabs Role In New Amazon Series #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Neighbours Spoilers: Finn Horrified, Amnesia Wearing Off As He Betrays Bea Kisses Elly  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# She should, and see where she and Finn can go in a relationship!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# They seemed happy, he smiled a lot!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Carly And Bobbie Worried About A Mob War - Make Plans To Keep Children Safe #HASHTAG#… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives Spoilers: Jen Lilley Daydreams of Theresa Donovan's Return - Possible Storylines and Her Post-Soa… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Brando Willing To Keep The Secret, Dev Is Suspicious #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Young and The Restless Spoilers: Nikki Holds A Gala To Celebrate Newman And Victor - Many Y&amp;R Characters Return… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[General Hospital Spoilers: Jason Morgan And Sam Forced To Split By Parole Restrictions? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives Spoilers: Sonny Asks Why Will Hasn't Filed Divorce Papers - 'Wilson' Recalls a Happier Valentine'… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Bold and the Beautiful Weekly Spoilers February 17 to 21: Liam Vows to Expose Thomas’ Plan -  Brooke Confronts… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# This one is not too bad, but there has been worse!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Days Of Our Lives Spoilers: Lani Crashes Gabi And Eli’s Wedding, Gets Her Payback! #URL# #URL#…]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
