<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicolas Cage makes the perfect kill-crazy parent in the first trailer for horror comedy Mom and Dad… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel is cancelling their fantastic She-Hulk series and it's a damn shame #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best, worst, and most unforgettable movie moments of 2017 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What do shoelaces and DNA have in common? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple issues apology for slowing down old iPhones #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This keyboard was inspired by a typewriter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Korea announces new cryptocurrency regulations coinciding with the drop in bitcoin prices, YouTube gets pulle… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FCC extends waiver for video game accessibility for the last time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists observe strange double whirlpool effect in ocean for first time #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LG debuts the ThinQ, a Google Assistant-powered smart speaker #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You thought your hella sick older cousin had a good Hot Wheels set-up. Check out this two-storey track.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple wireless charging patent describes ability to prioritize devices #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South Korea Announces New Cryptocurrency Regulations #URL# by titoyooo]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This would be so useful for marathon runners! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sony's A7R III mirrorless can take anything you throw at it: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Next road trip, make your way through these #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RNC tried, and failed, to insult Obama in its website code #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists observe strange double whirlpool effect in ocean for first time #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could this device be the answer to the fresh water shortage? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This tablet looks and feels like actual paper #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The bike helmet got a much needed upgrade #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #HASHTAG# My syndicated #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple gives in to furious customers, slashes price on iPhone slowdown fix #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Zero Mass Water, whose solar panels pull drinking water from the air: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A lump of clay transforms into the Hulk in this mesmerizing time-lapse #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Creating custom clothes has never been easier #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shield your swimmers from radiation with these cool boxers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple’s flagship Chicago retail store wasn’t designed to handle snow #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cole Sprouse from 'Riverdale' gave his brother a very interesting Christmas gift #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World Health Organization will recognize video game addiction in 2018 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Major hacker conference organizers accused of ignoring harassment, enabling abusers #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JPMorgan Chase and Samsung are partnering with IBM to build business apps on quantum computers:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You might be obsessed with taking selfies, but you don't have a mental disorder called "selfitis"… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a reason Uber's value just dropped by tens of billions of dollars: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This restaurant feeds all your senses #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[20 things you won't believe are turning 20 years old in 2018 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tokyo may use facial recognition for security at the 2020 Olympics: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best, worst, and most unforgettable movie moments of 2017 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have super human powers thanks to this suit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple keeps losing legal battles to an Italian company called ‘Steve Jobs’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Avengers wish Stan Lee a happy 95th birthday on Twitter #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New technology we're actually excited about for 2018 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This baby crib mimics a car ride for maximum snoozing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If you hate drinking water, this may help #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Check your kid's temperature with this quick and easy thermometer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This revolutionary cancer treatment could change so many lives #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Newark's mayor will buck the FCC and protect the city's net neutrality #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# in the U.S. and Canada that windows are breaking, and there's no end in sight #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The beauty of freezing bubbles is the only good thing about these nightmarish temperatures #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT alanohnsman: If riding in a Waymo 🤖  car makes you nervous, a new insurer is ready to help via forbes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the Grand Canyon fill with clouds in this timelapse of a rare weather phenomenon #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You don't need a plane ticket. You just need Instagram. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This device could help with your sleep apnea #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shout out to the mom who crocheted the 'Golden Girls' cast for Christmas #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It's totally magical watching this sculptor turn a lump of clay into the Hulk #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What makes Instagram's "recommended" posts so awful? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wireless mic Mikme brings high-end sound to mobile videos: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People really want to eat Tide pods (don't do it) and here's why (please, just don't do it) #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[T. rexes crashed a news segment and it was glorious #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This filmmaker calls himself an 'eyeborg' for a very good reason #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This smart bra monitors your breathing and heart rate #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi is a great human and an even greater Doctor #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's when Riverdale, Supergirl, The Walking Dead and the rest of your favorite shows are coming back… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stop reading what Facebook tells you to read #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meal kits may be convenient, but the waste they create might make your stomach ache #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA lends a hand to new American Girl doll with Mars aspirations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why do so many robots look like octopuses? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With autonomous vehicles it’s not about the journey, it’s about the destination #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LastPass fixes fingerprint security flaw in its Authenticator app #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This room is a bubble tea lover's dream come true #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Major hacker conference organizers accused of ignoring harassment, enabling abusers #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hey Donald Trump, this is the difference between climate and weather #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hellboy Creator Mike Mignola says the B.P.R.D.'s wildest twist was years in the making #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The beauty of freezing bubbles is the only good thing about these nightmarish temperatures #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tech companies need to stop making gadgets look like trash cans #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This secret harness will keep your shirt in place #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple gives in to furious customers, slashes price on iPhone slowdown fix #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bitcoin's very bad week continues with South Korea considering shut down of exchanges #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2017 was the year video went vertical #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[60 cybersecurity predictions for 2018: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The blockchain raises a key human question: How much should we pay to trust one another? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This would make your morning commute WAY more fun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT Forbes: Eric Schmidt to step down as Alphabet chairman, taking role as 'technical advisor'… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This. Car. Is. Lit. 🔥 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These internet mavens were the ones to watch in 2017—cautiously #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The illuminated square made of LEDs in the center of this photograph is meant not only to capture the viewer's gaze… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber's unreal $70 billion valuation really was unreal: #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You keep hearing about blockchains, but what the heck are they? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's why 'SMILF' should function as a blueprint for how TV should work in 2018 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This mini scuba gear lets everyone dive like a pro #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In the trailer for horror comedy Mom and Dad, Nicolas Cage makes the perfect kill-crazy parent… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Russia lost a $45 million satellite because ‘they didn’t get the coordinates right’ #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's Roger Federer just taking casual selfies with adorable quokkas #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TimoSaidWHAT New year, new phone. Grab 2018 by the horns, Timo! #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2017 was the year video went vertical #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ultimate theory of particle physics holds where physicists hoped it wouldn't #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Would you be on board with this crazy nail trend? 💅🌺 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A world dominated by self-driving cars is no longer just possible, it’s inevitable #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sand art taken to the next level #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ridley Scott thinks Disney should hire more experienced directors for Star Wars #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
