<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ladies of The Platinum Life Tease Major Drama: "Everyone Is Bound To Get Played Every Now and Then": Things are… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Sobs and Fears Being Robbed During Mexico Vacation: "We're the Biggest Targets Ever!": Kim… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jimmy Kimmel Gets Emotional When Responding to Las Vegas Shooting: "It's Too Much to Even Process": Jimmy Kimmel is… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Times Stranger Things Stars Natalia Dyer and Charlie Heaton Sparked Romance Rumors: After months of speculation,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Showcases Sexy Looks in Vogue Mexico Cover Shoot and Makes a Plea to Help Earthquake Victims: Kim… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saturday Savings: Jordyn Wood's Insta-Worthy Concert Tee Is on Sale Now!: When it comes to being young and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khloe Kardashian and Tristan Thompson Cuddle in Sweet Video After Pregnancy News: Khloe Kardashian was all smiles… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's Fast and Furious 9's New Release Date: Ladies and gentlemen, start your engines. Fast and Furious 9 finally… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amber Rose Debuts Sexy Superhero Alter Ego and Is Joined by 21 Savage at 2017 SlutWalk: Presenting Captain Save a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kristin Davis Mourns Sex and the City 3's Death Too: "We Will Just Have Our Memories": RIP Sex and the City 3. Like… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reese Witherspoon's 18-Year-Old Daughter Ava Phillippe Will Debut in Paris: While Ava Philippe is no stranger to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE PHOTOS - Kourtney Kardashian Covers Up After Brutal Facial Treatment: Kourtney Kardashian is paying the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientologist Kirstie Alley Blames Las Vegas Shooting On Psychiatric Drugs: She should have known this would go… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Veuve Clicquot Polo Classic-Approved Dresses for Fall: You know what the Veuve Clicquot Polo Classic is, don't you?… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hugh Hefner's Most Controversial Moments: For some, Hugh Hefner was a trailblazer. For others, an exploiter of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justice League Trailer Teases Superman and Will Give You Chills: CHILLS. What is believed to be the final trailer… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Bella Thorne Dates More Men Than Woman: Bella Thorne is looking for love, but she has a harder time finding it… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kevin Hart Posts Happy Family Photos With Pregnant Wife and Kids Amid Cheating Scandal: Two weeks after a cheating… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Outlander Could Not Be Moving Any Faster, But We're Not Sure We Mind: There's something about modern music played… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Margot Robbie, Jennifer Lawrence, Tessa Thompson and More Stars Land Covers for Elle's 2017 Women in Hollywood Issue #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lionel Richie Says He's "Scared To Death" Over Daughter Sofia's Relationship With Scott Disick: You mean he doesn't… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American Horror Story: Cult Unmasks Its Killer Clowns: WE KNEW IT! We. Knew. It. Ivy (Alison Pill) has been part of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Janet Jackson's Creative Director Dishes on Singer's State of the World Tour: Today marks the 20th anniversary of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RHOC's Vicki Gunvalson on Her Relationship With Tamra Judge: ''We Are Not in a Good Place'': Fall is here, and it… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Beckham Kisses Chloë Grace Moretz in Sweet Video: Actions may speak louder than words when it comes to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Jimmy Kimmel Ended Up an Unlikely Hero--and a Magnet for Controversy: Remember when the most controversial… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Teen Mom's Chelsea Houska and Cole DeBoer Celebrate Second Wedding Ceremony: Here comes the bride... again! Teen… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Tom Petty Covers, From John Mayer to Christina Perri: As fans all over the world mourn the loss of Tom… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ryan Murphy Says American Horror Story: Cult Mass Shooting Scene Edited After Las Vegas Tragedy: Apparently some… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch the Cast of Grey's Anatomy Get Wild Behind the Scenes: It's Thursday and that means we're in for another… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hollywood Is at a Crossroads--Finally--in the Wake of Explosively Damning Allegations Against Harvey Weinstein:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein Accused Of Rape By Three Women, Including Anthony Bourdain's Girlfriend Asia Argento: This is… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lady Gaga Celebrates Late Friend Sonja's Birthday With Touching Tributes: "I Love You": Lady Gaga celebrated what… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blade Runner 2049 Review Roundup: Is This One of Harrison Ford's Best Films?: Harrison Ford is receiving much… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bella Thorne Celebrates Her 20th Birthday By Licking YouTuber Tana Mongeau's Tongue: Nothing says "Happy birthday!"… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bored of the Brits? A Guide to the Stunning Swedish Royal Family: Scandals, Romance, Heartbreak Ridiculously… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Moments From Miley Cyrus' Tonight Show Takeover With Jimmy Fallon: There's really only one word to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kyra Sedgwick Reveals Why Ten Days in the Valley Drew Her Back to Series Regular TV: After seven long years, Kyra… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The X-Files Debuts New Trailer: Mulder and Scully Have to Find Their Son!: The whole world is in danger, and it's… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's Your Famous Mom Style? Find Out If You're a Jessica Alba, Mindy Kaling or Kate Middleton: Something's in the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein Blasts The New York Times Over Sexual Assault Claims: Harvey Weinstein is no shrinking violet. On… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ryan Gosling's Tribute to His Dog George Will Wreck You: Could we love Ryan Gosling any more? Turns out that on top… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Miley Cyrus and Jimmy Fallon Face Off in Lip Sync Battle on The Tonight Show: What better way to conclude a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matt Damon Denies Knowing About Harvey Weinstein's Alleged Sexual Misconduct: ''I Would Have Stopped It'': Matt… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Affleck "Angry" and "Sick" Over Harvey Weinstein Sexual Harassment Claims: Ben Affleck is no longer standing in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom Petty Dead at 66 After Suffering Cardiac Arrest: See His Life in Pictures: A music legend has left this world,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[O.J. Simpson Released From Prison After 9 Years: What's Next?: O.J. Simpson is a free man. The 70-year-old former… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heidi Montag and Spencer Pratt Welcome Son Gunner Stone: Speidi's son has arrived! On Sunday, Heidi Montag and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Salling Pleads Guilty To Child Pornography Charges: He better prep himself for a prison beatdown! Mark Salling… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Millie Bobby Brown Insists She's Just Like "Any Other 13-Year-Old": Oh, the places Millie Bobby Brown will go. The… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Real Housewives' Bethenny Frankel Charters Planes to Help Puerto Ricans Devastated by Hurricane Maria: More help is… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenna Johnson Can't Stop Gushing About the Season 25 Celebs in Her Behind-the-Scenes Dancing With the Stars Blog:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lisa Bloom Resigns as Advisor to Harvey Weinstein Amid Sexual Harassment Allegations: Lisa Bloom says she will no… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle and Her Mom Support Prince Harry at the Invictus Games' Closing Ceremonies: Stand by your man! Days… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kourtney Kardashian Slams Scott Disick for Being "Photographed With a Different Hooker Every Day": Kourtney… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessie James Decker Is Pregnant! See the Cutest Pics of Her Daughter Vivianne and Son Eric Jr.: It's official: baby… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gal Gadot and Kate McKinnon Kiss in Wonder Woman Parody Skit on SNL: Wonder Woman is such a tease! Gal Gadot hosted… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is Us Got Us Emotional About The Manny (And Jack Too, Of Course): Who knew Justin Hartley could look so good… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jackie Chan Says Rush Hour 4 Is Happening, but There's a Catch and it Involves Chris Tucker: A decade has passed… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ryan Gosling Freaks Out Over Avatar Font in SNL "Papyrus" Video: Hey girl, if you write to Ryan Gosling, don't use… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Delilah Reveals Son Zachariah Died of Suicide: "My Heart Is Broken Beyond Repair": Delilah is mourning the lost of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adrienne Bailon Says Kourtney Kardashian Was Her ''Breakup Buddy'' Post-Rob Kardashian Split: After a bad breakup… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE PHOTOS - Caitlyn Jenner Flies New $1.5 Million Plane She Bought For Herself With I Am Cait Money: You go,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Kardashian-Approved Case to Keep Your Phone Warm This Fall: Winter is coming, which means it's almost time to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE PHOTOS - Ben Goes Zen! Affleck Seeks Help At Buddhist Meditation Rehab: Ben's trying a new type of rehab… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carly Rae Jepsen's "Call Me Maybe" Viewed 1 Billion Times on YouTube: "Call Me Maybe" is the little pop song that… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rose McGowan Calls for Immediate Resignation of Weinstein Company Board: "The Golden Swamp Must Be Drained":… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Rihanna Is the Reigning Queen of the Canadian Tuxedo: Justin Timberlake and Britney Spears may have it done… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rachel Bilson Buys Pasadena Mansion After Hayden Christensen Split: Rachel Bilson is making moves. The actress has… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Macaulay Culkin and Brenda Song Spotted Holding Hands on "Affectionate" Date Night: Macaulay Culkin and Brenda Song… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RHOC Star Shannon Beador Gets Emotional Over Her Weight Gain and Husband David Being "Disgusted": Mother knows… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato Drops an F-Bomb and Jokes About Lip Syncing at Album Release Party Gig: Demi Lovato is keeping it real.… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein Has Been Terminated From The Weinstein Company, Effective Immediately: He's out. The co-founder… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Bachelor in Paradise Stars Raven Gates and Adam Gottschalk's Relationship: Raven Gates and Adam Gottschalk… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Little Richard Calls Same-Sex Relationships ''Unnatural Affections'' Years After Coming Out as Gay: Little Richard… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kaia Gerber Returns To LA After Whirlwind Modeling Tour In Europe: She left being a normal teen and came back a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessie James Decker Is Pregnant With Baby No. 3: See Her Hottest PDA Moments With Hubby Eric Decker: Baby, baby,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Zolciak's Daughter Brielle Biermann Flips Off Photographers Asking About Her Feud With Nene Leakes: You just… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Stiller Steps Out on Red Carpet With Daughter Ella Months After Announcing Separation: Ben Stiller has a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Late-Night Hosts React to Harvey Weinstein Allegations: After calling for better gun control following the Las… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry and Meghan Markle "Are as Good as Engaged": Prince Harry and Meghan Markle are making their way… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom Petty Dead at 66: UPDATE: After a mix of headlines surfaced throughout the day, Tom Petty's longtime manager… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blac Chyna And Rob Kardashian Are Now Being Sued By Her Ex, Pilot Jones: Lawsuits all around! Now Blac Chyna's… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maksim Chmerkovskiy Couldn't Be More "Proud" of Dancing With the Stars Partner Vanessa Lachey: Enough with those… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Craig Robinson Says He Lost 50 Pounds by Going Vegan and Not Drinking Alcohol: He put down the drink and picked up… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ava Phillippe, Kaia Gerber, Christian Combs and Every Celeb Kid Taking the Modeling World By Storm: The list of… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Finally! The Law and Order: SVU Change Everyone--Including Kelli Giddish--Has Been Waiting For: Things are changing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's Why Asiah Collins and Kid Ink Travel With a "Family Bus" and a "F--kery Bus" While on Tour: The couple that… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mean Girls Day: Cast Starts GoFundMe Campaign for Las Vegas Shooting Victims: "It's October 3rd." For Mean Girls… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kendall Jenner Says She ''Felt So F--king Stupid'' After Her First Big Controversy: ''I Would Never Purposely Hurt… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben Affleck Gets Uncomfortable When Asked About Harvey Weinstein, After Releasing A Statement Condemning The… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jason Aldean and Wife Brittany Head Back to Las Vegas ''to Start the Healing Process'': A lot can change in seven… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Julianne Hough's Makeup Artist Reveals How to Make Your Eyes Pop: There's a reason why celebs like Julianne Hough,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lea Michele's Makeup Artist Shares a Quick-Fix Beauty Tip: Thank goodness for wet wipes! Some days you got it, and… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Celeb Trainer Shares Workouts You Can Do in Jeans: The excuses we find for not exercising are endless. Are you… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch Ashley Nicole Get Ready to Walk Down the Aisle in WAGS Miami Season Finale Sneak Peek: "This Is My Moment":… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein Accused of Nearly 30 Years of Alleged Sexual Misconduct After Ashley Judd and More Speak Out:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SNL Makes Trump Look Like An Idiot For Puerto Rico Mishandling: It's a new season and SNL isn't giving up! The show… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harvey Weinstein Takes Leave Of Absence After New York Times Expose Blows The Lid Off Decades Of Sexual Harassment:… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's Why Tim McGraw and Faith Hill Are Releasing Their First Album Together After 21 Years of Marriage: Still in… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
