<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[The world's hottest tech companies are now worth more than $5 trillion, and they could be pointing out the next big… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Japan tops Colombia 2-1 in group stage, making World Cup history #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Senate rebukes Trump, reimposes sanctions on ZTE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demolition: 1,500 Pounds Of Dynamite Vs Two Cooling Towers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Opioid death toll in Canada nearly 4,000 last year, new data show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aurora-based Magna strikes deal with China’s largest electric vehicle maker #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India, Russia weigh rupee-rouble trade for defence deals #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon just made a subtle change to its website, and some shoppers say they're stressed (AMZN) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senegal gets Africa's first points, upsetting Poland 2-1 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Turn Off Smart Replies in the New Gmail #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Black Panther' star Chadwick Boseman gave up his 'Best Hero' MTV award to a guy who stopped a mass shooting #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Monday Insider Notes: Cole Anthony, Reid Travis, predictions and more notes on UK targets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10,000 Australians held a vigil for a young woman killed while walking home, and it's bringing attention to a much… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Trump Gets Right About Europe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump To Meet With Republicans During Crucial Week On Immigration #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In an exasperating abdication of responsibility, the Supreme Court says 'never mind' on gerrymandering #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump To Withdraw From UN Human Rights Council Today #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[El Salvador says Donald Trump violating human rights with zero-tolerance border policy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CVS just made a move that could protect itself from Amazon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Colombia World Cup Roster 2018: National Team Players &amp; Jersey Numbers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smoking Rates In U.S. Hit All-Time Low, CDC Says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump, Republicans to huddle as outrage grows over family separation border policy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Essential California: Fury by the border #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carlos Vela posts touching tribute after grandfather’s passing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bizarre Amazon Patent Application Suggests Jellyfish-Like Drones for Warehouses #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Southern Border Crisis Has To Be Fixed By Congress, Gidley Says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Migrant kids are ‘child actors,’ Ann Coulter says on Fox News, telling Trump not to be fooled #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 killed, 12 wounded in shootings in Chicago Monday #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Turnbull government: Those who would destroy the ABC, if they could #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stock Markets Drop Amid Escalating Tariff Threats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stock Markets Drop Amid Escalating Tariff Threats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google will fix Home and Chromecast bug that reveals your location #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[tvOS 12 developer beta 2 for Apple TV 4 and Apple TV 4K now available #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon Prime now available in Australia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leigh Valentine: If You Don’t Like That God Is Using Trump To Save America Then ‘Just Get Out’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rapper XXXTentacion killed in apparent robbery #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[World Cup 2018: England up and running with win, Russia back in action â live! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smart Speaker Owners Aren't Yet Widely Using Them to Control Connected Home Devices #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Early red card dooms Colombia in 2-1 loss to Japan #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How a Mexican soccer star accused of laundering money for drug cartels became a pariah at the World Cup #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Thinks He’s Being Mistreated By Media Coverage Of Family Separations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No, Trump Isn’t ‘Losing’ Immigrant Kids Or Ripping Apart Families. Here Are the FACTS. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Laura Bush pens scathing column on child separation as part of immigration policy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon Hub lets you receive packages even when you’re not in your apartment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Daily Show' slams Donald Trump for tearing apart families at the border #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Conservative riding head steps down after ties to Quebec far-right group revealed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Twitter Baffled By Trump’s Call for Stronger Borders to Stop… Canadian Shoe Smugglers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ex-FIFA head Blatter flying to Moscow for World Cup: spokesman #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Americans are satisfied with Trump’s North Korea summit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apprenticeship plans expand as Florida, federal programs near #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Authorities: Rapper XXXTentacion shot dead in Florida #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Armed civilian who took down Walmart shooter is pastor, medic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The World’s Oldest Known Sumatran Orangutan Has Died at Age 62 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fox News Host: Rep. Elijah Cummings Would ‘Rather Cry on Television’ Than Fix Immigration #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Florida man chugged a beer after being pulled over for suspicion of drunk driving #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saudia Arabia’s World Cup Team Plane Catches Fire In Midair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump's $200bn threat to China #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Market Snapshot: Dow futures slump more than 350 points as fears of a U.S.-China trade war ratchet up #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nielsen becomes the public face of Trump’s family separation policy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Man, 36, shot in Roseland #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All the rights EU citizens in the UK are set to lose after Brexit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are you trying the newest Android or iOS betas? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google's Larry Page 'floored' an early investor when he predicted it could be twice as big as Yahoo before it even… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9to5Toys Lunch Break: 27″ 5K iMac $800+ off, high-end 15″ MacBook Pro $2,299, Beats Headphones from $50, more #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Russia betting favorite vs. Egypt for Tuesday World Cup game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[England v Australia: third one-day international – live! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YouTube Picture in Picture is now available in Canada, with YouTube Premium #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Obama Prosecuted Nearly Half A Million Illegals #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump is using children as political bargaining chips. It doesn't get more crassly cynical #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WORLD CUP ROUNDUP: England avoids draw as Kane delivers stunner in stoppage time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump calls for tariffs on additional $200B in Chinese goods as trade war ramps up #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hands on: Google delivers simplicity w/ the long-awaited Android Messages for web [Gallery] #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Putnam 'Up &amp; Adam' event set for Oviedo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chinese Embassy Lashes Out Over Australian TV Segment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rapper XXXTentacion, 20, shot dead in Florida in 'armed robbery' as he left motorcycle dealership #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rush Limbaugh: Trump's family separation is a "manufactured crisis"; ???It???s all about people attempting to invad… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hands-on video likely gives the world its first look at Apple’s next-gen iPhone designs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Embattled Deputy Attorney General Rod Rosenstein wins case at US Supreme Court #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These 2018 iPhone mockups just got compared to last year's devices (VIDEO) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RF Front-End Modules Comparison Teardown Report 2018: Overview of Components Found in Products from Apple, Samsung,… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beijing isn't backing down, slaps tariffs on U.S. imports #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smoking reaching all-time low with US adults, government report shows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Smart move: Russia Dumps Half Of Its US Debt #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Malacañang: Like it or not, Sereno ouster final #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear EU Parliament: Why Are You About To Allow US Internet Companies To Decide What EU Citizens Can Say Online? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Westworld Mobile arrives this week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Call for US to adopt European-style privacy regulations; 90% of 9to5Mac readers in favor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Intel has paths around Trump’s China tariffs, analysts say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thexfiles: a literal child: why is the sky blue? some of yall: this filthy demon is demanding... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In support of President Trump’s policy of separating children from their mothers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Fox, ICE director defends tearing asylum-seeking families apart using a misleading statistic on human smuggling #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Apple AirPlay 2: All the details on Apple's latest streaming tech #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Parkland shooting survivor is reigniting his war against Laura Ingraham. Here are all of the advertisers that cut… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Political parties need privacy laws, all-party committee says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mexico’s fans went wild during World Cup win. But did the celebration really register on seismometers? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spain face World Cup date with destiny against Iran #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Family separations won't stop Asa from sending Guard to border #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google Fiber Microtrenching Blamed for Surge in Outages - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nokia X6 Global version listed on Bluetooth sites, along with Nokia 5.1 Plus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[As Merkel holds off collapse of her government, Trump tweets Europe made a âbig mistakeâ accepting migrants #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
