<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Scariest Movies That Made A Ton Of Money: Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman headline the 1995 psychological thri... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a reason some of us love scary movies (and some of us don't): Each Halloween, we are reminded that we... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Halloween, zombies, movies changing Mexico’s Day of the Dead: MEXICO CITY &gt;&gt; Hollywood movies, zombie shows, ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Hotels Made Famous By The Movies: Sometimes when you see a hotel in a movie you just want to go there. Som... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Halloween movies that starred actors before they were famous: • Many famous actors have started their care... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Great horror movies cursed with really terrible sequels: "The Birds II: Land's End" (1994) was so bad, it ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interview: Heather Graham on My Dead Boyfriend and Scary Movies: The lovely Heather Graham has grown up in th... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['I love you, Kate Middleton!': the worst TV movies about the royal family: Netflix’s new series The Crown is ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talking movies with Prasanna and Sneha: A flight of colourful birds takes off from the wall, cheerful cushion... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Presidents in the movies: What Hollywood's portrayals show about America: The film is a comedy, which is what... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best TV Shows and Movies New to Netflix, Hulu and More in November: Welcome to Watching, The New York Tim... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 movies that were sheer living hell to make: Are you sitting comfortably? Enjoying that popcorn, are you? Go... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Movies Leaving Netflix In November: As per usual for Netflix, the streaming service will lay some of its movi... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a reason some of us love scary movies (and some of us don't): Each Halloween, we are reminded that we... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 12 Best Halloween Movies That Aren’t Halloween: Okay guys, so we all know John Carpenter‘s 1978 slasher c... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do You Like Scary Movies? Here's a Theory Why: “We are all born with different personalities and temperaments... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Movies and TV Shows Coming to Netflix, HBO, Amazon Prime, and Hulu in November: Creed, Boyhood, All ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tired of Blocked Torrent Sites? Here’s How You Can Download an Endless Array of Movies and TV Series with a S... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 10 Best Movies Set In Or Around Halloween Night: October 31st is upon us, and as Halloween month comes to... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The most culturally important horror movies: I am currently working on a long-term project about horror movie... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Interview: Heather Graham on My Dead Boyfriend and Scary Movies: The lovely Heather Graham has grown up in th... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Scary Clown Movies to Watch This Halloween: Why in the the world are clowns so scary and creepy? Why are t... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Horror Movies That Pass the Bechdel Test: We're going to make a bold statement: Horror movies depend on wo... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a reason some of us love scary movies (and some of us don't): Each Halloween, we are reminded that we... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Where to watch free movies online — the legal way: Everyone has those days where they fire up Netflix or Hulu... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Presidents in the movies: What Hollywood's portrayals show about America: The film is a comedy, which is what... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dear Science: Why do people like scary movies and haunted houses?: All my friends are trying to convince me t... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 reasons why scary books are better than scary movies: I am terrible at watching scary movies — even when th... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Criterion and Turner Classic Movies Hope to Crack the Streaming Business With FilmStruck: If you build it... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Binge Watch ‘Batman’ Movies on HBO in November: Starting Nov. 1, HBO subscribers can watch nearly every moder... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best TV Shows and Movies New to Netflix, Hulu and More in November: Welcome to Watching, The New York Tim... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Movie Monday: Three must see war movies: These 3 upcoming battles films are certain to keep you on the edge o... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17 movies to watch on Netflix when you hate everything: No matter how peppy you are or how much you love life... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talking movies with Prasanna and Sneha: A flight of colourful birds takes off from the wall, cheerful cushion... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Presidents in the movies: What Hollywood's portrayals show about America: The film is a comedy, which is what... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is ‘Billy Lynn’ Going To Change Movies Forever?: The three-time Oscar winner’s latest, Billy Lynn’s Long Half... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[George Romero Can’t Make The Zombie Movies He Wants Because of ‘The Walking Dead’ and ‘World War Z’: For the ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Top 10 Favorite Feminist Horror Movies Will Scare the Crap Out of You While Making You Think: I think the ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best TV Shows and Movies New to Netflix, Hulu and More in November: Welcome to Watching, The New York Tim... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Captain Marvel and Black Widow signal the coming of female superhero movies: Scarlett Johansson made her debu... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything Coming to Movies On Demand In November 2016: November on Movies on Demand features a plethora of k... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 reasons why scary books are better than scary movies: I am terrible at watching scary movies — even when th... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Fantastic Beasts’ Points Wand at $75 Million Debut, Lower Than All ‘Harry Potter’ Movies: The big question m... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Classic International Movies: “Vampyr”: Plot summary: The young Allan Grey is a student of the occult who arr... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unforgettable movies of Shah Rukh Khan: Having appeared in more than 80 movies in Bollywood, Shah Rukh Khan h... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Best TV Shows and Movies to Stream in November: From the return of "Gilmore Girls' to the 'Citizen Kane' o... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Family-Friendly Halloween Movies, From ‘Hocus Pocus’ to ‘Goonies’: Lest we forget, Halloween is more than ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Walking Dead Ruined Zombie Movies for George A. Romero: The Walking Dead is back in a big way. After ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Walking Dead Ruined Zombie Movies for George R. Romero: The Walking Dead is back in a big way. After ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Best Android Streaming Apps to Get Movies and TV Shows for Free: This addon may contain pirated content. C... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 ‘Romeo and Juliet’ Movies, Ranked: Baz Luhrmann’s energetic adaptation of Romeo and Juliet, starring Leona... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do You Like Scary Movies? Here's a Theory Why: “We are all born with different personalities and temperaments... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“Why I weep whenever I watch my evil roles in movies” – Veteran Actress, Patience Ozokwor: Veteran actress, P... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A chat about an AI bot that fetches movies you love from all over the web: Arun and Riya are looking forward ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Criterion and Turner Classic Movies Hope to Crack the Streaming Business With FilmStruck: If you build it... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[New Netflix TV Shows And Movies To Watch This November: As the calendar turns we find ourselves with another ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“Why I weep whenever I watch my evil roles in movies” – Veteran Actress, Patience Ozokwor: Veteran actress, P... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scene Pick’s: Spooky Movies: Today, Scene shares their favorite horror movies that are sure to get the skin c... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A chat about an AI bot that fetches movies you love from all over the web: Arun and Riya are looking forward ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Books That Are Way Scarier Than Horror Movies]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mount Rushmore in the movies: Mount Rushmore in the movies It's Mount Rushmore National Monument's 75th birth... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17 movies to watch on Netflix when you hate everything: No matter how peppy you are or how much you love life... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[People Who Worked on Horror Movies Share the Creepiest Things That Happened on Set: Whether you’re a horror a... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix Halloween Movies: What to Watch if You're Not Trick-or-Treating: If trick-or-treating doesn't sound a... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[George Romero Can’t Make The Zombie Movies He Wants Because of ‘The Walking Dead’ and ‘World War Z’: For the ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read if you dare: The book isn’t too far from the movie, bu... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kevin Feige Is Ready to Move Beyond the ‘Completely White’ Casts of Comic-Book Movies: Chiwetel Ejiofor and B... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[12 ‘Romeo and Juliet’ Movies, Ranked: Baz Luhrmann’s energetic adaptation of Romeo and Juliet, starring Leona... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China Film Official Insists There’s No Ban on Hollywood Movies With Chinese Villains: A top Chinese film offi... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After Delay, Turner Launches Netflix-Style FilmStruck Service With Classic, Indie and Foreign Movies: Turner ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHL players reveal their favorite scary movies: Watching scary movies is a Halloween tradition, and NHL playe... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do You Like Scary Movies? Here's a Theory Why: “We are all born with different personalities and temperaments... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 75 Best Horror Movies of All-Time: Horror films are something you have to prepare for. Whether it’s gripp... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A chat about an AI bot that fetches movies you love from all over the web: Arun and Riya are looking forward ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Do You Like Scary Movies? Here's a Theory Why: “We are all born with different personalities and temperaments... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It Happened On Halloween: The Best Horror Movies Set on Oct 31: There are plenty of amazing horror films out ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Posts Tagged ‘best movies set in Halloween’: October 31st is upon us, and as Halloween month comes to an end,... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Frank Miller Says ‘Batman’ Movies Should Be More Grounded and Lead to Fewer Toys: The city in question is Got... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How the Walking Dead Ruined Zombie Movies for George A. Romero: The Walking Dead is back in a big way. After ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Unforgettable movies of Shah Rukh Khan: Having appeared in more than 80 movies in Bollywood, Shah Rukh Khan h... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bad Horror Movies Are Good For You: Ghoulies Monster Why Bad Horror Movies Are Good For You Humankind’s love ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talking movies with Prasanna and Sneha: A flight of colourful birds takes off from the wall, cheerful cushion... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top 10 Movies at the US Box Office This Weekend: The Tyler Perry movie Boo! A Madea Halloween ruled the weeke... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A chat about an AI bot that fetches movies you love from all over the web: Arun and Riya are looking forward ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[“Why I Weep Whenever I Watch My Wicked Roles In Movies” – Actress, Patience Ozokwor: Veteran actor, Patience ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shatrughan Sinha Was Mad For Movies In Childhood: Veteran actor Shatrughan Sinha was debuted in Hindi Cinema ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Critical Distance: INFERNO, Why It's Good to See Bad Movies: The word is out on Ron Howard's Inferno. Only 20... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Horror Movies That Pass the Bechdel Test: We're going to make a bold statement: Horror movies depend on wo... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Five Best Movies You Can Watch Free On Vudu That Aren't On Netflix: Walmart-owned Vudu announced it would... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 10 best new movies and TV shows coming to Netflix in November: Some months are better than others when it... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[James Gunn Directed Stan Lee Cameos For The Next Three Marvel Movies: Every Marvel fan knows that a Stan Lee ... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sharks, spinning heads and aliens: Ten top grossing horror movies: Traditionally, horror movies have been goo... #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Songs Made Infinitely Creepier by Horror Movies: A great horror movie without a great soundtrack simply doe... #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
