<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Initial Exchange Offerings Are Providing Big Returns, But Why? - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s Time for Every Sign to Shake! Things! Up! - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shares snap seven-day hot streak; U.S. inflation next hurdle By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I have a feeling the Nigeria vs The Rest of The World will kickoff soon.  First, it was the South Africans. Now it's the…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pre-order the new (adorable) Echo Dot Kids Edition, on sale for $49.99 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[UK Insurer L&amp;G Using Amazon's Blockchain Service for Bulk Pensions Deals - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vampire: The Masquerade - Bloodlines 2 : Tracking Your Prey Gameplay]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blockchain-Based Arm of Live Planet Acquires Former 20th Century Fox CTO By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[South African tribunal says it can't charge foreign banks in rand-rigging case By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reckitt picks PepsiCo man as CEO, going outside for first time By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coinbase's crypto debit card arrives to 6 new European countries - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sony noise-canceling headphones are $51.99 off on Amazon - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wall Street split on Tesla 2019 delivery promises By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Legend of Zelda, iRobot Roomba, Google Pixel 3a, Sony Alpha, and more deals for June 12 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CryptoCompare Launches Benchmark Rankings for Cryptocurrency Exchanges - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel's Avengers Game: The Internet Was Pretty Unkind To Square Enix's E3 2019 Reveal Trailer - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tether (USDT) Stablecoin Supply Exceeds 4 Billion on All Networks By Cryptovest - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Crude Oil Inventories Rose by 2.21M Barrels Last Week: EIA By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bitcoin Struggles for Price Gains As Litecoin Hits 13-Month high - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stocks- U.S. Futures Pull Back as Trump Toughens Stance on China Trade Deal By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. mortgage lenders optimism on profits return: survey By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nash Prepares to Launch Beta Version of Decentralized Exchange - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wall Street Flat as Inflation Supports Fed Rate Cut; Trade Tensions Weigh By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NordVPN's 3-year plan is now available for just £2.29 a month - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Etekcity Bluetooth smart body fat scale down to under £26 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019 - Crash Team Racing: Nitro-Fueled Free DLC Revealed, Including Spyro - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oninaki: What To Expect From This Fast Paced Action Game]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNBC TV18  LIVE || Business News in English - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FATF to Release New Rules for Global Crypto Sector, Impacting Exchanges, Funds, Custodians By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Refurbished iRobot Roomba 860 robot vacuum is $180 off at Amazon - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lost socks are a thing of the past thanks to this genius hack - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019: Fallout 76 Selling Special Bundle For Limited Time - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019 Schedule In Full: All Conferences, Events, Live Shows, And More - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best MAC Lipstick for Dark Skin So You Can Find a Signature Shade - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zara Owner Inditex Is Back in the Groove By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Acrylic Nail Hacks That Anyone With Dramatically Long Claws Should Master - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medical News Today: How is education linked to Alzheimer&amp;#HASHTAG#;s progress? - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Learn from an expert for less than $10 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Elon Musk says Tesla pickup will look like it 'came out of a sci-fi movie' - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dutch lawmakers step up tax demands on multinationals By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CCN Casts Doubt on Shutdown Plans as Google Appears to Correct Visibility By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019: TurboGrafx-16 Mini Announced, First Six Games Revealed - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[India stocks lower at close of trade; Nifty 50 down 0.50% By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The increase in cyber fraud (Yahoo Yahoo) has been in the rise. The latest being the 80 Nigerians in the Largest cyber fraud…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019: The New Xbox Is Scarlett, Launches Holiday 2020 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Enigma's Ethereum-Based Private Smart Contract Testnet Goes Live By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Nigerians have become endangered species globally, South Africans are hating us, African Americans are hating us, our sin…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crypto Winter Is Ending By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[IBM, Maersk's Blockchain Platform TradeLens Is Shipping to Russia - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I went to Hampton University and Georgetown, not using a dollar of aid meant for ‘African Americans’. This was true for most of…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oil demand growth grinding to lowest in years as global economy stalls By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This online coding course teaches C and is on sale for less than $40 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019: Xbox Scarlett Available Holiday 2020, Microsoft Confirms - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[JPMorgan Says Treasury 10-Year Yield May Be Set for More Upside By Bloomberg - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Save £220 on the Oral-B Genius 9000 electric toothbrush - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ford recalls 1.2 million Explorer SUVs for suspension issue By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019: The Witcher 3 On Switch Will Run At 540p In Handheld Mode, 720p Dynamic Resolution Docked - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brazilian President Rebuffs Cryptocurrency as His Administration Explores Blockchain - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This HP monitor and desktop bundle is only $369 — almost 50% off - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huawei cancels laptop launch because of U.S. ban - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Save 10% on the ultimate gimbal for your GoPro - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies Rise as Litecoin Leads Gains at 13-Month High By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gold Prices Rise after Trump Admits ‘Holding Up’ Deal with China, CPI on Tap By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former US Senator Rick Santorum Supports New Crypto for Catholics - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Napster Founder's IoT Startup Is Adding Tokens With $15 Million Round Led by USV, Multicoin - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: I understand the fears of the African Americans and South Africans and why they treat us different too🤣  Trust me, no one w…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John McAfee Unveils Magic Crypto Trading Platform; Promises Your Keys Your Crypto By Cryptovest - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dying Light 2: Infection And Exploration Evolved]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ArcelorMittal boss says EU must respond further to Trump's steel tariffs By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[There's a deepfake of Zuckerberg on Instagram. Your move, Facebook. - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber's newest self-driving car is here, courtesy of Volvo - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coinbase Expands Cryptocurrency Visa Debit Cards Across Europe - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: African Americans and South Africans should create a continent of their own where no other foreign national will associa…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Carrie Lam remains defiant as Hong Kong gears up for fresh protests - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nintendo E3 2019 Recap: Switch Announcements - Breath Of The Wild 2, Games, News, Trailers, And More - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Renault chairman weakened as Macron snubs meeting By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[De'Longhi Autentica coffee machine on sale for under £340 - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside Monero's 'Last Ditch Effort' to Block Crypto Mining ASICs - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CryptoCompare Launches Exchange Benchmark in Response to Concerns Over False Volume Reporting By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: #USER# The palace leads you to fame, the market leads you to fortune and loneliness leads you to wisdom.  Remember t…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cardano Climbs 10% In a Green Day By #URL# - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medical News Today: Insomnia: &amp;#HASHTAG#;Long-distance&amp;#HASHTAG#; CBT as effective as in-person therapy - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Motorbike taxi firms rev up for race into West Africa By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[De'Longhi coffee machines, Samsung 4K TVs, Sony portable speakers, Fossil smartwatches, and more on sale for June 1… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The easiest way to relax during a workout, according to fitness experts - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Nigerians are facing the 'ko s ogbon to le da ' syndrome all over the world. We do bad, we are frauds, we do good, we are…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adidas slides as traders say top investor GBL plans to sell part of stake By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Ghost Recon: Breakpoint Is A Hardcore Survival Shooter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: First it was South Africa now African Americans  Tell me is it an offence to be hardworking??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best tech of 2019 (so far) - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ford to spend $180 million to fix suspension issue in Explorer vehicles By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Azerbaijan Government Partners With IBM on Blockchain Customs Deal By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Major Hong Kong Property Firm to Seek Regulatory Approval for Tokenized Real Estate By Cointelegraph - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to stop thinking about someone in 6 easy steps - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel's Avengers Game: The Internet Was Not Kind To Square Enix's E3 2019 Reveal Trailer - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E3 2019 Recap: Nintendo Announcements - Breath Of The Wild 2, Switch Games, News, Trailers, And More - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[is it worth the hype - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Glossier Brow Flick Is the Next Boy Brow - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. stock futures decline ahead of inflation reading By Reuters - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Outer Worlds: Taking The New Vegas Formula To Space]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
