<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump has taken over $10000 from every man woman and child to prop up his failing economy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes, because you keep trying to claim that your religious beliefs have some authority, they don't.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# And Trump changed the policy. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So after Dr Ben Carson has finished his abortion experiments?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# But not from Trump's skyrocketing deficits.  You'll be paying for those for your whole life.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# As long as everyone is capable of consent, this hurts no one.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# According to you. Others have a Constitutional right to interpret differently. You hav… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# If you like deficits stolen from our grandchildren]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh no, big words, do they confuse Trumphumpers?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Yes it is, your opinion counts for nothing regarding other people's Constitutional rel… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Who changed the policy and now removes children from their parents?  Trump.  The child snatcher.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Because there is already a federal law that does exactly that]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Says you. Which is irrelevant. They have Constitutional religious freedom from your th… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Awesome. Constitutional religious freedom in practice.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# That's the policy change that introduced family destruction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# How did Weld and Bloomberg do?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No,but i now owe that amount extra.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Family destruction is the Trump policy change]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Costs... Healthcare for all, College for all, Fair Taxation burden distribution, Balanced bu… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# The deficit is up 148% in 3 years]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# I get it, you are a homophobic theocratic fascist who thinks everyone should have to… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Awesome, Constitutional religious freedom in action.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# From the Trump doj in his first April]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Murderous Trumphumper neonazi thugs killed innocent people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The skyrocketing deficit.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Now try and care this much about children in cages.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Irrelevant to other people's Constitutional religious freedom to believe differently t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I'd guess a typo. Probably born in 1923.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Run by the attorney general acting on Trump's orders.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Racist cowards are so scared of brown people.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You don't get to deny others their Constitutional religious freedom.  Your theocratic… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# The GOP, the party of criminals.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# McConnell will block anything anyway, so why bother?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, 10.6 to 19.9 isn't double.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Trump defended him as 'good people']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So says you. Their church says different. Your beliefs are irrelevant to their beliefs… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Oh, poor baby, did Obama not fix Bush's record deficit immediately? How te… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# You lost dixville notch to Bloomberg!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No, they changed policy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Trump cites his own economic failure in proposed cut to planned federal raise]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Trump has already abandoned it.  148% deficit increase in just 3 years!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# When Obama cut the deficit by a record amount.  I liked that.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What you think the Bible teaches is irrelevant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Unless its farmers?  Or deficit spending?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Irrelevant, you made a claim about 'rich' people, without defining what rich is.  Top 50%? 10%? 1%?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Half the number of Democrat votes.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# So I'm correct, thanks.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# Should be epic]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# But as Bernie doesn't want Socialism, your point is moot.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Nope, family separation is a Trump policy.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Family breakup is a Trump Policy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# He's even blocking Trump now!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What you think about scripture is irrelevant to the Constitutional religious freedom o… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Enjoy Trump bankrupting the USA]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# So a public option would be so popular Private insurance would cease to be.  Sounds great.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Well no, because no one else was handed a $1417b deficit by their predeces… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Like all the Trump operatives registered in multiple States?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: Powerful! Here's the video: "Jim Jordan called me crying"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# You tool.  You voted to leave the EU.  You are the immigrant.  These are the checks non EU citizen… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# If you know, why are you afraid to tell me how much?  Oh, and in Canada UK France Australia Ja… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are they enjoying the $10000 debt each?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How much has his skyrocketing deficit cost the black community?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# For Anti American bigots.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No,  #URL#  Are you ignorantly confusing the debt with the deficit?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Oh...so Constitutional religious freedom only applies to your religion and denominati… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# The deficit has increased 148% in Trump's 3 years.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# He beat you in Dixville notch!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# #USER# No,family destruction was not the Obama policy]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# But, but, but Obama!  Soviet style whataboutism is irrelevant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Given the number of child rapes in churches, we should therefore shut those down as well!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Uncle Gym the Fiddler]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How much does the USA currently pay for Government healthcare per capita?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# He won Dixville notch as a write in!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# It skyrockets the deficit over $1t for years and years, and the debt to over $30t.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# What happens to GDP, the stock market, jobs, etc if you remove Trump's $1063 billion annual unpaid stimulus?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You do realize that marriage at that age is legal in many US States because of fundamentalist Christianity?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your opinion is irrelevant to their rights.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Thanks for highlighting the difference between unaccompanied minors and family destruction.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Because Constitutional religious freedom is supreme to your theocratic fascism.  It me… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# This is Twitter, have you considered a whiteboard to make these little memory aids for yourself?  Dementia Donnie.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, a trump policy change at the doj April 14th or 25th 2017 i think, trying to remember.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# How special for Anti American bigots like you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your theocratic extremism is irrelevant to the Constitutional religious freedom of others.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# How is your $1t plus deficit fiscally responsible?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# They aren't, but they feel it.  Facts don't care about your feelings]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# What did you run for?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# All churches share the problem.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: The next time you hear conservatives claim we can't afford Medicare for All, remember that it would actually save $450B and pr…]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Roger is a criminal. A threat to society.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I cannot believe that any man not personally and actively involved in the abuse of children would… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Remember that 94 million out of the labor force that Trump screamed about and blamed Obama?  Its 96 million now...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# I'd gladly 'give back' the $10,000 plus Trump has cost me so far.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Your interpretation is irrelevant to the Constitutional religious freedom if others to interpret differently.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# You haven't defined what you mean by rich.  What % are YOU referring to?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I wonder why so many of Trump's ex hookers are subject to non disclosure orders?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Are you drunk?  It sets $1t plus deficits into the future!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Socialist healthcare concentrating on cures not profits.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# Says you. So what? Your theocratic fascism is irrelevant.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# No, it was a policy change in the April of 2017.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# So companies can thrive under a single payer single provider taxpayer funded universal… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
