<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Trump Makes History, Delivers Powerful Message at March for Life Rally #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Eight Rockets Hit Iraqi Military Base Housing American Troops -- 4 Injured #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Washington Post Covers for Amazon’s Supplement Fraud #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump &amp; Melania Get ROARING Applause At College Championship Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adam Schiff Faces Impeachment Fallout as Celeb Dr. Drew Mulls Primarying Him #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Told the One Dirty Secret Everyone in Washington Covered Up #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[if thisisn't the cutest darn thing. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi Loses It On House Floor, Compares Trump To Murdering Mobster #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Petition: 80,000 Canadians Demand Prince Harry, Meghan Markle Pay Their Own Security #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Trump Has Hilarious Time Welcoming LSU Football Team To White House #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this info needs to go viral.  please share. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sacramento Taxpayers President Warns of Prop. 13 Bait and Switch - California Globe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mexico Will Crack Down on Central American Caravan Bound for US #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[McConnell Reveals Impeachment Trial Rules With Firm Warning To Democrats #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fb sent me a quote I posted of John Lennon 5 years ago for reposting. .  I ok'd it.  they then blocked it saying it… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Knew they couldn't get along financially without the Royal monies coming to them. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Calif. AG uses misleading language to raise $12.5 billion in new taxes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYT: Trump's Economic Sanctions Have Destroyed Iran's Will to Fight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC Admits 98 Million Americans Were Given Cancer Virus Via The Polio Shot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tamiflu Fraud Bilked $1.5 Billion from Government, Alleges Whistleblower #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Sets The Internet On Fire With Meme Of The CENTURY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Breaking: Two Rockets Hit Near U.S. Embassy In Iraq #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[this is so sad.  God bless them. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hempworx is the most forward looking company ever.  we now have Spanish subtitles on the site  More languages to come.  Whoa.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Legal Team Launches All Out Assault Against Democrats’ Partisan Impeachment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Attention everyone!!  the C B D industry is about to become a multi-billion dollar industry.  People are waking up… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How five members of Joe Biden’s family got rich through his connections #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[please share this and share this. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the stupidity of youth today. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Samantha Markle Says Sister Meghan Only Wants to Get Rich and ‘be Hollywood’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump: White House will seek to end human trafficking #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani Claims He Will Release Evidence Today that Shows Joe and Hunter Biden Were Involved in a 'Multi-Milli… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran Is Crashing - Lunch Alert! - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iraq Veteran Shares ‘Heroic’ Story About Vince Vaughn Following Uproar Over Trump Handshake #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Pro-Iranian Militia Leader Killed In Iraq by Unidentified Gunmen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hillary's Revenge: She Unloads On Bernie - Lunch Alert! - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump's Support for Iranian Protestors Breaks a Twitter Record, Something the MSM 'Will Not Report' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[absolutely outrageous statements.  what's with this guy.  didn't he get enough money from his daughter? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Meghan Markle's Dad Tears into Daughter in Explosive Interview #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Harry And Meghan Already Find Snag In Canadian Living, Take Legal Action #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Signature the Vietnamese restaurant that opened just a few months ago is already out of business.  feel sorry for t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[totally upset. Instinct will not have a third season.  One of my favorite shows.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Israel Announces New 'Laser Sword' Breakthrough Designed to Shred Enemy Weapons #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden’s Brother Frank Linked to Projects Receiving $54,000,000 in Taxpayer Loans from the Obama Administration—… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The chart the Trump campaign should be 'plastering absolutely everywhere': Deirdre Bolton #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Project Veritas Drops More Bernie Bombshells, And Things Are Worse Than We Thought #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry, Meghan Markle Will No Longer Use Royal Titles, Queen and Buckingham Palace Announce #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Look WHO’s Talking! Vaccine Scientists Confirm Major Safety Problems • Children's Health Defense #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Green Puppy Born To A White German Shepherd Had The Humans Freaking Out #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I wrote Aron's story before and had absolutely no comments.  maybe if you hear it in his words, you will understand… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy, Jr. Assembles Legal Team to Sue FCC over Wireless Health Guidelines • Children's Health Defense #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Feds Blame De Blasio For Murder Of 92-Year-Old Woman By Illegal Immigrant #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Project Veritas Drops Bombshell Hidden Camera Videos Exposing Bernie's Campaign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Warren's Son In Law Produced Iranian Government Funded Film #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aron and Cathy Parker - 500k Affiliate Success Story with MyDailyChoice! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry Breaks Silence After 'Megxit' Announcement #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Financial Records Show Joe Biden Has Made Millions Since Leaving Office. How Did He Do It? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Project Veritas Drops Bombshell Hidden Camera Videos Exposing Bernie's Campaign #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Project Veritas Drops More Bernie Bombshells, And Things Are Worse Than We Thought #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[still getting 3 robo calls a day. anyone else getting them?  thought they were banned.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[check out Erin Elizabeth's page, Health Nut News. amazing summit on anti aging free #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[my god.  what a bunch of cheaters and despictable people. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hundreds of US-Bound Migrants Storm Border, Rush into Mexico #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Your Food Grown on Sewage? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Sends Message Of Support To The Iranian People Written In Persian #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie's Iowa Team on Lockdown After Embarrassing Video Goes Viral #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ghislaine Maxwell’s Emails Hacked, Damaging Info On Famous People Linked To Epstein Sex Trafficking Case Could Be R… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flu Vaccines Increase Lung Tissue Damage and Pneumonia Related Death #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[great.  progress continues to  be made. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[thank you DMV for getting my new license to me before my birthday.  next time can we do a pic that doesn't make me… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adam Schiff Faces Impeachment Fallout as Celeb Dr. Drew Mulls Primarying Him - #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seven Times the GAO Found the Obama Administration Violated Federal Law #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Climate change hoax COLLAPSES as new science finds human activity has virtually zero impact on global temperatures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is this a good thing? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge: Hunter Biden Must Appear in Court After Violating Order to Turn Over Financial Docs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[REPORT: FBI Investigating Ilhan Omar’s ‘Sham Marriage’ — And Now ICE Is Involved #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hempworx expanding for sure.  here are some of the announcements relating to the European market.  let me know who… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love this story.  do you #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran's Only Female Olympic Medalist Announces Her Defection from Iran in Scathing Message #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I love this story, do you? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Corbyn Cordingley Dead 14 Hrs After Flu Shot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MEGXIT: Canadians Overwhelmingly Against Paying For Prince Harry And Meghan Markle To Live There #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[the father now the half sister.  what in god's name are they blaring about?  they really hate her guts. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[do you know that people still eat at Taco Bell.  what are they doing to their insides.  went by one with 15 cars waiting.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr Peter Gøtzsche exposes big pharma as organized crime #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[well, I found one of the social media sites I have been looking for.  MeWe.  have you joined?  I'm going to.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[HAARP OVER AUSTRALIA-GEOENGINEERING / CHEMTRAILS/HAARP These are weapons to manipulate the weather #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dems Reveal Behind Closed-Doors That Pelosi’s Impeachment Stunt ‘Failed’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WATCH: Warren Refuses to Shake Bernie’s Hand After Debate, Bernie Throws Up Hands After They Speak #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Update: Three U.S. Firefighters Killed While Battling Australia's Wildfires Identified #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Caught on Camera: W.H.O. Scientists Question Safety of Vaccines #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[anyone have an alternative to Fb for social media?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Illegal Border Crossings Fall A Staggering 90% In Arizona Following Trump Policy Change #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[anyone know about Zelle pay?  rec'd email that I rec'd a payment.  not opening for sure.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Planned Parenthood, Which Says it Needs Taxpayer Money for 'Health Care,' Just Announced that its Political Arm Wil… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[92-Year-Old Woman Sexually Abused and Murdered by Illegal Alien After New York Refused to Hand Him Over to ICE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders Campaign Staffer Who Called for Gulags, Violence Was Arrested for DUI and Drug Charges #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Robert Kennedy Jr - Science Has Proven Vaccines are NOT safe (Jan 2020) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Feds Investigating Comey Over Leak Tied To Hillary Investigation #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
