<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[You Remember Jessica Simpson, Right? Wrong #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officer Shot in the Bronx in ‘Assassination Attempt,’ Police Commissioner Says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[For 25 Years in Prison, He Said He Was Innocent. A Judge Just Agreed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When the Teenager or Young Adult Has Cancer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Treacherous Antarctic Waters Open Up, Just Briefly #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China Expands Chaotic Dragnet in Coronavirus Crackdown #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiny Love Stories: ‘I Worried About Telling Him My Age’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Takeaways from Today's Trump Impeachment Trial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NBA All-Star Weekend: Celebrity Game photos #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[$9 Cabbages, Emergency Pork: Coronavirus Tests China on Food #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago woman charged with involuntary manslaughter after crash kills her spouse, injures state trooper #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Black athlete says he was wrongly detained, threatened by Illinois police officers at rest stop while traveling wit… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Block Impeachment Witnesses? Republicans Have Many Reasons #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police investigating fatal shooting of Elmwood Park teen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[First Look: Hayden Hall offers DMK-curated bites, natural wine bar and a second Ada St. location #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago Red Stars made big strides last year. But, Sam Kerr or not, they’re looking for more. ‘We expect to be in t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Politics: Our New Morning Tip Sheet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Palestinian Authority Is a Sinking Ship #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brexit is Friday. But as Britain leaves the EU, not much will change immediately. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Curie basketball coach Mike Oliver removed from position amid accusation of ‘physical altercation’ with student #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bulls hope for the returns of injured starters Otto Porter Jr. and Wendell Carter Jr. shortly after the All-Star br… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is the Black Quarterback Revolution Going to Last? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oscars 2020: The complete winners list #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No matter who wins the NBA All-Star Game, Chicago students will benefit. Here are the two charities handpicked by t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jay Cutler reportedly talking to CBS and ESPN about NFL TV job — 2½ years after ‘Very Cavallari’ co-star walked awa… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Afghan Passenger Plane Crashes, Officials Say #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Danny Farquhar throws himself into coaching after near-death experience: ‘I’m just happy to still be alive and stil… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Georgia Drops Special Driver’s License Requirements for Puerto Ricans #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former Coast Guard Lieutenant Is Sentenced to 13 Years in Prison on Gun and Drug Charges #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Homelessness in California: Making Money by Delivering Eviction Notices #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago attorney Kelley Flanagan calls fellow ‘Bachelor’ contestants ‘little babies’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is No Way to Run a Central Bank #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[While Stained in History, Trump Will Emerge From Trial Triumphant and Unshackled #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Question All Democrats Need to Ask Themselves #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Impeachment All but Behind Him, Trump Celebrates and Keeps Focus on Bloomberg #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Like Europe in Medieval Times’: Virus Slows China’s Economy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tenerife - Sporting en directo #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After Disasters, Puerto Ricans Are Left With $1.6 Billion in Unpaid Insurance Claims #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[On Politics: Biden Seizes on a Comment #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The best tweets we saw during the Grammys 2020 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spanish Terrorist Is Extradited From Brazil After Decades on the Run #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats, Coronavirus, the Oscars: Your Friday Briefing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, Merkel’s Anointed Successor, Won’t Run for Chancellor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buffalo Grove trustees approve using motor fuel tax money to pay village’s share on road projects #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A New Martyr Puts a Face on China’s Deepening Coronavirus Crisis #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[They Documented the Coronavirus Crisis in Wuhan. Then They Vanished. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marcus Randle El, who played football at Thornton High School and Wisconsin, charged in deaths of two people in Jan… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With little oversight by Whitney Young leaders, swim coach gained ‘carte blanche’ access to pool, then stole thousa… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘I May Have Killed Someone’: Drifter Charged in Upper East Side Murder #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pilot course on racial equity debuts at OPRF High School #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s Budget Math Grapples With Economic Reality #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Have a Search Warrant for Data? Google Wants You to Pay #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Steven Souza Jr. is ready to make the most of his latest opportunity with the Cubs — whatever his role is #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A look at some key stats and numbers for the Super Bowl #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s Middle East Plan: Starting Point or Dead End? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super Bowl Prediction: Why the 49ers Will Beat the Chiefs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After Acquittal, Trump Repeats Inaccurate Claims on Impeachment and Ukraine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Saudi-Russian Alliance Is Strained as Coronavirus Saps Demand for Oil #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Berkeley Law School Drops Boalt Name Over Racist Legacy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tessa Majors Killing: 14-Year-Old Boy Charged With Murder #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Happy hour deals in Chicago, Feb. 6-12 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ousted From Washington, Ex-Spy Valerie Plame Asks Voters to Send Her Back #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A hard seltzer festival was inevitable and here it comes: Seltzer Land coming to Chicago this spring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fear, Fury and the Coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Think Trump’s Learned a Lesson? Hahahaha #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FDA approves first treatment for kids with peanut allergy #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[State of the Union Address, Impeachment, Iowa: Your Wednesday Briefing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Kicks Off the Daytona 500, and a Race for Florida Votes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Modern Love Podcast: Susan Kelechi Watson Reads ‘When Cupid Is a Prying Journalist’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nissan Sues Carlos Ghosn for $90 Million #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Will Thousands of Latinos in Iowa Be Greeted at ‘El Caucus’? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barbecue spot with sides from family recipes opens in Pullman food hall, plus more Chicago restaurant openings #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Haves of Iowa and the Have-Nots Across the Border #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How Do Bats Live With So Many Viruses? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli Faces New Accusations Over High-Priced Drug #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos’s Phone Hack Should Terrify Everyone #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Damming the Lower Mekong, Devastating the Ways and Means of Life #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Piece of the American Id #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Freshman Sidney Rogers gives Glenbrook South an aggressive edge: ‘When she has the ball, we’re good.' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China Targets the Coronavirus, and Farmers Pay a Price #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iowa Should Never Go First Again #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Saturday Night Live’ Spoofs Trump’s Impeachment Trial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iowa Will Be the First Test Case for 2020 Election Security #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tyson to cut 500 jobs, including some in Chicago, as part of restructuring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Birds of Prey’ review: Harley Quinn and her girl gang are lovable psychopaths #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Sell the Team!’ Please, for the Sake of Mets and Knicks Fans #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 noteworthy moments from the 1988 NBA All-Star Weekend at Chicago Stadium, including a frosty reception for Isiah… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brain Injuries Are Common in Battle. The Military Has No Reliable Test for Them. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Troy Price, Iowa Democratic Party Leader, Resigns Over Caucus Debacle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1 ejected when ambulance hits car stopped on shoulder of Veterans Memorial Tollway near Lockport #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In case you’re wondering what to call Chicago singer Nate Barksdale’s music, take a cue from him and call it ‘neon… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SARS Stung the Global Economy. The Coronavirus Is a Greater Menace. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[In India, Protesters and Modi Tussle Over Who Can Claim Gandhi #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gantz to Meet Trump on Peace Plan, but Alone, Not With Netanyahu #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Librarians Could Face Charges for ‘Age-Inappropriate’ Material Under Proposal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Art Was Looted 123 Years Ago. Will It Ever Be Returned? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maybe you’d like to know real cold? Chicago winter and ‘Call of the Wild’ are reminders of Jack London #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s Team Celebrates Acquittal at (Where Else?) His Washington Hotel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Border Patrol Will Deploy Elite Tactical Agents to Sanctuary Cities #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Brazen Gunman, 2 N.Y.P.D. Officers Shot and the Fallout #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
