<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[This Puppy Loves To Sleep On His Back And The Photos Are Adorable (30 Pics) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Auto Chess on mobile is improving … but confusing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Hellboy In Hell’ Could Someday Be The Live-Action Adaptation We Deserve #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump promise of new Mexican tariffs brings protests #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Balague shares what Pochettino's told him about Tottenham training in build-up to CL final #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BGT Viewers Shocked After Girl Appears To Call Dec The ‘C-Word’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cricket World Cup 2019 live stream: how to watch every game online from anywhere #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Something that no-one expects'...Boss excited at signing Aston Villa prospect #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leeds United should sign free agent who Gerrard compared to James Milner #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China tells Canada of 'consequences' of helping U.S. with Huawei case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WGA’s David Young Defends Chris Keyser, Blasts The Press In Letter To Membership #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tesla opens Model 3 orders in Australia, Japan and a few other places #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Chainsmokers &amp; Bebe Rexha: 'Call You Mine' Stream, Lyrics, &amp; Download - Listen Now! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Planting more trees 'one of the best things we can do' to reduce carbon in the air #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[French Open live stream: how to watch 2019 Roland-Garros tennis online from anywhere #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grey’s Anatomy (Sort Of) Confirms Jackson’s Fate After Season 15 Finale #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mindy Kaling is Supported by B.J. Novak at 'Late Night' Premiere! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What SMEs need to know in the event of a cyberattack #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aurinia Pharmaceuticals Announces Upcoming Annual General Meeting of Shareholders #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Come back': Some Forest fans want 30-year-old to return after what he's just tweeted #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daily Horoscope, Tarot &amp; Numerology Predictions For All Zodiac Signs In Astrology, Friday, May 31, 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Who Is Ronald Stolarczyk? New Details On The Man Who Shot And Killed Burglars In His Home And Is Now In Jail #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift Adds Katy Perry's New Song to Her Apple Playlist! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boxer Anthony Joshua is one giant thirst trap Now that Idris Elba is married, there’s an opening for America’s Next… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scripps spelling bee ends in 8-way championship tie #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best New Knives and EDC of May 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is There a 'Ma' (2019) End Credits Scene? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ITV Orders UK Version Of Hit Reality Series ‘The Masked Singer’ From Argonon’s Bandicoot #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadian brands winning over Chinese consumers despite Canada-China spat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gucci Mane &amp; Justin Bieber: 'Love Thru the Computer' Stream, Lyrics, &amp; Download - Listen Now! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Definitive Timeline Of James Holzhauer’s Historic Run On ‘Jeopardy!’ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drake Jokes He's Selling Steph Curry's Hair Lint on eBay #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Borat’ Kidnapping Staged, Led To Pamela Anderson Marriage Breakup, Says Sacha Baron Cohen #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Eyelid Surgery Right for Me? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Free, Downloadable Tech Backgrounds for June 2019! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Isle of Man TT live stream: how to watch IOMTT 2019 from anywhere #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lakeview Community Partners Limited Presents Refined Plan for Lakeview Village Development #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BlueShore Financial Launches New Financial Spa Branch in Downtown Vancouver’s Financial District #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to watch or download movies for free with CotoMovies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Phoebe Waller-Bridge: James Bond Is “Absolutely Relevant Now” But The Film “Has To Treat Women Properly” #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Cofounder Taught a Group of Male Investors About Periods to Start Her Business #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I Transformed This Bullied Boy Into His Favorite Comic Book Character #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Now You Can Live Like ‘Simpsons’, ‘Stranger Things’ Or ‘Friends’ As IKEA Recreates Rooms From Iconic TV Shows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sennheiser’s AMBEO Soundbar is Calibrated Just for You #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best ‘Friends’ Episodes Of All Time, Ranked #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Huawei Mate 20 Pro makes a comeback on Google's Android Q beta program #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The guide to good swimwear for every shape from €9 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Good Omens is the show that fits the divided world we live in #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['We've missed you'...Some Rangers fans respond to star's message #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[S&amp;P upgrades Indonesia credit after Widodo election win #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Morning After: Ferrari's first PHEV and 'Death Stranding' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump’s surprise tariff threat to Mexico may upend new NAFTA deal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The unsung heroes of 5G: which companies are pushing the tech forward? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's happening to Jupiter's Great Red Spot? Astronomers see unravelling of 400-year-old storm #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Things from the 90s that we will never forget #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kid Can’t Stay On Transplant List Without A Stable Home, So His Teacher Adopts Him #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl Accused Of ‘Stealing’ Someone’s Boyfriend After Posting Shot Of Her Legs #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Awesome Things Gear Patrol Readers Bought in May #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Swimsuits For Every Body Type #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[67 Of The Most Creative 3D-Printing Examples Ever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zion Williamson spurned Jay-Z and LeBron and other news of the week The Week That Was May 27-30 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[I Asked 17 Women To Tell Their Abortion Stories To Make It A Less Confrontational Topic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How do you know that your yogurt is bad? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gerry Ryan's voice will return to RTÉ 2FM in an hour-long special today #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tove Lo: 'Glad He's Gone' Stream, Lyrics, &amp; Download - Listen Now! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 'Schitt's Creek' Cast Attend Emmy FYC Screening! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maine passes bill requiring ISPs to ask permission before selling data #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eight Kids Were Perfect In Becoming Scripps National Spelling Bee Co-Champions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pushing a 28-core CPU to its limits: 6GHz and beyond #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Signs of Being Smothered in a Relationship that Seems Like Love #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The JOE Friday Pub Quiz: Week 142 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber loses $1 billion in Q1 2019 as costs grow for drivers, food delivery #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Irish weather: Met Eireann predicts up to 35mm of rain with warning in place for three counties #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Morning After: 'Modern Warfare' and preparing for WWDC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is There a 'Rocketman' End Credits Scene? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rita Ora, Tiësto, &amp; Jonas Blue: 'Ritual' Stream, Lyrics, &amp; Download - Listen Now! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Intel's Project Athena laptops can sense when you're near #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Microsoft's first UK store opens in London on July 11th #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Artist Illustrates 10 Spirit Animals Related To Mental Health And Many Will Find Their Own In Them #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pixar's Onward teaser reveals Chris Pratt and Tom Holland's new fantasy world #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pedestrian dies after being hit by HGV in suspected hit and run in Dublin #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It’s a very mixed bag on the weather front for the Bank Holiday weekend #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ben &amp; Jerry’s CBD Ice Cream Will Help You ‘Chill’ Out #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[La La Anthony Will Play Brian Austin Green's Breadwinning Wife on BH90210  #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katy Perry Goes Hippie in 'Never Really Over' Video - Watch Now! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to expect at E3 2019 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Raptors are acting like they’ve been here before The Raptors lead the series 1-0 after an all-around effort #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Matthew Vaughn talks X-Men trilogy studio battle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney Reveals 11 Celebrities Behind New Lion King Movie Characters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Citi Recognized for Innovation, Leadership in Derivatives Clearing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What to Watch this Weekend: HBO's Deadwood movie, plus the Good Omens debut #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Avoiding These Deadly Data Backup Sins #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DeepMind AI uses teamwork to defeat human 'Quake III' players #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sprinting burns 40% more fat than other forms of cardio, study finds #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NTT Com Managed Services, Wholly Owned Subsidiary of NTT Communications, Completes 100% Acquisition of CAPSiDE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mike Tyson &amp; Wack 100 Did NOT Come to Blows During Podcast … Just Genius PR #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Forests In Britain That You Wouldn’t Enter At Night #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Bring em back down to earth':..Some Aston Villa fans respond to club tweet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Metal investors need to scope out molybdenum #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AMC Weighs In On Georgia’s Abortion Law While Contemplating A Big Change For ‘The Walking Dead’ #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
