<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Rolls-Royce Believes it Would Have Gone Bankrupt Without BMW’s Support  Considering how much Rolls-Royce charges fo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It Isn't Even Spring Yet, But This Affordable Trend Is Taking Over the World  We should preface by saying that this… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Long-Range 2019 Nissan Leaf Plus Starts at $37,445 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Aston Martin Valkyrie’s Hybrid V-12 Powertrain Makes 1,160 HP #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Celebrity Way to Wear Sneakers This Season #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kia’s Latest Electric Concept Car Has 21 Screens  Last week, we got our first look at the concept car Kia will show… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rolls-Royce Believes it Would Have Gone Bankrupt Without BMW’s Support #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2018 BMW X2 Long-Term Update 1: Fair Trade  Staff photographer Robin Trajano and I have agreed to swap long-term ca… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Trends All the Stylish Girls Are Wearing in Paris  With shows like Jacquemus and Dior already unfolding during Pa… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 BMW M340i xDrive Prototype Review: Almost an M3, With AWD #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Car Compare: 2019 Lexus ES 350 vs. TLX, Q50, MKZ, and LaCrosse  The ES is Lexus’ best-selling car, and it’s a best-… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Car Compare: 2019 Lexus ES 350 vs. TLX, Q50, MKZ, and LaCrosse #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 Tips on How to Choose the Perfect Wedding Band  While we tend to put most of our focus into searching for the per… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Safety Agencies to Investigate Fatal Tesla Crash in Florida #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019 Roush Raptor Looks Ready to Rumble #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fashion Forecast: 3 French Girls on Their Favorite Fall 2019 Trends #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Elon Tusk: Tesla Chief Changes Twitter Display Name #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Emerging London Brands You Need to Know About #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyft IPO Filing Shows Surging Revenue, Widening Losses  SAN FRANCISCO, March 1 (Reuters) – Lyft Inc inched closer t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone on Instagram Keeps Asking Me Where These Boots Are From #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Egg Yolk Eyes" Are the Weird Trend Makeup Artists Can’t Stop ‘Gramming #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seinfeld Sues the Dealer That Sold Him the Alleged Fake Porsche #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The "Basic" Skinny Jeans Fashion Girls Will Always Wear  Like most things in fashion, skinny jeans follow their own… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Maternity Dresses That Will Always Look Good in Photos  Anyone who's gone through the experience of carrying a c… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These Just Became Spring’s New It Shoes Overnight #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Trends All the Stylish Girls Are Wearing in Paris #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rivian Has Been Disguising Test Vehicles as Ford F-150s #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Audi R8 V10 Decennium Celebrates 10 Years of the 10-Cylinder Sports Car  If you’ve been waiting 10 years to buy an… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Diane Kruger Knows the Chicest Way to Wear Mango in Paris #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Spring Sneaker Outfits I’m Currently Drooling Over #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Under-$200 Items I Know Will Develop a Cult Following Come Spring  With March one day away, I think it's officia… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Dresses Everyone Will Wear to the Next Royal Wedding Just Launched #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ferrari F8 Tributo Is Brand’s Most Powerful Production V-8 Ever #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Refreshing or Revolting: Polestar 2 vs. Tesla Model 3  Despite some production challenges, the Tesla Model 3 was th… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Wore Skinny Jeans With $50 Sneakers From Amazon  Hot off the heels of Meghan Markle and Prince Harry… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Celebrity Way to Wear Sneakers This Season  There’s a reason we cover celeb style on the regular. Fashionable A… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Spring Things You’re About to See in Every French Girl’s Wardrobe #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ferrari F8 Tributo Is Brand’s Most Powerful Production V-8 Ever  We will miss the Ferrari 488 GTB, the powerful yet… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Dresses Everyone Will Wear to the Next Royal Wedding Just Launched  Remember that time (at least) three guests… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Luxury Lingerie Brands That Are Always Worth the Investment  Of all the ways you can show yourself some extra lov… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top Hairstylists Have Spoken—These Are the Best Cuts for Every Face Shape  Within the ever-colliding stratospheres… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fashion Forecast: 3 French Girls on Their Favorite Fall 2019 Trends  As we speak, Paris Fashion Week is just about… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYC Girls Are About to Be All Over This New Belt-Bag Trend  There’s a new accessory trend in town, and it’s coming… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Pieces All the Fashion Girls Just Bought From &amp; Other Stories  Where do we go when we want to shop for something… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019 Ram HD First Test: How 1,000 LB-FT Performs at the Track #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019 Ram HD First Test: How 1,000 LB-FT Performs at the Track  “Hey, man,” the Ram PR dude said to me. “Would you m… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Spring Ankle Boots to Wear With Skinny Jeans  Whether you live in skinny jeans on the reg or just pull the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Storm Jameson "For what I have received, may the Lord make me truly thankful. And more truly for what I have not re… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[U.S. Safety Agencies to Investigate Fatal Tesla Crash in Florida  WASHINGTON, March 1 (Reuters) – The National High… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Spring Things You're About to See in Every French Girl's Wardrobe  We've been talking a lot about items with a c… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Only 6 L.A. Nail Salons Fashion Girls Love #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Long-Range 2019 Nissan Leaf Plus Starts at $37,445 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PSA: We Found 17 Cute Jumpsuits for Petites  Let’s face it: No matter who you are, shopping can be a difficult task… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[4 Tips on How to Choose the Perfect Wedding Band #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Seinfeld Sues the Dealer That Sold Him the Alleged Fake Porsche  A few weeks ago, we learned that Jerry Seinfeld ha… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Biggest Wedding Dress Trends of 2019, According to a Bridal Expert  If you’re a bride-to-be searching for a str… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Henry David Thoreau "How many a man has dated a new era in his life from the reading of a book." #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kia’s Latest Electric Concept Car Has 21 Screens #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Car Compare: 2019 Lexus ES 350 vs. TLX, Q50, MKZ, and LaCrosse #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Emerging London Brands You Need to Know About  London is a city constantly buzzing with fresh talent. While the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[37 Things to Buy Your Friends as Birthday Gifts This Year  You think you know your friends well until it comes time… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Aston Martin Valkyrie’s Hybrid V-12 Powertrain Makes 1,160 HP  We’ve known for a while that the Aston Martin Va… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Under-$50 Reformation Item Everyone Is Buying For Spring  Bold statement: Tie-dye is the new animal print. The… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Wedding Bands for Pear-Shaped Engagement Rings  With all the attention we like to give finding the perfect… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[37 Things to Buy Your Friends as Birthday Gifts This Year #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 Mercedes-Benz GLC-Class Gets a Face-Lift and More Power #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everyone on Instagram Keeps Asking Me Where These Boots Are From  A big part of my job at Who What Wear is to try t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019 Roush Raptor Looks Ready to Rumble  Need a more butch-looking Ford F-150 Raptor? Well, for $13,000 and up—plus… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NYC Girls Are About to Be All Over This New Belt-Bag Trend #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Spring Sneaker Outfits I'm Currently Drooling Over  I've lived in Los Angeles long enough to have observed that t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Refreshing or Revolting: Polestar 2 vs. Tesla Model 3 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["Egg Yolk Eyes" Are the Weird Trend Makeup Artists Can't Stop 'Gramming  Makeup artists agree that in 2019, we'll s… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Wedding Bands for Pear-Shaped Engagement Rings #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Under-$50 Reformation Item Everyone Is Buying For Spring #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Diane Kruger Knows the Chicest Way to Wear Mango in Paris  Paris Fashion Week is in full swing, which means celebri… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rivian Has Been Disguising Test Vehicles as Ford F-150s  It’s difficult for automakers to keep their prototypes und… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Luxury Lingerie Brands That Are Always Worth the Investment #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust Me—Buy These 21 Things  Trust Me—Buy This is a monthly series where our market editor, Nicole Eshaghpour, mak… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trust Me—Buy These 21 Things #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2019 Volkswagen Jetta GLI Is Reasonably Priced Starting at $26,890 #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Maternity Dresses That Will Always Look Good in Photos #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Top Hairstylists Have Spoken—These Are the Best Cuts for Every Face Shape #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lyft IPO Filing Shows Surging Revenue, Widening Losses #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Spring Ankle Boots to Wear With Skinny Jeans #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Biggest Wedding Dress Trends of 2019, According to a Bridal Expert #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2018 BMW X2 Long-Term Update 1: Fair Trade #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meet Elon Tusk: Tesla Chief Changes Twitter Display Name  Feb 27 (Reuters) – Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Only 6 L.A. Nail Salons Fashion Girls Love  L.A. fashion girls love their nails as much as they love their snea… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[6 Very Important Ways We Wore Puffer Jackets This Season #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Under-$200 Items I Know Will Develop a Cult Following Come Spring #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The "Basic" Skinny Jeans Fashion Girls Will Always Wear #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PSA: We Found 17 Cute Jumpsuits for Petites #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton Wore Skinny Jeans With $50 Sneakers From Amazon #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 Mercedes-Benz GLC-Class Gets a Face-Lift and More Power  Mercedes is making a lot of news at this year’s Genev… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spied! Next-Gen Volkswagen Golf Looks Bigger  Our spy photographers caught the eighth-generation Volkswagen Golf ou… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Audi R8 V10 Decennium Celebrates 10 Years of the 10-Cylinder Sports Car #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Pieces All the Fashion Girls Just Bought From &amp; Other Stories #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2020 BMW M340i xDrive Prototype Review: Almost an M3, With AWD  Patient folks who wait a few months after the launc… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Long-Range 2019 Nissan Leaf Plus Starts at $37,445  Yesterday, Tesla announced that it would finally begin taking o… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[It Isn’t Even Spring Yet, But This Affordable Trend Is Taking Over the World #URL# #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
