<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Making History Review: Fox's Goofy Sitcom Makes Time Travel Fun Again #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[AMC Expands Chris Hardwick's 'Talking' Franchise to Air Year-Round #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Billy Campbell Crime Drama 'Cardinal' Renewed for Second and Third Seasons #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bobby Moynihan Cast in CBS Pilot, Signaling Potential 'SNL' Exit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NBC's Charlaine Harris Drama 'Redliners' Casts Its Lead #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[1920s Harlem Music Soap From L.A. Reid, 'Smash' Duo, Kenny Leon Set at Fox #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['RuPaul's Drag Race' Moves to VH1 From Logo #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bobby Moynihan Eyes SNL Exit With Lead Role on CBS Pilot Me, Myself &amp; I #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Howard Leeds, Writer and Producer on 'Brady Bunch,' 'Facts of Life' and 'Silver Spoons,' Dies at 97 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix Releases First Trailer for David Fincher's FBI Series 'Mindhunter' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel's Inhumans: Serinda Swan to Play Medusa on New ABC Series #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TV Ratings: Trump's Congress Address Falls From Comparable Obama Speech #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Alicia Keys Does a Killer Janis Joplin Impression #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Feud': How the Show-Stopping Opening Credits Came Together #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Dancing With the Stars' Cast Includes Simone Biles, Mr. T and... a Professional Dancer #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix's 'The Get Down' Hit With Union Claim for Holding Actors Too Long (Exclusive) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[ABC's Marvel Drama 'Inhumans' Finds its Black Bolt in Anson Mount #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flip or Flop Is Getting Five Spin-Offs #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shemar Moore and His Perfect Pecs Are Coming Back to TV #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Empire's Taye Diggs to Star in ABC's End of Days-Themed Doomsday Pilot #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oliver Hudson to Star in ABC's Emily Kapnek Comedy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casey Wilson to Play Busy Philipps' Sister in Tina Fey Comedy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fear the Walking Dead First Look: Strand's a Bloody Mess in Season 3 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Story Behind 'Switched at Birth's' Emotional Racism Episode #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arianne Zucker Is Leaving Days of Our Lives #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago Fire Is Getting a New Firefighter #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['13 Reasons Why' Trailer Previews Netflix's Teen Suicide Mystery Series #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RuPaul's Drag Race Moving From Logo to VH1 for Season 9 — Watch Video #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Flash Recap: Gorilla Warfare — Plus, How About That Ending?? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dancing With the Stars Season 24: Glee's Heather Morris, Mr. T, Charo, Nancy Kerrigan Among Cast #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drama High Pilot Adds Amy Forsyth as Theater Department's 'Queen Bee' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Suits Exclusive: Mike's Worst Nightmare Is Back to Crush His Dreams Again #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Reasons Why: Watch First Trailer for Netflix's Teen-Suicide Mystery #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shemar Moore to Star in 'S.W.A.T' Reboot for CBS #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fox's Marvel Pilot Adds Reign Alum Sean Teale as New Mutant Eclipse #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Flash: Who Knew a Gorilla Attack Could Be So Boring? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ratings: Trump's First Address to Congress Falls Short of Obama's #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Cattrall to Play U.S. President in Swedish Crime Series #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Voice': Alicia Keys Knows How To Land Artists on Second Night of Blind Auditions #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[G.L.O.W. Wrestling Comedy, Starring Alison Brie, Gets Netflix Premiere Date #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The Americans' Season 5 to Feature More Family Bonding #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RuPaul's Drag Race Gets Season 9 Premiere Date — and a New Network! #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rita Wilson Joins Fox's Sheldon Turner Drama #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel's Inhumans Has Found Its Silent Star #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenna Fischer to Star in ABC Comedy Pilot Splitting Up Together #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel's Inhumans Finds Its Queen Medusa #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TV Land Promotes Frank Tanki to General Manager #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Taye Diggs to Star in ABC's 'Doomsday' Drama #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Supergirl Photos: Will Kara's War With Cadmus Make an Enemy of Lena? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Russia's CTC Media Strikes Licensing Deal with NBCUniversal Dreamworks #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenna Fischer to Star in ABC's Emily Kapnek Comedy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fox's Marvel Drama Enlists 'The Goldbergs' Favorite #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mindhunter Teaser: Jonathan Groff Grills Serial Killers in New Netflix Drama #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get Ready to See a Whole Lot More of Chris Hardwick Talking #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dancing with the Stars' Season 24 Cast Includes an Olympic Gymnast and a Fool Pitier #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shemar Moore Plots Return to CBS, as Star of S.W.A.T. Drama Pilot #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Andrew Garfield, Stevie Nicks, Taylor Lautner Display Their Hidden Talents for James Corden #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casey Wilson Set as Co-Lead Opposite Busy Philipps in NBC's Tina Fey-Produced Comedy Pilot Sackett… #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Voice Recap: Five Alive #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fear The Walking Dead's First Look Photos Answer a Big, Spoilery Question #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katie Holmes Thinks the Kennedys Would Have Been Great at Social Media #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Criminal Minds Exclusive Sneak Peek: Reid Makes a Prison Buddy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The100 Mega Buzz: Who's About to Go Rogue? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arrow Exclusive: Curtis Reveals His Plan to Win Paul Back Without Quitting Team Arrow #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[iZombie Stars Debate Who's Better for Peyton: Ravi or Blaine? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Better Call Saul' Season 3 Will Offer First Look at Saul Goodman #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix "Just Getting Started" in Europe, CEO Reed Hastings Says #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Good Fight: John Cameron Mitchell Cast as 'Milo Yiannopoulos' in Stinging Alt-Right Takedown #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump Addresses Congress: 7 Supremely Uncomfortable Moments #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Get a First Look at GLOW, Jenji Kohan's '80s Pro Wrestling Comedy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Supernatural Preview: Is Mary in the Right? And Can She Recruit Her Sons? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jimmy Kimmel Hosts "Trump-Free Tuesday" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pitch on the Bubble: Keep or Cut? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bobby Moynihan Joins CBS Pilot, Meaning He May Leave SNL #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Switched at Birth Boss Talks Changing Perspective to Tackle Campus Racism #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Talking Dead's Chris Hardwick to Get Weekly Talk Show on AMC #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Marvel's 'Inhumans' Taps Serinda Swan as Female Lead #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[TVLine Items: Trump-Free Kimmel, Diana Rigg Joins Victoria and More #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Goldbergs Exclusive: Karate Kid Adam Learns to Sweep (Not the Leg Though) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How 'Chicago Justice' Became a Love Letter to 'Law and Order' #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YouTube Gets Into the Live Streaming Cable Business #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dr. Phil Moves From WME to UTA #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mary Kay Place Remembers 'Big Love' Co-Star Bill Paxton's "Enormous Energy, Stamina and Joy" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Reasons Why: Watch the Heart-Wrenching Trailer #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix Previews European Series 'Dark,' 'Suburra' and 'Cable Girls' in Berlin #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Grey's Anatomy: June Squibb and Hal Holbrook to Guest-Star #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix Boards BBC Drama 'Troy' From 'Night Manager' Writer #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fewer TVs Are Being Used These Days (And Some Folks Don't Even Have One) #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Training Day' Creator Remembers Bill Paxton: "He Swung for the Fences, Every Time" #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ask Ausiello: Spoilers on Big Bang, Bates, Bones, Nashville, Walking Dead, Flash, Once, Grimm and More #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Days of Our Lives' Arianne Zucker to Exit #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Web Video Star Casey Neistat Reveals His Plans at CNN #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hunted Finale Sneak Peek: Have Aarif &amp; Immad Clinched Victory... or Defeat? #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Archie Panjabi to Star in Fox's Campus Sexual Assault Pilot #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Casey Wilson to Star in NBC's Tina Fey Comedy #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['GLOW,' Netflix's Women's Wrestling Comedy, to Launch June 23 #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How 'Buffy the Vampire Slayer' Will Mark its 20th Anniversary #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Is Us: New Photos Sure Make It Look Like Kevin and Sophie Are Definitely Back On #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CNN Chief Jeff Zucker Unveils Plan to Dominate Digital: New Shows, a $25M YouTuber and Donald Trump (Of… #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Mindhunter First Look Is Pure David Fincher Goodness #URL# via #USER#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
