<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau bows and shakes hands with Iranian foreign minister in photo-op – True North #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can Moscow finish Nord Stream 2 gas pipeline despite US sanctions? ‘Never say never’ says Gazprom — RT Business News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[KNIGHT: Pipeline protests have nothing to do with supporting the Wet’suwet’en people – True North #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From clothes to condoms: Coronavirus is threatening global consumption in ways you never knew were possible — RT Wo… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon has 37,000 job listings - maybe its most ever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA confirms SpaceX will become the first private company to send astronauts to the space station #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 1,000 former DOJ officials call on U.S. Attorney General Barr to resign]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FCA plant closure: China supply issue causes Fiat Chrysler's Serbia plant closure, Auto News, ET Auto #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The cost of dying: How a spike in cremation rates is changing the funeral industry]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fossil-fuel industry hosts EU presidency #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#URL# NASA, Space Exploration and Astronomy News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Half a million Romanians want to stay in UK]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadians already quarantined on cruise ship in Japan to be isolated for another 2 weeks at home]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kosovo Parliament Not Informed on Signed Agreements with Serbia, Says Speaker Osmani    - Exit - Explaining Albania #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mountain Zlatibor, Serbia - Photo of the Day - Havana Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SpaceX Crew Dragon spacecraft nears last parachute tests before astronaut launch debut #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With eye on moon, NASA to seek new astronaut applicants in March]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Demonstrators gather at Confederation Bridge to back Wet'suwet'en hereditary chiefs]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Famed biologist Richard Dawkins sparks Twitter row with ‘eugenics would work for humans’ argument — RT World News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serbia's Natalija Kostic Gets Engaged to Boyfriend during WTA Thailand Open #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Scotsman - Scottish News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Local news, sports, business, politics, entertainment, travel, restaurants and opinion for Seat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RCMP mistakes stroke victim for drunk, leaving him half-paralyzed in jail cell for hours, lawsuit says]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Medium – Get smarter about what matters to you. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Copper wire thieves wreaking havoc on Seattle #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michel proposes GNI 1.074 percent for budget #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GM scraps historic Holden car brand in Australia - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is How a Society Dies #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uganda's Queen of Katwe star Nikita Pearl Waligwa dies aged 15 - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Auditors: Commission should update nuclear-safety rules #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[N.B. premier cancels controversial plan to close rural ERs overnight]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heathrow diversion: New York flight makes 'emergency landing' and passenger detained - MyLondon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The New York Times - Breaking News, World News &amp; Multimedia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[MALCOLM: Has anyone seen our Prime Minister? – True North #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Inside the meeting between Mohawks and Canada's Indigenous services minister]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SETI search of interstellar Comet Borisov finds no sign of alien 'technosignatures']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two injured in Moscow church knife attack #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Petr Pavlensky: Russian activist's girlfriend held over Macron ally sex video - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serbia Honors Author Handke Amid Anger Over Milosevic Ties #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[bne IntelliNews - Fiat halts production in Serbian plant as coronavirus disrupts supply chains #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Petition update · MEPs rally to support citizens rights post Brexit as our fight for an #HASHTAG# goes on ·… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your Monday Briefing - The New York Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chaos at Heathrow Airport as 'technical issues' cause mass disruption]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secretary Michael R. Pompeo and Senegalese Foreign Minister Amadou Ba at a Joint Press Availability - United States… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The New York Review of Books #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats fear rule of law crumbling under Trump]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Three Bright Planets Align In The Morning Sky]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amid a crime wave on Yakama Reservation, confusion over a checkerboard of jurisdictions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crossing the border to go to school in the US - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Egypt's health ministry announces first confirmed coronavirus case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson could rip up human rights to push through new terror law]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DROVER: It’s time to regulate online pornography in Canada – True North #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Washington Post: Breaking News, World, US, DC News &amp; Analysis - The Washington Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trudeau's office won't say if it recorded meeting with Iranian foreign minister]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA's iconic 'Pale Blue Dot' photo of Earth from space just got a 21st-century makeover]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EU plan on AI: new rules, better taxes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secretary Michael R. Pompeo's Meeting with Senegalese President Sall - United States Department of State #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The United States and Angola: Deepening an Important Strategic Partnership - United States Department of State #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mysterious 'fast radio bursts' from deep space repeat themselves every 16 days]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Is Belgium heading for new elections? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[French reforms: Why France is resisting Macron's push on pensions - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Brexit: France warns UK of bitter trade negotiations - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Celtic Barber – Unpacking My Bottom Drawer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Read The Liz Vicious Daily ▸ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[German president criticises US at Munich Conference #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Budget, Zuckerberg, Pelosi and Cayman Islands This WEEK #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Senate braces for fight over impeachment whistleblower testimony]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serbia and Cuba strengthen relations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Egg-freezing: What's the success rate? - BBC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Star City adventure: Take a sneak peek into India’s first space crew training in Russia — RT World News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘A little bit of excitement at no extra cost’: Sanders quips after TOPLESS anti-dairy protesters steal show at Neva… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lithuania National Day - United States Department of State #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SpaceX delays launch of 60 Starlink satellites due to rocket valve checks]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blockade continues despite 'modest progress' made in talks between federal minister and Tyendinaga Mohawk]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[EU parliament warns of data transfer risks due to UK immigration rules #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Candidates make electability arguments, talk Bloomberg as focus turns to more diverse states]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Local news, sports, business, politics, entertainment, travel, restaurants and opinion for Seat… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[bne IntelliNews - Serbia and Kosovo agree to restore railway, motorway links #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blue Jays legend Tony Fernandez dies at 57 from stroke, kidney complications]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Munich Security Conference: UK suffered because of its absence]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LIVE Starship Assembly at SpaceX Boca Chica Sunday Feb 16 - YouTube #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the EU can do for South Sudan - right now #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Solar Orbiter launches on historic mission to study the sun's poles]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SpaceX hires former NASA human-spaceflight chief]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Secretary Michael R. Pompeo and Senegalese Minister of Economy Amadou Hott at a Memoranda of Understanding Signing… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA has a plan for yearly Artemis moon flights through 2030. The first one could fly in 2021.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Federal government to bring home Canadians on board quarantined cruise ship]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 cases of environmental dissenters being cancelled – True North #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ethiopian migrants who make the desperate journey to Saudi Arabia via Yemen - Reporters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kurti Government Didn’t Authorize Signing of Two Agreements with Serbia - Exit - Explaining Albania #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FUREY: Majority of First Nations support Canadian energy – True North #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The last best chance for Donbas and peace in Europe? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mars breakthrough: UK-build, plasma-powered rocket could halve journey times to Red Planet]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Skylarks, chamois to be protected in RO]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists just watched a newfound asteroid zoom by Earth. Then they saw its moon.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[When is the best time to visit Banff, Lake Louise or Jasper?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Outrage as Downing Street adviser backs EUGENICS, mandatory birth control and giving kids mind-altering drugs — RT… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Thought biathlon was boring? Meet Dorothea Wierer – the Italian star sending fans wild at the 2020 World Championsh… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Net payer countries push back on EU budget plans #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hypnogoria: HYPNOGORIA 138 - A History of Horror Video Games Part I #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
