<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Hope Hicks returning to White House after 2-year hiatus - CBS News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi tears Trump's speech. Right there on the podium - Los Angeles Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Better Buy: General Electric vs. General Motors - The Motley Fool #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Democrats finish full day of presentations in Trump impeachment trial – Updates - USA TODAY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BlackRock Sends Huge Warning Shot at Companies Ignoring Climate Risk - Greentech Media News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 1700 healthcare workers infected with COVID-19, says China - CityNews Toronto #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More than 100 House Dems reject Trump peace plan in open letter]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Past Crises Tell Us About the Coronavirus - Wall Street Journal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NSA alerted Microsoft to major Windows 10 security flaw - CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The coronavirus death toll has jumped by 242 in just one day - SBS News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant’s death reverberates beyond sports - The Washington Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watch SpaceX Blow Up a Falcon 9 Rocket to Prove It's Safe for People - WIRED #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beijing’s Hong Kong envoy says lack of national security law allows ‘sabotage’ - South China Morning Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Flynn sentencing delayed amid bid to withdraw guilty plea - POLITICO #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[With Wuhan virus genetic code in hand, scientists begin work on a vaccine - The Jakarta Post - Jakarta Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[[Update: Google responds] Google Maps ‘hack’ uses 99 smartphones to create virtual traffic jams - 9to5Google #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[PlayStation 5: Patent Reveals Voice Control Support and New Vibration Feedback on PS5 Controller -… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[White House spokesperson: Media's 'obsession' with impeachment 'won't let up']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here’s where Vegas odds put the Democratic candidates ahead of the Iowa caucuses - Kansas City Star #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[College basketball picks -- Can UNC save its season against Duke? - ESPN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[American Heart Association's Go Red for Women encourages wearing of red - TribLIVE #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Report: Tom Brady 'embarrassed' by salary, plans to move out of New England - msnNOW #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Warren issues new disinformation pledge, promising to hold Facebook, Google and Twitter responsible - The Washingto… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Dancing dragon' feathered dinosaur fossil discovered in China - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[5 U.S. cities to start testing patients with flu-like symptoms for coronavirus - WRCB-TV #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CDC confirms second case of Wuhan coronavirus in US - WLWT Cincinnati #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2 Miami University students who returned from China are in isolation, being tested for coronavirus - WJW FOX 8 News… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[GOP senators request Hunter Biden travel records from Secret Service - Washington Examiner #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These lava lakes drained catastrophically—and scientists caught it in action - National Geographic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justice Roberts blocks Sen. Paul from naming whistleblower, source says – and Paul may force the issue - Fox News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Prince Harry makes big announcement after stepping back from royal role - HOLA! USA #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Buried in Trump's peace plan, a proposal that could strip thousands of Israeli Arabs of their citizenship - The Was… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NFL Draft 2020: Tua Tagovailoa's hip reportedly healing well, QB could be cleared for football activities soon - CB… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Most Iowa Democratic caucus-goers support a single-payer health-care plan - The Washington Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Susan Collins a yes on witnesses in impeachment Senate impeachment trial, Alexander is a no - The Washington Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chicago woman infects husband with coronavirus, first human-to-human spread in US - FOX 31 Denver #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Xinhua Headlines: Virus-hit Wuhan speeds up diagnosis, treatment of patients - Xinhua]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trevor Noah: Bloomberg talked about black people 'like they're crime piñatas' - The Guardian #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cruz scolds reporter who brought up his daughters]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[US military aircraft crashes in Afghanistan - ABC News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Telescope reveals details of sun's turbulent surface - The Denver Channel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Officials: Four Newport News students under self-monitoring at home for coronavirus - #URL# WVEC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ken Starr predicts the top witnesses for Trump impeachment trial - Fox News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lindsey Graham: Senate Intelligence Committee will call Ukraine whistleblower - Washington Examiner #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[2nd person dies from flu in Kansas City - KCTV Kansas City #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Texas A&amp;M student may have 2019 novel coronavirus, university says - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiger: Presidents Cup was 'Busiest week of my life']]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The distance, costs and health problems make a journey to the red planet incredibly risky - CTV News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden Could Be Impeached by GOP Over Ukraine if He Wins, Iowa Senator Says - Bloomberg #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NASA Team Salutes Spitzer Space Telescope - NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scientists fear the ‘doomsday glacier’ is in even more trouble than we feared - Raw Story #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sorry, You Might Get the Flu Twice This Year — Here’s Why - EcoWatch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[House Democrats not invited to trade deal bill signing at White House - CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders isn't a brawler — and that's why he can't beat Trump - New York Post #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[More coronavirus cases likely in San Diego, local hospital says - FOX 5 San Diego #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders responds to critics: My campaign is for the working class - Fox News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What will NASA's Mars 2020 rover be called? There's 155 names on the shortlist. - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police release names of family members shot, killed in Grantsville - KSTU FOX 13 Salt Lake City #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[British scientists accidentally discover immune cell that 'may kill all cancer' - TheBlaze #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dow Jones Rebounds 300 Points, As Coronavirus Spreads; Apple, Nike, Roku, Tesla Big Movers - Investor's Business Da… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Juul Won't Be the Only One Hurt By a Ban on Flavored Tobacco Products - The Motley Fool #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uber claims top spot in Indian ride-hailing market - TechCrunch #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenelle Evans Returns to The Land: Is She Back Together With David Eason?! - The Hollywood Gossip #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to stay healthy on a plane as coronavirus, flu, colds raise travel concerns - USA TODAY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown granted $110K bond on three charges - ESPN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LSU's Ed Orgeron almost got kicked off his college team; now he's a state hero - USA TODAY #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aaron Hernandez Netflix documentary: Recorded prison phone calls offer unfiltered look into mind of former NF -… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[FBI investigators visit Robert Hyde's home and office - CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spacewalking astronauts close to fixing cosmic ray detector - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WHO gives coronavirus official name, says vaccine is 18 months away - CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The distance, costs and health problems make a journey to the red planet incredibly risky - CTV News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Farrah Abraham: Investigated By CPS For Neglecting Sophia?! [UPDATED] - The Hollywood Gossip #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Coronavirus ruled out in Porter County patient, health officials say - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's the Xbox Series X Mystery Port? It's for Expandable Storage - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg ready for Facebook to pay more tax as he welcomes rules review - Fox Business #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['The little telescope that could' has retired. It changed how we see the universe - CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China's new coronavirus cases drop, but world still on alert - Reuters #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Heart disease can be prevented with lifestyle changes - Denver7 – The Denver Channel #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Happens to Your Body When You Get the New Coronavirus? - msnNOW #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dixville Notch, New Hampshire live results: The first primary polls open at midnight - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything we know about the Alpine Meadows avalanche that killed one, injured another - Sacramento Bee #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[200 people in Atlanta being monitored for coronavirus - CBS46 News Atlanta #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant helicopter crash: Clues found in wreckage as new cellphone video emerges - CBS News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Iran has a 'shockingly strong' war-crimes case against Trump over Soleimani's killing — and it could win - Business… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Red state Democrat says he's open to having Hunter Biden as witness in impeachment trial - CNN #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[L.A. County Sees Jump in Flu Activity, With at Least 70 Deaths Reported Statewide - KTLA Los Angeles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Super Nintendo World coming to Universal Orlando, too - Fox News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Solar Orbiter up close: Inside the clean room with the next sun probe (photos) - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eli Manning announces his retirement New York Giants - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Robert Kraft Gives Hope To Patriots Nation, 'We Plan To' Bring Back Tom! - TMZ #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘The Marvelous Mrs Maisel’ Cast Dedicates SAG Award Wins To The Late Brian Tarantina - Deadline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These Are the 3 American Firefighters Who Died in the Australia Plane Crash - The New York Times #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Don't Save for Retirement Until You've Hit This Key Milestone - The Motley Fool #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[China virus outbreak death toll hits six with more than 300 infections confirmed today - CBS News #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Leaked Photo From Chinese Conference on Coronavirus Response Reveals Hundreds of Medical Workers Have Been Infected… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's a way to beat the tax burden for IRA heirs - CNBC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Soaring Inflation and Crashing Home Sales: Coronavirus Devastates China’s Economy - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Deadly illness on rise in U.S., and it’s not the coronavirus - #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Microsoft Confirms Massive Windows 10 Upgrade Changes - Forbes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Samsung Galaxy S20+ leak confirms 120Hz display, ultrasonic fingerprint scanner, and no headphone jack -… #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
