<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Trivago Spokesman's DWI Case Dismissed After Alcohol Ed Classes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dog the Bounty Hunter's Daughter, Lyssa Chapman, Arrested in Hawaii #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rich the Kid Sued by Management Company for Over $3.5 Million #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessica Alba -- Good Genes or Good Docs?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown Suspect In Battery and Burglary, Cops Working On Arrest Warrant #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Information Society Singer Kurt Harland 'Memba Him?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump Sarcastically Tweets About Cory Booker Dropping Out #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess Who This Brace Face Turned Into! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vanessa Bryant Says Kobe and Gigi Memorial Will Go Down Feb. 24 at Staples Center #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serena Williams Gets Boxing Lesson From Mike Tyson #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trick Daddy Looks Horrible in Mug Shot Because of Lupus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj's Brother Sentenced to 25 Years to Life for Child Rape #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Cheer' Cast Hot Bods -- Guess Who! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Keanu Reeves, Carrie-Anne Moss On Set for 'Matrix 4' in San Francisco #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mary Carey Fighting 'Pippi Longstocking' Tami Erin in Celebrity Boxing #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nathan Bookman on 'Good Times' 'Memba Him?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rudy Giuliani Says Prez Trump's Right, Put Pete Rose In The HOF! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Love Island' Host Caroline Flack Dies by Suicide at 40 Before Trial #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Bad News Bears' Jeffrey Davies Takes First Steps Months After Crash #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenelle Evans' Ex-Husband Courtland Rogers Arrested for Drugs, Larceny #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Aerosmith's Joey Kramer Says He's Going to Grammy Event Despite Court Ruling #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazing! The Photo Of Britney Spears That Will Leave You Shocked Doesn’t Look Like Her! - Code List #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj's Rosa Parks Line Was No Disrespect, Timing a Coincidence #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Hudson In Character For Aretha Franklin Biopic 'Respect' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mya Has Secret Wedding in Seychelles, First Look at Her Dress #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Biden Calls Voter 'Lying Dog-Faced Pony Soldier,' Credits John Wayne #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Serena Williams Shuts Down Question About Meghan Markle, 'Good Try' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Little Nathan Jr. in 'Raising Arizona' 'Memba Him?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rick Fox Says WNBA Stars Can Ball Out In NBA, Kobe's Right! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown Performs First Show in FL, Throws Cash Onstage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle &amp; Prince Harry Abandon Royal Titles, Queen Bids Farewell #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ronnie Ortiz-Magro Giddy As Woman Flashes Him in Hollywood #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[E-40 Has Custom Tequila for the 49ers After Super Bowl, Win or Lose #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['1917' Sam Mendes Ad Claims Early Oscars Victory, Apparently a Mistake #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Antonio Brown 911 Call, Driver Claims AB Was High #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Quibi Teams Up With Chance The Rapper For First Super Bowl Ad #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tell It To My Heart Singer Taylor Dayne 'Memba Her?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bo Jackson's Rare Broken Bat From Final Season Up For Auction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Glee' Star Dot Jones Recovering After Emergency Heart Surgery #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Wendy Williams Didn't Break Girl Code with NeNe Leakes Quitting 'RHOA' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lindsay Lohan Shouts Out High School Production of 'Freaky Friday' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Ultimate Ranking of Britney Spears' 13 Top 10 Hits - E! Online #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj, Meek Mill Reignite Beef with Outrageous Accusations #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nicki Minaj Regrets Mudslinging With Meek Mill on Social Media #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Juice WRLD Died from Accidental OD of Oxycodone and Codeine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cardi B Masks Face With Bling At Offset's Fashion Show in Paris #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mark Cuban Says 'I Would Support' Changing NBA Logo to Kobe Bryant #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rep. Tim Ryan Says Obamas' First Oscar Nomination Wasn't About Luck #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[L.A. High-Rise Fire Leads to Daring Rescues #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jamie Lynn Spears' Baby Daddy Casey Aldridge Arrested For Burglary #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess Who This Happy Kid Turned Into! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guns N' Roses Ex-Guitarist DJ Ashba Cuts Plea Deal in DUI Case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shareef O'Neal Reveals Biggest Lesson He Learned From Kobe Bryant #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[R. Kelly GF Joycelyn Savage's Sad Mug Shot After Fight with Azriel Clary #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber's Kobe Bryant Tribute Art Raises $12,000 for MambaOnThree #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama Releases 2020 Workout Playlist, Oldies &amp; Edited #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's The Big Frigin' Difference? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rep. Andre Carson Says Political Ads During Super Bowl Better Be Fun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sergey Kovalev Blew Off $650k Payment to Female Assault Accuser, Lawsuit Claims #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pamela Anderson, New Hubby Producer Jon Peters First Pic Together #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Vic Mensa Arrested for Felony Possession of Brass Knuckles #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Opens Up About Lyme Disease and Health Struggles in Docuseries #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Guess Who This Bow Baby Turned Into! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Netflix's 'Cheer' Producers Turned Down Daytona Footage, Varsity Claims #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ugandan Disney Actress Nikita Pearl Waligwa Dead at 15 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[College Football Player Body Slams Cop During Arrest, Insane Police Video #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jessica Simpson's Book Tour Security Beefing Up After Anti-Fur Protests #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jenelle Evans and David Eason Back Living Together, Get New Pet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WWE's Alexa Bliss, 'My Pig Is Cuter Than My Butt' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lizzo Rocks Strappy Gold Swimsuit on Heels of Jillian Michaels Remarks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nikki Bella Showing Off Her Baby Bump After Pregnancy Reveal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[YG Will Perform at Grammys After Arrest and Release, Lawyer Says #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boosie Badazz Cops Sweet Plea Deal in Georgia Weed Case #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Future Claims Alleged Baby Mama Has Mental Health Issues #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tom Brady Jokes About Julian Edelman's Arrest #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump Attends Daytona 500, Jokes He Wants to Race #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Timbaland Aiming to Lose Nearly 200 lbs. After Kicking Opioid Addiction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dog the Bounty Hunter Has Chill Birthday at Benihana, No Sign of Moon #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Future's Covering His Son's Legal Case Financially, Kid's Not 'Indigent' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Team Roc Leaks Mississippi Prison Video of Violence, Inhumane Conditions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cops Grab Alleged 'Penis Man' Graffiti Artist in Arizona #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Boosie Badazz Says White Battle Rapper Deserves Punch For Using N-Word #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Carter Released Early From Prison After Texting Suicide Conviction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mario Lopez and Elizabeth Berkley in Character For 'Saved By The Bell' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson Posts Emotional Goodbye To Dad After Death, 'I'm In Pain' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[DaBaby Sued By Alleged Miami Battery Victim #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NY Giants Owner Won't Commit To Eli Manning In 2020, 'Everything's Up In The Air' #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tank Says Sex Absolutely Counts as Acceptable Valentine's Day Gift #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jordan Belfort Says Bernie Madoff Deserves to Die in Prison #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Famous NFL Fans Having A Field Day! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chainsaw in 'Summer School' 'Memba Him?! #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Johnny Depp Jams on Guitar During High School Charity Concert #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barstool Sports President Dave Portnoy Talks New Riches, Super Bowl Bets #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tekashi 6ix9ine Sued for Using 'Stoopid' Intro Without Permission #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meek Mill Gets Into Shouting Match With Ex Nicki Minaj's Husband #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chuck Liddell Hopes Cowboy Cerrone Beats Conor McGregor At UFC 246 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Khabib Shoots Down $100 Mil Rematch with 'Idiot' Conor McGregor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blac Chyna Says She Didn't Injure Rob Kardashian Besides a Broken Heart #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Death and Cynic Drummer Sean Reinert Dead at 48 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Joe Giudice Parties with a Flock of Hot Babes in Mexico, Teresa Who? #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
