<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[CTM Spotify Playlist: June 10, 2016 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fifty Dead in Mass Shooting at Popular Orlando Nightclub: The attack is the deadliest in the h... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Authorities End Search for Man Who Fell Into Yellowstone Hot Spring: The 23-year-old wandered ... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Richard Simmons to Transition Into a Woman?: Rumors of Richard Simmons becoming "Fiona" are un... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump Tweets That He 'Appreciates the Congrats' on Being Right About Terrorism: Donald Trump t... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Tonys' touching tribute to Orlando victims #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kareem Abdul-Jabbar on Muhammad Ali: "His spirit was indomitable" #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# So much speculation and so few REAL facts!   These people don't know how to give up!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Gee tRump, where did you serve in Vietnam??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# A REAL "B" list of "celebrities!   Where did you find these people??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# #USER# Such a nice man...a total idiot!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# There is NO "National Emergency" due to immigration in this country, you idiot!  I've been here in… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Maelyn is absolutely phenomenal !!   Love that singing!!  #USER# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Watchdog: FDA food recall procedures put consumers at risk #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Do YOU ever really read these notes that people post - or are these just passed on to another offi… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And Pat Buchanan was quoting Dylan Thomas...of course Trump wouldn't know that...since… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# And WHY is this border issue suddenly such a big deal???   Not since the days of the Alamo has the… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oklahoma Police Get New Device for Civil Forfeitures: While Oklahoma police did get a new devi... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# And WHO made up that Tweet?   Certainly not you.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sanders meets with Obama as Democrats push for unity #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["No question" privilege a factor in ex-Stanford swimmer's sentence #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gift cards used to lure patients for genetic test scam #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Are you really soooo stupid and self-centered??   Can't you see that this "gov't shutdown" is doin… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Biden letter praises Stanford sex assault victim's courage #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I thought you were going to"Make America Great" in the last election!  Well, that obviously didn't… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ...and WHY is this incident such a big deal to you???   I've lived with the same borders for my 72… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Will Las Vegas finally land a major professional sports team? #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Need a getaway? Ditch Wi-Fi for the wilderness in a tiny house #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tales of heroism emerge from Orlando mass shooting #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This is what this SICK group is up to down here in Florida... I can't believe that they have stood up sooo long - a… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.#USER# #HASHTAG#.  Do away with the stupid "rap" stuff...I muted my TV]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Terrifying Warning' About Ice Cream Trucks and Chloroform: A viral social media post claimed ... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Since I worked in healthcare for over 40 years I was always required to get flu shots...AND I've neve… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pentagon investigates military insurance fraud #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What does Obama-Biden endorsement mean for Clinton? #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Can a parrot serve as witness in murder trial? #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT to #HASHTAG# #URL# love this girl!!   Great singer]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[RT #USER#: RT if you need a drink after tonight’s episode. #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl Scouts CEO on global sisterhood, attracting minorities #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orlando commissioner: "This is the largest crime scene we've had to process" #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tango: See more with a new kind of phone #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Eye Opener at 8: President Obama endorses Clinton #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why Orlando gunman calling 911 during attack is "very significant" #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# With all the hype of "Women Now" tonight, what's up with FloRida and the scantily clad dancers???   Bad t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's the deal with the Voice and Apple Music???   I will NOT purchase anything from that company!   I use only An… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Donald Trump on Orlando shooting: "We need much better intelligence" #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pat Robertson: “Orlando Shooting Is God’s Punishment for SCOTUS’ Same-Sex Marriage Ruling”: Fa... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gawker files for bankruptcy protection #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orlando's first openly-gay commissioner "heartbroken" by massacre #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# So WHY is the stock market diving soooo badly??]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Since you claim to be soooo wealthy, why am I getting emails and phone messages asking for money f… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reward offered for Olympic gold medal stolen from car #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA["48 Hours:" A slain student's case unlocks long-unsolved crimes #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jail Installs New Olympic-Sized Swimming Pool for Stanford Rapist: A fake news article reporte... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# What a creepy looking photo...and probably what he REALLY looks like!   I've gotten to the point whe… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# ...and what about crooked Donald Trump?   Maybe you should just resign rather than be impeached!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nightclub shooter was body builder, security guard #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Detroit man wrongly imprisoned for drug killings released #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orlando Shooter Was a Registered Democrat: Orlando shooter Omar Mateen registered as a Democra... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# I honestly believe at this point you'll go into the history books as the single most horrible pres… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama Hugging Daughter After Graduation: A student with a quote from Prophet Muhammad... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Why in holy hell are they keeping Paul in the house?   I think it's a rig by the producers to add a point of interest]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Question...What justification do these officers have for auto or body searches just because"they sm… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[At least 50 killed at Orlando nightclub shooting #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #USER# And the American public no longer believe ANYTHING that tRump fella has to say... he's l… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Orlando shooter able to buy guns despite being on FBI radar #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Chump...as to this "wall" nonsense - you're an immature idiot.   Get over it!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[CTM Spotify Playlist: June 9, 2016 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[.#USER#-. We love your singing!  And you're sooooo beautiful on top of it all.  Keep up the great work!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Crowds gather along Louisville streets to honor Muhammad Ali #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Uncounted California Ballots: It's true that millions of California ballots have yet to be cer... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Israel retaliates after deadly terror attack at market #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Victoria Woodhull Was the First Female Presidential Candidate, Not Hillary Clinton: Was Victor... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Barney Frank Criticizes Bernie Sanders: A quote about the Democratic party has been incorrectl... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[LGBT Phoenix Endorsed Trump After Orlando Shooting?: Two Twitter accounts purportedly linked w... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Google Manipulates Searches for Hillary Clinton?: A viral video accused the search engine of m... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Girl Scouts CEO: "We really need to invest more in girls" #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Abandoned Military Base's 'Experimentation Room': A photograph of a control room at an abandon... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Could a parrot serve as witness in Michigan murder trial? #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Stories of heroism emerge from Orlando nightclub massacre #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Link Latte 242 #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nile Rodgers on inspiration, composing music #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Facebook to Delete Photographs Automatically Synced from Phone: Some Facebook users received a... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Judge Curiel a Member of 'Latino KKK Hate Group' Called 'La Raza': U.S. District Judge Gonzalo... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Who designated these people as "celebrities?".  I watched part of the first episode and NO MORE!   A bunch of " has beens!"]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA['Multiple Shooters' At Orlando Nightclub Rumors: A post on Facebook claimed that multiple shoo... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#HASHTAG# show SUCKS this season...and WHY is Paul the smuck still there?   I'm not watching anymore of this garbage...]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tennis star vows to appeal multi-year doping ban #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Adam, I was just watching the video of you and Sara Evans doing the "LEATHER AND LACE" duet...HER voice is sooo muc… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# #HASHTAG#.   Why is Chris Kroeze still in the runnings???   Nasal voice!!]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Mom Shaves Daughter's Head After She Bullied Girl with Cancer: A video purportedly shows a mot... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# That border is DEFINITELY not the big source of crime in this country!!    Where have YOU BEEN living??  In your dreams?]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER#.  You're fabulous up there on stage!   Ya got all my votes tonight!  I'll bet all of your male clas… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# You stupid a**hole- a "national crisis" in your dreams!  Get over this boyhood want for a "wall" t… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bill Clinton, Mike Tyson to be part of Muhammad Ali memorial service #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Significance of Orlando gunman calling 911 during standoff #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[#USER# Why is it that the Texas border guards say a wall or fence will do LITTLE to prevent illegal borde… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nile Rodgers reflects on music career and success #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kevin Hart Beaten at Miami Club: A photograph purportedly showing actor Kevin Hart with facial... #URL# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiny wilderness houses encourage vacationers to disconnect #URL# #HASHTAG# #HASHTAG#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
