<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[24 Truly Waterproof Mascaras That Withstand Sobbing, Beach Vacations, and Sweaty Commutes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Reasons Seaweed Belongs In Your Diet and Beauty Routine #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner Shared a Rare Glimpse of Herself Makeup Free #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Thoughtful Mother's Day Gifts to Give First-Time Moms #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Wear White This Spring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Spring Shoe Trends to Start Shopping Now #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Curious About Clean Beauty? Here Are 4 Things to Know #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[27 Low-Back Swimsuits That Are Anything But Boring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What Is a Hair Gloss, Anyway? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[17 Dry Shampoos I Have Known and Loved #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Powder FaceTunes Your Face IRL and Is Only $12 Right Now #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Cara Delevingne on RuPaul, Gender Fluidity, and Being More Real on Instagram #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beauty 101: How to Get the Perfect Red Lip #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If You Love RuPaul's Drag Race, Support Your Local Drag Show #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[She has fire in her soul and grace in her heart. &lt;3 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian Enlisted a Squad of Lookalikes to Sell You Her Carolina Lemke Eyewear Collection #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[8 Bikini Trends That Are Taking Over Instagram This Summer #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[14 Pink Lipsticks So Good You Will Want to Quit Red #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here's How To Get Your Longest Lashes Ever #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Things Stephanie Shepherd Packs to Survive Coachella #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Protective Summer Hairstyles for Women of Color #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[You've Been Sleeping on Hot Rollers and It's Time to Change That #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[23 Fresh Updates on the Classic Straw Hat #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Best Dressed: The Week in Outfits #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[If I had to teach someone just one thing about lip color, it would be this: Find a lipstick that looks good on your… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Face Wipes For When You're Too Lazy To Wash Your Face #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Your dresses should be tight enough to show you're a woman and loose enough to show you're a lady. - Edith Head #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Rebecca Taylor's New Collection Will Help You Battle Your Office AC #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beauty 101: How to Draw the Perfect Cat-Eye #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Louis Vuitton's Cruise 2020 Show Will Take Off at JFK Airport #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Add a Pop of Pastel With These Spring Trends #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Sugaring Hair Removal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This $8 Drugstore Liquid Liner Gives Me the Easiest, Most Perfect C #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 High Cut Swimsuits That Are Sexier Than Bikinis #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Following Blackface Controversy, Gucci Launches Program to Promote Diversity and Unity #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 13 Best Eye Creams For Every Issue and Every Budget, According To a Dermatologist #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Reformation Launched Its Permanent Plus Size Collection Just in Time for Spring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drugstore Beauty Finds That Feel Expensive #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Best Shampoos for Oily Hair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Céline Dion Is the New Global Spokesperson for L'Oréal Paris #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What's Getting a Stitch Fix Box Like? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dermatologists Pick 15 Sunscreens Light Enough to Wear Under Makeup #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[25 Unique Mother's Day Gifts You Haven't Thought Of Yet #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NAILS; One thing you can get into shape without exercise.]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Royal Off-Duty Looks of All Time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Temporary Hair Dye Sprays Perfect for Festival Season and Commitment-Phobes #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Week in Parties #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Using Lavender Oil #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See the Hottest Bags Making Their Debut at Paris Fashion Week #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Laser Skin Tightening #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kimora Lee Simmons Leissner Is Bringing Back Baby Phat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[16 Pairs of Leggings You Can Wear to a Real or Fake Workout #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Travel Hack Stephanie Shepherd Uses on All Her Flights #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Best Sunscreen For Your Face, According to ELLE Editors #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[21 Classic Sunglasses for Every Face Shape #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Best Green Concealers for Camouflaging Pimples and Redness #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[21 Lightweight Jackets That Will Get You Through Spring’s Confusing Weather #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hailey Baldwin and Kendall Jenner Dress in Layers Despite the 80-Degree Coachella Weather #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Travel Beauty Products You Should Pack, According to an Expert Who's Been to 70 Countries #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Affordable Bridesmaid Dresses You Won't Be Mad About Buying #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hailey Baldwin Is the New Face of Levi's 501 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Priyanka Chopra, Sophie Turner Put Beach Bodies on Display in Miami #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This Silk Pillowcase Would Make Sleeping Beauty Want To Go Back To Bed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Spring Makeup Trends to Start Wearing Now #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[7 Hair Ring Ideas to Dress Up Braids, Buns, and Everything in Between #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Amazon Just Launched Its Own In-House Beauty Line and It's All Under $40 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These Straight Leg Jeans Are Sustainable, Not Too Wide, and They Weirdly Smell Great? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[3 Ways to Style Sneakers #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What You Need to Know About Jennifer Lopez's Engagement Ring #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A-Beauty Is the Opposite of K-Beauty— and It's Here to Save You Time #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hermès Is Officially Launching Makeup and Skincare #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Everything You've Ever Wanted to Know About Microneedling #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Beauty 101: How to Apply Fake Lashes So They Look Super Realistic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to Plan an Outfit Around a Bathing Suit #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[11 Pairs of Uncool Mom Shorts That Are Actually Cool #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[9 Ways to Wear Gold Nail Polish, the Power Suit of Manicures #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The happiest girls always have the prettiest nails. - Tammy Taylor #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Emilia Clarke Wore a Breathtaking Cinderella-Like Gown to the Game of Thrones Final-Season Premiere Party #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Fashion is Art and You are the Canvas! &lt;3]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kristen Bell's Favorite De-Puffing Eye Patches Are 50 Percent Off Today Only #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Are Necklace Bags the New Fanny Pack? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 Sunglasses Chains for the Person Who Always Loses Their Shades #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The 8 Best Moisturizers for Reviving Dull, Coarse Natural Hair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[What the Does 'Business Casual' Even Mean Anymore? #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Gigi and Bella Hadid Were Two of the Best-Dressed Guests at Marc Jacobs' Wedding #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Shop 7 Street Style Pics We Love #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[15 On-Sale Pieces That Will Help You Deal With Tricky Spring Weather #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the power of #HASHTAG# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[My Hair Takes Forever to Dry and This Cuddly Pink Towel Cut My Dry Time in Half #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Best Tanning Oils for Those Who Love the Sun—and Those Who Hate It #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A Definitive Ranking of the Best, FUPA-Defying Mom Jeans #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[10 Things You've Gotta See at Banana Republic #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hailey Baldwin Reveals the ''Biggest'' Secret About Her Appearance and It's Not What You'd Expect #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Yes, You Can Straighten Your Hair Without Using Heat #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The Perfect Brushes For Your Dream Eyebrows #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Here’s How One ELLE Editor Gets Dressed For Work, Including a Full-On Ball Gown #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Solid &amp; Striped Adds Bags and Clothes to Their Mix #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[13 Full-Coverage Swimsuits, Because Not Everyone Is Down For Cheeky Bikinis #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Benefit Cosmetics Creates Brow Shades for Redheads and Grey Hair (Finally!) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Hallelujah, I Found a Natural, Eco-Friendly Deodorant That Works #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
