<author lang="en">
  <documents>
    <document><![CDATA[Amy Schumer ‘Feels Lucky’ to Have One Embryo as She Shares Update on IVF Journey #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pearl Harbor survivor and USS Arizona crew member has died at 97 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kawhi lights out from beyond arc to claim MVP #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Former college volleyball stars and their two daughters killed in crash #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analysis: Did Xi Jinping know about the coronavirus outbreak earlier than first suggested? #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why stocks keep moving higher. And higher. And higher. #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sonic the Hedgehog pips Detective Pikachu to record box office opening – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Dakota Kai def. Tegan Nox (Street Fight) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Back to the Future deepfake inserts Robert Downey Jr. and Tom Holland – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kobe Bryant Honored in Touching Tribute by Jennifer Hudson at NBA All-Star Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber on Love, Fatherhood, Billie Eilish &amp; More: 5 Revelations from the Star’s Zane Lowe Interview #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The coronavirus crisis is raising questions over China’s relationship with the World Health Organization #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Photos of the Week: 2/9/20 – 2/15/20 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kate Middleton opens up about ‘mommy guilt’ on podcast #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jalaiah Harmon, the teen who created the viral Renegade dance, performed at the NBA All-Star game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Nearly 12,000 Democrats turn out for first day of early voting in Nevada #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A police officer working at Walmart shot multiple times while trying to stop a shoplifter #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Air Force Academy blames accidents for traffic at NHL game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two people are dead after getting trapped under avalanche they accidentally triggered #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Katy Perry Gets Choked Up Over Heartwarming Audition in ‘American Idol’ Season 3 Premiere #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[WWE to hold largest talent tryout in Saudi Arabia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Van Jones Says Dwyane Wade Was Courageous for Supporting Zaya #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[See house collapse in landslide #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiffany Haddish, Chadwick Boseman and More Celebs Attend NBA All-Star Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Oyo’s revenue surged in FY19, but loss widened, too #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daytona 500 postponed until Monday because of bad weather #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Arsenal are finally putting Arteta’s ideas into practice #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Disney actress Nikita Pearl Waligwa, who appeared in ‘Queen of Katwe,’ dead at 15 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sheamus serves as honorary pace car driver for NASCAR’s 62nd Daytona 500 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Canadian farmers have a plan for tackling climate change #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Jennifer Hudson &amp; Common Perform Emotional Kobe Bryant Tributes at 2020 NBA All-Star Game #URL# #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The BroserWeights def. The Undisputed ERA to become NXT Tag Team Champions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[SEC stacked with NCAA Tournament bubble teams #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This father lost his wife during childbirth. Now he’s taking action #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Howard, No. 18 Kentucky women top No. 6 Mississippi St 73-62 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle and Prince Harry All Smiles After California Trip #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[After a slow start, the Renegades beat the Wildcats 25-18 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Power Rankings: Maryland is moving in the right direction #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NXT Women’s Champion Rhea Ripley def. Bianca Belair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[P.J. Walker throws 3 TD’s as Roughnecks beat Battlehawks, 28-24]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[John Tortorella talks about matching up with the New Jersey Devils #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Whitney Cummings and Miles Skinner End Engagement A Year and a Half After His Proposal #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Americans evacuated from Japan cruise ship as coronavirus cases top 71,000 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Darvish: Astros should be stripped of ’17 World Series title #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All the Ways Kobe Bryant Was Honored at the NBA All-Star Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Today’s Presidents Day. Here’s what’s open and closed #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kawhi Leonard named the first winner of the Kobe Bryant MVP Award at the NBA All-Star Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Daytona 500 postponed until Monday by rain #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Death toll tops 1,770 from coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[BattleHawks’ comeback falls short in 28-24 loss to Roughnecks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[School sends 6-year-old with ADHD to mental health facility #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Downhill’ hits the slopes and the skids #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Column: As big fight looms, poolside with the Gypsy King #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Last shot wins: Team LeBron wins All-Star Game 157-155 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders is in a very weird position #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Bald eagles across the United States are dying from lead poisoning #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Analyst: I’ve seen thousands of sentencings. I’ve never seen this #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Blackwood makes 52 saves, Devils beat Blue Jackets 4-3 in SO #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[President Trump Attends Daytona 500, Jokes He Wants to Race #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[‘Recess’ Voice Actor Jason Davis Dead at 35 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NHL-best Bruins beat Rangers 3-1 for 9th win in 10 games #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Ne-Yo Splits From Wife Crystal Smith After 4 Years of Marriage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kevin Stenlund talks about gaining confidence despite the team’s loss #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[From Europe to America, G2 Esports’ brash frontman Ocelote is building an empire #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pelosi, Pompeo turn up the heat on China’s Huawei at security conference – CNET #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Sources: Cavs, Beilein discussed parting ways #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Shaves Off His Mustache, Teases Its Return #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Paying homage to greatness — 2020 NBA All-Star Game showed the power of basketball #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Follow live: Team LeBron vs. Team Giannis in All-Star format that honors Kobe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Trump campaign manager deletes Air Force One photo after realizing it’s from 2004 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Drew Carey’s Ex-Fiancee Amie Harwick Murdered in Hollywood Hills #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Original Content podcast: ‘Mythic Quest’ is a likable comedy with a single standout episode #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Two homes collapse in landslide along the Tennessee River #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[How to protect yourself from coronavirus #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Police found more than 1,400 marijuana plants inside a building in Northern California #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Why China is destroying some of its cash #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[This video of J.J. Watt dancing with his grandma is the cutest thing you’ll see today #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Liverpool smiling, PSG fretting as Champions League returns #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Chaka Khan Roasted on Twitter Over Her National Anthem Performance at the 2020 NBA All-Star Game… #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Magic leads tributes to Kobe at All-Star Game #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Original Content podcast: ‘Mythic Quest’ is a likable comedy with a single standout episode #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Missing Milwaukee woman and two daughters found dead in a garage #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[These people caught the coronavirus and survived #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Implosion fails to take down entire building #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A black student is suing law-enforcement officers after he says he was handcuffed and threatened with a gun #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Pederson, Stripling back to work with Dodgers after no trade #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NXT TakeOver Portland: Live results and reactions #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[NXT Women’s Champion Rhea Ripley vs. Charlotte Flair #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The sights, sounds and highlights of NBA All-Star Sunday, featuring Team LeBron vs. Team Giannis #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[The fourth quarter of the All-Star Game will never be the same again #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Tiger ‘just off,’ finishes last at Riviera after 77 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[One thing we’ve learned from wagering on the XFL through two weeks #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Lightning acquire F Blake Coleman from Devils ahead of NHL trade deadline #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[No. 4 SD State beats Boise State 72-55, remains undefeated #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Kanye West to Open NBA All-Star Game With Special Performance (Exclusive) #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[A’s Liam Hendriks helps fire victims back home in Australia #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Garza scores 24 points; No. 21 Iowa beats Minnesota 58-55 #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[All-Star weekend, as expected, was about honoring Kobe #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Scott wins at Riviera, Park captures 20th LPGA Tour title #URL#]]></document>
    <document><![CDATA[Birthday girl and her friends dressed as Target employees and took over the store #URL#]]></document>
  </documents>
</author>
